Secret
Don't smile.
You would smile like that,
are you also... going to leave me?
Once you get what you want,
you are also going to leave me.
You told me to do what you tell me.
Until you tell me to leave, Boss...
I will not go.
♫ I made that person cry
♫ Because of my incredibly bad obsession
♫ If the tears steal the heart and disappear
♫ Because I thought she would come closer
♫ I believe that I love you
♫ It's shaking me like crazy
♫ If this limping love of mine
♫ If it moves near, because you might hide from fear
♫ Even though I say I'm hurt as if I could die, I only watch
♫ If the tears knew my heart
I was wondering how you entered the Recipe Contest, but
the taste isn't half bad.
How did you know...
Without even knowing that,
do you think I would've given you this work?
What?
I'll send Gwang Soo, so wait, alright?
What do you mean selling?
The board of directors made a decision today.
Once our financial team evaluates
and comes up with a price,
it will go directly to the sales process.
If we secure invesment with the restaurant as a collateral,
we don't have to sell, right?
Where that kind of funding is possible,
Hannam-dong is the only place.
We can't sell the restaurant, before my father returns.
The decision will be made by my father!
I'll make an appointment,
but don't expect much.
Everybody wants a piece of the action, but
Hyung, isn't K-Group attractive to you?
Because he wanted more than what he deserves,
even abandoning his children,
I grew up watching my father like that.
This much is sufficient for me.
Jo Min Hyeok was here.
It seems your expression is not happy.
No, I threw a good punch.
But, it didn't make me feel better.
You heard the Board of Directors' decision, right?
Jo Min Hyeok,
If he can't keep the restaurant management rights,
it will be more difficult in the future.
No. The way I see it, it won't be that difficult for Min Hyeok.
Seeing that he can't let go of what he has in his hand,
because that means he's still able to hold out.
Unni, sit down.
Unni, it's now fall.
Your skin can get cracked easily.
You have to think of your age.
You're at the age where it is essential to take care.
Look at that, your lips are all chapped.
You don't have the right attitude for dating.
Unni... this
is as expensive as one month's worth of this place!
I'll give it to you.
Unni, you can't forget how well I treat you!
Hey! If you are able to put that on your face,
pay your monthly rent on time!
Unni, by the way, how far have you gone with the President?
Ha- have you gone as far as the lips?
Hey~ Hye Ri!
It seems I'm right!
I'll be back soon.
Aigoo. Bravo.
Rent?
♫ 3,4 Happy Birthday
♫ That song is too common so it's not for your birthday~
♫ So we would like to congratulate you with a new birthday song~
♫ Today is a joyful day. Today is a good day.
The world is beautiful.
♫ Everyone get together with a happy mind
and celebrate...
♫ Happy birthday...
♫ We congratulate you~
Boss.
What?
Happy birthday to you.
What about my present?
I'm sorry.
♫ Happy birthday~
Tell Kang Yoo Jeong to come here.
♫ We congratulate you~
It's what you selected.
You explain, too.
Yes?
Have you completed the sauce you were making?
Yes.
We're going to meet the investor tomorrow.
We have to increase the value of the restaurant
as high as possible.
Explain your recipe, and work on the plan again.
Boss,
That's not what I can do...
How are you going to get revenge working in a kitchen?
Don't kid yourself thinking I'll help you without reason.
Ahn Do Hoon,
he is fretting because he can't prey on this restaurant.
You just have to stop that.
And I have to get back what is mine.
Then we both win. Okay?
What is it?
I got a call from the security office.
They said the restoration has been completed.
What happened?
You're here?
I didn't know that the busy Ahn Do Hoon would get here so quickly.
Anyway, I was just getting ready
to watch something interesting.
Let's watch it together.
Gwang Soo, start it.
I only now remembered that Gwang Soo went to that cafe that night.
In order to show this to me,
did you called me?
Why?
Since you've seen it already,
there is nothing new?
Yes.
I was with Yoo Jeong that night.
So?
I can see what you're going after, but
the location captured on screen
is not the scene of the accident.
This can't become any evidence at all.
Then.
For something that can't be any evidence at all,
why would you so desperately find it, and
even erase it?
Why did you do it?
RET
SECRET
It's that son of a bitch.
The one who drove is also that son of a bitch!
Kang Yoo Jeong, you the woman just...
Just as what Ahn Do Hoon said,
the blackbox by itself can't be an evidence.
If it can't be, make one!
Let's go to the Prosecutions Office.
Order one steak and one pasta.
Your order is here.
Thank you.
Enjoy.
Let's talk for a bit.
What did you get scared of,
that you ran all the way here?
Did you tell him?
Did you tell Jo Min Hyeok that I drove?
Don't treat me like a worthless person.
The one who made me worthless is you.
Shackled by your great sacrifice,
the one who is struggling is me!
I'm on company time.
If you have something to say,
wait until I get off work.
The prosecutor and the suspect were having a relationship...
and that Prosecutor was Ahn Do Hoon?
So?
Is that all?
Shouldn't there be another trial?
When there is a concern that a decision can be made
unjustly, because of the personal relationships,
he can be excluded at the trial stage.
But, Attorney Ahn gave a proper sentencing.
There won't be any problems legally.
It's possible for the suspect
to file a motion for unfairness, but
that's not the case here.
If the suspect is not the culprit,
can you appeal for a retrial?
What are you talking about?
A retrial is something that will shake up
the entire prosecution organization.
Without concrete evidence, it won't be accepted.
Why, is there an evidence?
If there is,
will you take the case, Hyung?
Who exactly is the culprit..
By any chance,
are you saying it's Attorney Ahn?
Do you have any other evidence?
So you can use it at a time like this,
have you hidden something?
I guess you're right.
Seeing you now, Oppa,
it would have been good if I had done that.
Anyway, with that,
you won't be able to implicate me.
I'm not enough of a coward to implicate you for that.
Don't lower me to your level.
Why?
Are you scared because you have too much to lose?
That position you're in now,
hold on to it.
Until I drag you down with my hands,
make sure to hold out.
What's the matter?
Are you alright?
Yes.
Please go carefully.
This is a place of work Kang Yoo Jeong.
Quit if you're going to go meet men during working hours.
Don't do as you please thinking that the President has got your back.
I'm sorry.
This kind of thing will not happen again.
Who did you meet?
Attorney Ahn
came to see me.
What for?
It was a personal matter.
Please don't misunderstand.
There is no other meaning...
I won't misunderstand... if you tell me not to.
That day, if you had not driven,
actually, if it was Ahn Do Hoon who drove,
then, you wouldn't have written me off like this.
No.
If...
Even if I had not driven,
I was at that place.
The night when that person passed away,
I was clearly at that place.
The anger you feel toward me,
it's a matter of fact.
What you tell me to do is not hard.
Just that,
I forget everything, and
what if I go on living with smiles,
I'm more fearful of that.
The customer you are calling is unavailable...
Schedule another date.
At that time,
confirm Min Hyeok is here and after that,
call me.
Again, not like the practice, but a real thing.
Begin.
I said start.
♫ Today is a happy day. Today is a good day.
The world is beautiful.
Again, again, again.
You're going to do it absentmindedly to the customers too?
With all sincerity while smiling.
Do a little dance too. I saw you doing it well earlier.
Look straight at me.
♫ Today is a happy day. Today is a good day.
Now you try it.
I said do it.
What are you doing?
♫ Today is a happy day. Today is a good day.
♫ The world is beautiful. - Louder.
♫ Everyone is gathered together with cheerful hearts
♫ Boss's birthday~
♫ Congratulations to you~
♫ Con..grat..ulate
Is this how you play?
It was so childish that I didn't want to cut in.
But I should still mind my manners.
Happy birthday.
Ah. right.
Sorry about the studio. Because I had work.
Work?
This kind of work.
It suits your level perfectly.
Is it the Boss's birthday?
Yes.
What?
It's right, today is my birthday.
Why didn't you ask her about the accident?
Hearing from Kang Yoo Jeong...
Wouldn't it be the most accurate answer?
Because she will not answer,
that Kang Yoo Jeong.
The most solid evidence is
from Ahn Do Hoon's mouth,
it would be listening directly from him.
What is more important than the board of directors' decision
is the decision of the Madam Min Hyeok will be meeting tomorrow.
The reason why Jo Min Hyeok changed tomorrow's schedule
is because of that person?
If that investment confirms,
rather than the sales that come with
complicated procedures and full of rumors, the board
will hold up Min Hyeok's hand.
It's not a small amount of money.
Since she is not someone who moves small money,
Min Hyeok is personally going to see her.
All external contracts
cannot be acknowledged unless the Legal Team agrees.
The review of the investment contract,
I will personally confirm it.
Kang Yoo Jeong will be accompanying Min Hyeok tomorrow.
Do Hoon, what you're capable of,
I'll have high expectations for once.
If...
Even if I had not driven,
I was still at that place.
Crazy mother.
If Kang Yoo Jeong didn't drive,
what would he have done...
It's not my style to extend my hands to people and kneel.
I've never done it before.
So, you do a good job.
Oh, please come in.
You're here.
Thankfully, the legal team came first, and
I was briefed well on investment conditions.
Yes.
Please, sit.
This is the planning document.
You've got a great talent.
From Attorney Ahn, about the present situation,
I heard some unbiased helpful words.
Madam, you're investing quite a lot in the K-Group.
After we reveal the information we have,
is when you should make your choice,
was what I was thinking.
King's Restaurant,
what is the reason I should invest in it?
Just by looking at your face, President Jo,
I cannot offer this money, can I?
Can I use your kitchen for a moment?
Yes, you can.
I didn't prepare the main ingredient on purpose.
Our sauce at the King's Restaurant,
because of our pride that it goes well with any ingredient.
My father...
ran an old bakery in town.
Because I liked sweet things too much,
he made vegetable bread.
The vegetables I hated so much,
he made them with the sauce I really liked.
He has passed away now
but that taste remains with me as a good memory.
If you hear our brand King's Restaurant,
The distinct taste that people will remember is our value.
This isn't your personal business, Kang Yoo Jeong.
Please sell your memory somewhere else.
I am not here to sell a memory.
The sauce that we make...
We're confident that we'll be able to
capture the customers' taste buds.
We need assuredness, not confidence.
As the major shareholder of King's,
the position of K-Hotel is...
The president of the restaurant is me.
Aren't you here as an advisor for this investment contract,
Attorney Ahn?
What I represent is
not the restaurant, but K-Group.
It has good enough palate.
It appears you can't trust each other
amongst the K-Group family,
but to ask me to provide the funds?
Doesn't that seem a little far fetched?
I guess the rumor of Chairman being gravely ill is true.
Seeing how they sent out an incongruous team.
Shinha Hotel people are here.
I'm scheduled for another appointment.
I will contact you upon review.
Attorney Ahn.
If you break the rules like that,
it makes me feel really bad.
I acted according to the Board of Directors' opinion.
I'm sorry if it made you feel bad.
Is that right?
Keep holding out like that,
until I go back up again.
Let's go.
Thank you
for making me feel disappointed in you,
more and more.
I'm sorry.
Don't say sorry.
But, because of me.
It's not your fault.
Nothing has been decided yet.
Still...
Please!
Don't you know how to blame it on someone else?
It's the easiest way.
Just think of it like it was Ahn Do Hoon's fault,
if anything goes wrong.
What is this?
It was your birthday.
It's Cream Bread.
We don't have an oven, so I baked it in the rice cooker.
The shape might not be appealing,
but it's delicious.
I don't like sweet things.
Oh.
Then, would you like to have a meal before you go?
Drive safely.
I'll accept it since you gave it to me.
Omo, unbelievable President. It's been a long time.
You became even brighter! But behind you is...?
1+1?
Unni, is today some special occasion?
I started a new business.
It's magic. Herb oil.
If you have a few drops of this,
then your immunity level improves, your blood circulates well, and it is the best for your stamina.
Unni, Unni! If you sell that thing worth less than $1 for $20,
you're going back to jail!
Omo, omo. If you take this, the this potbelly filled with
grease (fat) will get completely flat!
Would you like to become a partner in this miraculous business?
Unni, it's Boss's birthday, so I was going to ask him
to have a meal with us.
President's birthday?
Really? Then, we have to honor him.
♫ Happy birthday to you, happy birthday to you
♫ Dear President, Happy birthday to you!
- Come on! Come and join in on this meal all friendly like.
- Gwang Soo, you!
Please sit.
Gwang Soo, let's eat together.
You always stand like that, so hurry up and come.
That's right, let's eat. Eat.
New face, one plus one.
♫ What is your name? What's your phone number?
I'm Choi Gwang Soo.
Choi Gwang Soo, you have a nice name. Have some.
Drink first. Drink first.
Have a drink, have a drink!
It's alright, I'll call a substitute driver. Have some.
You won't be able to sleep at night and you know what
would be palpitating (herb oil's good for stamina she said!).
Gwang Soo...
Sing! Sing! Sing!
♫ If you can't sing, you can't get married~ ♫ Ah, the person we hate~
♫ If it [song] doesn't come out then we'll go in for invasion,
♫ Bam-ba-da-bam-bam!
♫ 1 beat, rest and go, 2 beats, rest and go,
♫ 3 beats, rest and go,♫ 1, 2, 3, 4!
Ah, until when do you--
♫ My love that looks towards you,
♫ is absolute, absolute it is.
♫ My love that looks towards you, is express speed love.
♫ I love one person
♫ I That person is you
♫ Even though I cannot say
♫ Love or farewell
♫ In the world where there is none
♫ I want to meet once again
♫ My love
[Ahjumma (Hong In Joo)]
It's me.
Did father
go into surgery?
If you don't have an appointment, you can't see her.
Then this. Please at least pass this.
I made it last week so it's perfect to eat this week, you know?
Please do me this favor.
President, I have found Lee Hae Jin.
Who?
Kang Yoo Jeong's cellmate from jail.
Why did she report Kang Yoo Jeong?
After she reported, thanks to the recommendation
Ahn Do Hoon wrote, while he was a prosecutor,
she was transferred to a vocational training center.
What?
Recommendation
(Vocational Center Recommendation)
Seoul Central District Prosecutor Office
Posted by Prosecutor: Ahn Do Hoon
This is the screen shot of parking lot CCTV
that Ms. Lee Ja Yeong requested.
Please, save me just this once!
I cannot send my father off like this.
They said they found my dad.
- Where?
In Pohang.
Dad! Dad Dad!
I would like to be by your side.
Is it because of Ahn Do Hoon?
Ahn Do Hoon!
It was Hannam-dong madam.
She said Min Hyeok came by again.
She is also curious
as to what kind of person Kang Yoo Jeong is...
That woman must have done well.
She didn't seem like a person
who would move big money on shallow emotion.
I can't know that.
She is not curious about you, Do Hoon.
Would you like to take one?
Are you really going to do it?
Why? Are you going to cling on to me or something?
What kind of relationship are we in?
Can you say you have a
deeper relationship with Jo Min Hyeok?
Do you want to have me?
Then, that woman, get her off Min Hyeok.
Can you do that?
If I do that, can you come to me?
What should I do?
I do have to marry.
Would you be satisfied,
even if you were my second?
Us two... Don't we really seem like fools?
Put your guard down.
I didn't call you for work.
If it wasn't for work, I wouldn't have come all the way here.
I'm behind on contracts I need to confirm.
I'll make it short, then.
Lee Hae Jin.
Kang Yoo Jeong's fellow inmate,
who reported her for child abuse, right?
Why did you write the recommendation for her?
It is something that has nothing to do with you.
It has nothing to do with me.
It's Kang Yoo Jeong that's the problem.
For someone whose first reaction is to close her mouth,
as soon as you are mentioned,
why did she turn around like that?
That's what I'm so intrigued about.
There is no secret in the world, right?
Just what is it that you want to say?
The prosecutor who was screaming
for the justice of an era,
behind the scenes, secured his child... Wow.
Attorney Ahn, you and I...
What I said that we're not different,
I would like to take that back.
Because I don't think I can become
such an insidious character.
Did Kang Yoo Jeong turn around knowing this, or
did you pull some other crap that is huge?
Wasn't the parole
a plan that you came up with, Jo Min Hyeok?
You should say what is right.
It was you who made the choice, Attorney Ahn.
Jo Min Hyeok!
The person who put the red flag on the parole document
is not me, but yourself.
For me it was simply,
for the sentencing you gave,
I wanted Kang Yoo Jeong to serve out the term
in the correctional facility. Of course,
I absolutely regret that now, but...
Regarding the red flag on Kang Yoo Jeong's parole,
before the evaluation result even came out,
it had gotten disapproval
due to insufficient qualifications.
So, is it because putting the red flag
on the parole evaluation bothered you, that you did such a thing?
So as not to let your fault surface,
you used a hired hand
to make the parole itself negated?
Take him away.
San... Not now.
San, San, San, San!
San. Let go, let go.
That's a little cowardly.
Isn't Kang Yoo Jeong too pitiful?
What are you so righteous about?
Not having been able to protect our women,
is the same for both of us.
Ji Hee!
That's right...
You have to come on strong like that.
That has to be... so that the secrets you have,
it will be fun peeling them off one by one.
Matters regarding Kang Yoo Jeong's father,
I'll think about that slowly.
What's going on? You didn't even call.
Officetels or places like that are nice,
although they are claustrophobic, right?
Aigoo, but, your face doesn't look so good.
Is something wrong?
No...
Where's mother?
She said she had an appointment in the daytime
and left the store today. She's not back yet.
Don't worry about the house.
I barely settled your mother down about moving.
She was making such a fuss.
It's empty here too, now that you're gone.
What's the point of moving to a bigger one?
It's old and the hill is steep
so it's difficult for you, father.
Just move to a comfortable area.
No,
I don't want to ask anyone a favor.
It's enough to be called boss at my own store.
What more can I ask for?
Why?
Father.
I'm living a good life, right?
Why is the front door opened?!
Hon-
Oh you scared me!
Why are you surprised seeing your own son?!
- Hey...!
Hey... hey... hey...
No that's not it,
You should have called us before you came!
Then what about you...
How come you're so late without telling me where you were!
I mean...
Over there...
I'm going to go change.
What's wrong with her?
Did you eat?
Is there something in the storage?
What's wrong with you today?
So strange.
Hello! We're from King's Restaurant!
You came!
I'm the one who called.
Since I didn't host Min Hyeok's birthday party,
I thought better late than not.
I see.
Please start setting on the table over there.
And prepare the food over there.
One person should suffice, so you all can go.
Is that okay?
Pardon?
Yes.
Min Hyeok.
Min Hyeok?
Yeah?
The Chairman moved to the recovery room yesterday.
Post op progress?
We have to wait and see, but he'll recover.
Before he returns, he'll be attending a meeting in Berlin.
It'll be a good opportunity
to show the public that he is healthy.
I heard about the investment.
You did well.
She was asking about the employee who accompanied you,
is it the woman, you said before,
who worried you?
I will take care of my own business.
I don't want to meddle with your personal life, either.
Should your marriage with Shin Se Yeon go wrong,
what'll happen,
you should know better than anyone.
Attorney Ahn's file...
Why haven't I seen it yet?
The incidents you incurred,
he did a good job cleaning them up, and
Except for running around due to the board's decision,
like the Chairman said, he is an elite K-Group needs.
We should use him as long as he is useful,
the impediment
is Se Yeon.
Attorney Ahn and Se Yeon,
it'll be good to keep an eye on them.
Min Hyeok-ssi is quite late, isn't he?
Min Hyeok-ssi! Happy Birthday!
What is this... We didn't know
you would settle down with one woman.
As expected, Shi Se Yeon must be exceptional.
Happy Birthday Min Hyeok-ssi
I didn't even get to congratulate you
on your birthday.
Want to have a glass?
Please bring some wine here.
Why are you here?
What's all this?
What are you trying to do?
I told you.
Congratulate you on your birthday,
congratulate you on getting the investment as well.
Our marriage also,
congratulate in advance.
- Shin Se Yeon!
We're in front of my friends.
Please mind your manners.
Please clean this up, here.
One moment please.
Could you bring us some coffee here?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Yes?
You've worked hard.
The diligence that you sent from the morning,
The Hannam-dong granny,
I think she changed her mind.
Really?
What a relief! Really, what a relief.
What is it?
Is the coffee far from being done?
Yes, it's done.
Move.
I'll clean it up.
- I said go.
Go, because it's hot.
Since I've sent away my friends,
we four should cozily have a drink.
We four?
Bring the desserts please.
Didn't you enjoy this kind of thing?
Everyone knows, but pretending not to.
Se Yeon...
How about you, Yoo Jeong?
The man you've dated in the past,
the man who tortures you in the worst way.
Who are you more uncomfortable with?
You don't need to answer.
She shouldn't have any feelings for me.
"Let's not feel sorry for each other anymore.",
she told me on the day she gave me the ultimatum.
Why? Do you have something to say?
I'm sorry...
But,
you two look vulnerable.
You two look suitable to each other.
Since I don't seem to be needed anymore,
I'll get going.
Rest of the kitchenware, I'll come back tomorrow for them.
How was it? Didn't you like this kind of thing?
It's my present. Did you like it?
Is it fun?
Setting up something like this for fun,
wasn't it a hobby of yours, Jo Min Hyeok?
I must have told you not to cut in,
when I'm talking to Se Yeon.
The present I prepared for you,
I should be able to send it to you soon.
Attorney Ahn, you know something?
There is no one who is really strong,
who pretends to be strong.
Attorney Ahn,
you look very much susceptible to danger now.
For your congratulations,
thank you.
Get in.
I'll take the bus.
Get in!
You said you'd do what I tell you,
get in.
I know Min Hyeok.
I've watched him since kindergarten.
If only Seo Ji Hee died,
I thought I could have him, but...
The way Min Hyeok looks at that woman,
it's love.
Thank you for giving me a ride, boss.
♫ A person came into my life
♫ The person I should not love
♫ No I should not, no I should not
♫ I tried to turn away many times
♫ I made that person cry
Because of my incredibly bad obsession
♫ If the tears steal the heart and disappear
♫ Because I thought she would come closer
♫ I believe that I love you
It's shaking me like crazy
If this limping love of mine
♫ If it moves near, because you might hide from fear
♫ Even though I say I'm hurt as if I could die
I only watch
♫ I believe that I love you
It's shaking me like crazy
If this limping love of mine
♫ If it moves near, because you might hide from fear
♫ Even though I say I'm hurt as if I could die
I only watch
♫ If the tears knew my heart