Secret
What is this?
Just what are you?
Owner of this building.
Such an evil karma, isn't it.
I never sold this place.
Get out of our house immediately.
I don't want to be here either.
I'll let you slide up until this week,
so know when to get out.
Or, I'm forcing you out.
On who's account?
This is my house where I lived my whole life.
You have no right.
Just why do you keep following me and torment me?
Who are you? Why are you doing this?
How degenerate do you have to be,
to do something like this to a human being?
How can a human being
do this to another human being?
What you did... Was that something
that can be done to a human being?
How did it feel to abandon and leave
a dying person on the street?
This lousy building? This is nothing.
Compared to what you took away from me!
You only have this week.
It'll be best if I never see you again.
Are you done crying?
Did you come to watch, or to sympathize?
Both.
If we had heard the song until the end,
it would have been better.
There's this saying...
Because of the person who wouldn't cry for you...
Don't cry.
Wipe your tears.
And...
Because of the person who would cry for you, Se Yeon... Cry.
What should I do with the building?
Should I take care of it?
Don't touch it. Just leave it.
Now, following around Kang Yoo Jeong, too... Stop that.
Yes.
It's annoying.
Substitute, was it you?
You can't hit a person... and just leave.
The likes of your kind
dare touch something of mine?
For something like this... Don't act all so scared!
Why are you doing this?
Following me all the way here! . .
Why are you doing this to me?
Stay comfortably while you're inside.
Because when you come out,
it will become very uncomfortable.
Yoo Jeong.
Oppa.
What happened?
No. It's nothing.
Look at me. Did you get hurt?
I think I have to move out of the house.
The building owner came by.
He told me to move out this week.
If he tells you to move out suddenly like this...
I'll talk to him.
No.
I'll take care of it. Don't worry about it.
Still...
He is a difficult person to talk to.
Let me talk to someone like that.
Please let me do that.
It is true that I am in debt.
What are you doing here?
I don't know... what I'm doing here, either.
Aren't you going home?
Go home for what? There's nothing there to do.
Did something happen?
Something?
It's because of you going up on stage, right?
You've had stage fright since you were little.
Mighty Shin Se Yeon, who was she trying to lobby...
that she even thought of singing on stage?
Jo Min Hyeok.
I didn't go up there for others.
It was you whom I sang for.
What you wanted to give to me,
was this it?
You already have everything so I didn't have anything to give you.
I at least wanted to sing for you.
Then, you should have told me in advance.
It was wrong timing...
I want to leave. I'm tired.
Se Yeon.
Then, can't you sing now?
Ultimately, I'm the only one who has to hear.
Jo Min Hyeok. You...
Could you shed tears for me?
I'm saying, could you cry for me?
Why are you like this?
Unlike Shin Se Yeon, suddenly.
I want to stop now.
What?
This marriage...
I'm not going to do it.
RET
SECRET
How did it feel to abandon and leave
a dying person on the street?
This lousy building? This is nothing.
Compared to what you took away from me!
Dad.
We have to go.
Should we go traveling?
Mountain or ocean, should we go see them?
Ocean?
Mm.
Let's go traveling.
Right, ocean.
Let's go.
Can you take this off of me? It's itchy.
No. You have to keep it on.
Take it off!
Dad! Dad!
Dad!
Forty five...
forty six...
forty seven.
When I was your age, I couldn't pinch my stomach.
I was tight.
Mom!
Do five more.
Having inborn capabilities do not matter.
Whether you manage it or not,
that's what determines the victory or defeat.
If I took after you, I wouldn't have to work hard like this...
why did I take after dad?
You're right.
It would have been so great. Mm?
Now that I've had a chance to look, Mom,
I don't think we have anything resembling.
We have different tastes in food,
different body types, too.
My friends also say the same thing.
That we don't look alike at all.
Mom, by any chance...
Yes?
Tell me the truth. I'm a not a kid anymore.
What?
Mom, which parts did you fix?
This kid! This is not a fixed face.
Not a lot anyway...
Come on, which part did you fix?
Tell me.
Okay. Okay. It's the eyes.
I don't think so.
Se Yeon, that day...
Please come in.
What is this? You said you didn't want to get married.
This is not marriage.
It's business.
That's a down payment. This is a contract.
I already signed it.
This is the Lucida diamond ring, cut in the year 99.
Princess cutting that emphasizes the brightness...
I don't know much about that.
Which is the most expensive one here?
You want that one?
That's it?
Why? It looks big enough.
If it's big, the biggest one in the world.
If it's expensive, the most expensive one.
Or... Choose a ring that you really want to give me.
What you want to give me... Do you have none?
Hey, the ring is...
Please wrap that one for us.
Because the down payment, the more the better.
I think you might even ask for a breach of contract fee.
Of course.
It's all written here. Read it well.
What responsibility the party that reneges first will bear.
If I give you the down payment, what are you going to give me in return?
Just by me standing beside you, your worth will go up.
Hey, Shin Se Yeon, you...
The ring. I'll accept it.
Of course the apple won't fall far from the tree!
That family is second to none
when it comes to managing their profit.
You know Se Yeon isn't like that.
What you mean she isn't like that?
From grade school, Se Yeon is my childhood friend.
A friend?
You... Don't say things like that casually.
You have to fall in the water together
to know who your real friends are.
Review (the contract) and send it back after revising
the part that is unfavorable to us.
Yes.
Kang Yoo Jeong. Did she leave?
She has to get out by this week.
Last time, you told me not to follow her anymore.
Hey!
Even if you don't follow her, you're supposed to know where she is!
I'm sorry.
I don't want to eat anymore.
Even so, how dare you come here?
Even if Do Hoon says to come here,
you barge in here with your sick dad as an excuse?
- Mother-in-law.
- Hey, hey.
If other people hear you they're going to misunderstand.
Why am I your mother. We're strangers now.
I'm sorry, Mo...
I also know I shouldn't be visiting like this, but
my dad can't sleep well in strange places.
- Dad!
- Omo!
Shoes.
That's why you should have been preparing already...
How many times have do I have to tell you...
You need to get your head straight! Haven't I told you that?
We only have 2 rooms. Where will we have him sleep?
Do Hoon said he'd be late.
Have your dad go into Do Hoon's room.
Thank you so much, Father-in-law.
Father-in-law my butt.
Thank you.
Dad, it's alright.
Hard and complicated things... I will take care of it all.
You're leaving?
Yes, Sunbaenim.
I've clearly given you the advice.
Yes?
I have no personal feelings about this,
so don't blame me.
This is an organization. And I'm a member of that organization.
I'll see you next week at the Supreme Court.
Supreme Prosecutors Office
Court Summons for Prosecutor Ahn Do Hoon
This is a favor I got by agreeing to share a meal with the manager here,
so you have to do well.
Thank you, Hye Ri.
Kwang Soo, it came off.
Yes.
Let's go.
Our President is so young.
Isn't he daebak?
What's wrong?
Why?
Come here quickly!
There's an empty spot here.
This is where you'll do your work.
Why did you do that?
Unni stop it! That's enough!
Let go!
I've got this!
Sorry.
I don't think I'm suitable to work here.
I'm sorry Hye Ri. You helped me so much.
2nd Floor.
I've told you not to appear in front of me again...
Now you've entered my boundary?
Yes, ahjumoni.
Again?
No, I'll be there right away.
Sorry.
Why is she going up?
She's coming. She's coming.
Should I follow her?
No. That's fine.
I'm tired from attending an early meeting.
Let's go.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry, Ahjumma.
I'm sorry.
Dad. Why did you come here again?
Yoo Jeong, open the door. It's locked.
This is not our home anymore. Let's go home.
Open the door.
Next time,
let's come back here again, okay?
Your mother didn't like sweets at first.
She became this way because
she kept eating the bread I baked again and again.
She really liked creme filled pastry.
Dad!
Dad! Dad!
Can you see that his vessels have swollen?
It's urgent that we conduct the operation that pinches
the cerebral artery right here.
Ah, we've made provisions by administering drugs, but
just think of it as a time bomb residing inside his head.
If he has the surgery he'll be okay, right?
Post surgery, we have to keep watching to see.
Please let him have the surgery.
Doctor.
Please save my dad.
Let's go home!! I'm not taking it off!
If my dad continues to be stubborn, he's going to pass out again.
Dad, let's take this off just once.
No way! Go away!!
Dad, take it off!
If you don't put this on, I'm going to
send you back to the nursing home!
Wear this.
Wear. Hand!
Whoa... Take this as a collateral.
Keep it safe. I'll be coming to take it back.
I'm a Special Prosecutor Park Hyeon Seok.
Assemblyman Kim Chang Seok stated a suspicion
that the Prosecutions Office had conducted entrapment.
At this office, regarding this statement,
we're going to investigate to determine the truth.
You have submitted your motive of investigation,
have you not?
Yes.
Prosecutor Ahn Do Hoon.
Can you spare a moment of your time?
This will become your spot.
This is Assemblyman Kim's overseas account information.
What is the reason you're handing this over?
Why don't you come work at the K-Group headquarters?
And think of this (information) as kind of a
contractual deposit.
Do I look easy to you?
You don't seem easy, but
desperate.
Put cuffs on Assemblyman Kim once again and
just take off your suit refreshingly! (quit your job)
Dad!
Doctor!
- My head! Ouch!
- Someone hold him!
Please stop moving.
Hold him please.
Open your eyes!
Please move aside, guardian.
Man, when do we finish all these? We're going to work
through the night again.
Team Leader Kim.
If you give me the account's receipts and
communication records...
The boss told us not to give you anything while
you're being investigated.
He said not to give you any work.
It's a face that says that something's not going well.
What brings you here?
I used it well.
Did you come here to give back a handkerchief?
If I said that I was here to return your handkerchief,
that would seem like an excuse. .
I don't know why I came here.
I just wanted to drink alcohol and insult people.
Suddenly I thought of you.
I'm not a person with that much free time.
Each day I have thousands of cases to go through, and...
Mr. Prosecutor!
The boss told you to go home since you don't have anything to do.
How much can you give me for it?
How much did you pay for it?
It was a gift.
The craftsmanship is really well done and the
condition isn't bad...
Please give me as much as you possibly can.
Later, I'll definitely come back to retrieve it.
Please just book the surgery date.
I will pay the rest later.
Ms. Kang Yoo Jeong!
Yes?
What is it?
Let go of me, please.
Why are you doing this?
The ring I had made to give to my daughter-in-law,
is in your hands? Why is that?
Do you have any idea how much this is?
You hand over a $150K ring at $4K?
Why didn't you just wear it yourself?
You can't sell it anywhere, as it has a unique product identifier.
Have you never thought to find the owner, given its value?
I'm sorry.
I asked to see you because I thought maybe my son found another woman.
But I don't think that's the case.
Notify the police and hand her over.
That ring... I'm the one who gave it to her.
Let's go.
Get up.
I told you it would be wise not to appear in front of me again.
How low are you to sell another person's belonging?
I... will make sure to pay you back.
Easier said than done.
My dad is sick and I needed money for his surgery.
I knew it was wrong, but
I must have lost my mind for a moment.
Your old father?
Must be nice to have many excusable things.
Sorry! I'm really sorry.
Don't say sorry.
I don't need an apology that you wear on your mouth.
Feel the pain as much as me.
Try losing the most precious people,
without having a chance to do anything.
How pathetically painful that is,
shouldn't you feel it too? Huh?
Get out. See you at the police station.
Get out!
I'm sorry.
Hey!
Please save me just once!
I can't let my dad go like this.
Put me in the police station.
I'll go to jail. I'll take punishment.
My dad getting the surgery and smiling,
please let me go after I see just that,
I'm begging you!
This time...
If you just let me watch my dad by his side...
Hey! Get off of me!
Aren't you even embarrassed?
No, I'm not embarrassed.
I can do even worse things.
What I'm embarrassed of...
is what I had done
to that person who passed away.
I don't think I've paid off my sins.
For my whole life...
For my whole life, I will never forget it.
How can I forget?
Don't speak of it carelessly.
I said don't speak of it carelessly.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
So what do you want to do?
If I give you the chance to save your father,
what will you do for me?
As you can see, I have a lot of money.
That surgery fee, I can lend it to you too.
Se Yeon.
What are you doing here?
What do you mean?
I wanted to insult someone while drinking alcohol.
Who is this?
Someone that came to see me.
Say hi to her. My friend Shin Se Yeon.
And there... Prosecutor Ahn Do Hoon.
If you're going to drink, do you want to do it together?
We were going to drink anyways.
Okay then.
Where should we go?
And we have someone precious, too.
Oh right...
I'll deposit the money into your account tomorrow.
Okay. Thank you.
I'll go now.
Don't go.
I told you not to go.
I even did what you were asking.
Se Yeon, I feel today...
Are you trying to run away?
Were you originally weak on alcohol?
Still, you shouldn't run away.
As a man.
I know this is awkward since it was so sudden.
But,
have we met before?
No.
Prosecutor Ahn, I'm hurt.
You've always refused, when I asked you to drink.
What do you do?
Min Hyeok...
How do you know him?
Personal friendship.
What I ask her to do... This and that,
she takes care of them.
Do Hoon.
Are you tense because a woman is next to you?
Why aren't you saying anything?
I feel uncomfortable, since this was unexpected.
We should quickly introduce Prosecutor Ahn to some ladies.
I heard there is a problem
when someone doesn't date for too long.
How do you feel about Prosecutor Ahn?
He's still single, isn't he handsome?
Jo Min Hyeok!
I have... a boyfriend.
Is that so?
What does your boyfriend do?
Just...
He is a person who is doing great work.
Great work?
I need to go to the bathroom.
Have you known Min Hyeok for a long time?
Min Hyeok and I are expected to get married...
did you know?
No. Please don't misunderstand.
The boss...
he is just a good person that is lending me money for my dad's surgery.
That's it.
This isn't my place to come.
That this isn't your place to come...
as long as you know it.
I'll leave first.
What are you doing?
I'm not doing anything.
That woman came to me on her own, and...
said she needed money for her father's surgery,
so what can I do?
Letting aside any hate,
I have to save who needs to be saved.
Because unlike someone,
I don't turn against a human life.
Kang Yoo Jeong, isn't she really thick-skinned?
She recognized you, right?
The prosecutor who convicted her is right next to her,
but she didn't even flinch.
Using money to capture the woman
who is done paying for her sins,
Isn't that too low?
I didn't know you would
support Kang Yoo Jeong this much.
Kang Yoo Jeong...
is no longer a defendant.
She's simply a normal woman
who has gone through the legal system.
What are you talking about?
It's uncomfortable to stay here any longer.
With money...
and power, you think you can move people.
This kind of ties, it's repulsive.
That woman, is she the one that killed Seo Ji Hee?
I'm sorry.
The truth is...
Jo Min Hyeok!
You're not really hurt.
You're just whining to let people see you're hurting.
If you keep being like this...
I can't marry you.
If you think this marriage is a business,
you should at least keep the minimum courtesy
for your partner.
Do you know where Kang Woo Cheol is?
I haven't seen him.
What have you been running around doing?
Did you go see that man because you need money?
Do you know who he is...?
- Oppa!
I can't find Dad. He's not at the hospital.
He's not at the bakery either,
even though he always goes there.
What are you saying?
- Dad isn't here!
Maybe he went to Mom's grave?
He goes there often. I need to go there!
Let go of this.
Yoo Jeong.
- He is not here!
I'll look for him, so calm down!
How can I calm down when my Dad's not here?
I already got his surgery date! I need to find him!
For now, go to the police station
and report missing person first.
I'll look for him.
Ahjussi.
Please find my Dad.
Because he needs to get a surgery right now,
we need to find him quickly.
Please calm down and
fill the missing person's form out.
Father.
I can't quite figure out which way is home.
Lets go to Yoo Kyeong and Yoo Jeong.
Yes, Yoo Jeong is waiting for you.
Get in quickly.
It's a relief.
Be careful driving.
Yes, Father-in-law.
You're just talk.
Last time you cracked open Yoo Jeong's forehead.
Even then I was...
worried because it was raining so hard.
When I saw Yoo Jeong dreaming about fixing her car...
The car was so damaged...
I had thought it was a relief that
only her forehead was cracked open.
That...
do you remember that?
Why would I not remember?
You were the one driving,
but you put the blame on my Yoo Jeong.
Do you think I don't know that?
If you do that again this time,
I won't just let it go.
Okay, Son-in-law Han?
Seat belt.
Be careful.
Be careful driving.
Okay, that's enough for today.
Good job for today.
Let's see each other again at ten tomorrow,
Prosecutor Ahn Do Hoon.
Is it this kind of thing you meant
what you said about your belief?
In order to keep your belief in the organization,
that you have to know how to bend.
I didn't know it meant stepping over the Hoobae like this.
Rather, that I don't need the truth or the belief!
Getting ahead in life is all.
Why didn't you tell me that?
Prosecutor Ahn,
Having an illusion that you're the only person of justice,
isn't there a problem with that?
How you got the Assemblyman Kim's file,
there is something I heard about that.
Only for the truth and justice,
you had Assemblyman Kim apprehended?
That's not it.
Having a high profile crime figure under your belt,
you wanted to get ahead in your career...
Do you have enough confidence to deny it?
Please find my dad
Yes?
Yes, yes, a red jacket.
Yes, that's right.
Where are you?
Huh?
Po Hang?
Uhhh...
For overlooking the ring incident...
Thank you.
Even if it takes my whole life,
I'll pay you back somehow.
Because I have an urgent matter right now...
I'm sorry.
Please be nice...
They found my dad.
Where?
Po Hang.
Ahhh, so annoying.
Taxi!
You said Po Hang.
Dad!
Dad.
Dad. I'm sorry. What do I do, Dad?
Dad!
Dad. Dad! Dad...
Dad. Dad...
Please give us a word.
This investigation...
as a typical Prosecution's external-pressure Investigation,
that fact that it was an attempt to end my political life,
has been clearly revealed.
By shedding the misunderstanding thus far,
I'm planning on reinstating myself back to
to the folds of my political party.
Thank you for coming here as soon as you came out.
It's not like there was anyone waiting for me.
Funeral for Kang Woo Cheol.
Survived by daughter Kang Yoo Jeong.
Hey, hey, that's not needed.
Do I need to tell everybody I got out?
It's laughable. If you eat that (Tofu), do you become innocent?
Not bad.
There's someone who'd cry on your behalf and all.
Did you find a place to stay?
You crazy bitch.
Is this time for you to worry about me?
It'd be easy enough for me to get settled.
If it's that difficult, YOU can come and see ME, wench.
♫ Even though I reach out my hand
♫ There is no use
Why?
Is there someone you're waiting for?
♫ After the love ended
It really gets on my nerves.
You always smile like that
when you're having a hard time.
♫ Where you had stayed,
there were only tears
Grave of surname Kang, Woo Cheol &amp;
surname Kim Mi Yeong (mother).
♫ And they disappear away
♫ Although it hurts,
I live on without crying
♫ It's me who finally says I love you
♫ The words I didn't know back then
♫ The words I didn't want to hear
♫ Inside your flowing tears
♫ The fact I have lived there
♫ If I had also known it back then
Take this.
It's all that I have.
I feel I have to do at least this,
to feel more at ease.
I thought a lot
while staying at the funeral parlor alone.
"When will Oppa come?"
"Will he be here today?"
"Would he be here in the early morning?"
I waited and waited for you, but you wouldn't come.
But when I thought about it,
if you were to have come the first day,
I would have been so busy holding and leaning on to you,
that I would not have been able to send off my dad very well.
Yoo Jeong.
If you had come the second day,
I would have been so busy hating and blaming you
for coming late,
and not have been able to think of my dad much.
So, thank you.
Coming today (at the right time).
It's fine that I got to see your face like this.
I'm sorry.
Oppa,
let's just end... the things we're sorry for.
All the while, we've...
worked so hard.
Don't you think?
Yoo Jeong.
We were so worried per chance we'd cause each other pain,
so we just laughed things off.
This isn't right, you know.
If we meet like this,
you'd once again feel guilty.
And that guilt would cause you to want to do something for me.
And I would feel burdened and try to figure out how I should behave.
It'll be repetitious (vicious cycle).
But the thing I did (gone to jail for him),
I will never regret it.
Even if that situation arises again,
I will make the same decision.
So, stop feeling sorry.
What is there
that I could do for you?
Help me leave first.
The memory of someone's appearance from behind
is supposed to last for a very long time.
I think it'd be difficult
to see your appearance from the back.
I'm not confident.
My dad...
I never got to buy you a nice pair of shoes.
I shouldn't have made an excuse of being busy.
I should have gone together
when he asked to see foliage together.
I should have listen to his stories more.
I should have told him even more stories next to him.
The breads you baked for me
were really delicious.
They were the most delicious in the world.
I shouldn't have washed this coat.
So it'd smell of Dad more.
Daddy.
Dad,
be born as my child
in your next life.
I will be your dad.
So I can return all
that I have received from you.
What should I do, Dad?!
What do I do now?
Dad, what do I do?!
How about Kang Yoo Jeong?
I couldn't tell her whereabouts for several days now.
Find her.
Yes, sir.
Ah, never mind.
Finding a person is a piece of cake for you.
Substitute driver!
Hey, substitute driver!
Hey! Get a hold of yourself!
Get a hold of yourself!
Wake up!
Wake up!!
♫  Would it be okay if I were to follow. ♫
♫ I'm holding still for fear of it. ♫
♫ Should we really have met? ♫
Over here!
Over here!!
- A person is dying.
- Please come this way.
♫ The scar I can't erase has become pained. ♫
♫ Would I be able to say I love once again? ♫
♫ I abandon you over and again,
but still you're there again. ♫
♫ No matter how hard I try to erase you,
like an incurable disease ♫
♫ Spreading inside of me
I just can't stop this love ♫
♫ I walk on the same street as I did that day
In the lost memories, ♫
♫ to the door where I see you ♫
♫ If you are standing in the lost time ♫
♫ Please don't move, don't try to forget me ♫
♫ The stopped time is ticking away through you again ♫
Don't die.
Without my permission...
Absolutely, don't die.
♫ Will I be able to say I love you once again? ♫
♫ I throw you out and throw you out,
but in the end I'm filled up by you ♫