Secret
Gwang Soo?
Yes.
Everyone I love,
why do they all leave me like this?
To you, I'm
always a bad guy, right?
Ji Hee?
Don't forgive me.
What to do?
That woman,
I don't want to lose her.
♫ One day that one day
♫ Each of us, we saw for the first time today
♫ Suddenly I felt suffocated
♫ And my painful memories
♫ Have all disappeared
♫ I believe that I love you
♫ It's shaking me like crazy
♫ If this limping love of mine
♫ If it moves near, because you might hide from fear
♫ Even though I say I'm hurt as if I could die
♫ I only watch
♫ Even though now is not the time
♫ I can feel you as you tremble
What do I do?
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
The words that you're sorry,
don't ever say them again.
I won't let go of you.
Even if I let go of everything else,
Don't think about other things.
Just stay by my side, that's all.
♫ I only watch
♫ If the tears knew my heart
Secret
Episode 14
I have to go now.
I have someone I have to meet.
You just stay here, like this.
Don't go anywhere.
I'm not tell you, but I'm asking you.
Nice picture.
I'm...
too thick-skinned, right?
Would there be anything else that you have no control over,
besides a person liking another person?
Let's go in.
Min Hyeok!
Chairman is already stressed now.
If you too act like this...
I'll be stubborn for just once, Father.
I will not go through the marriage.
In this situation now, if you too act like this...
I know I've been given more than my share.
But until now,
not even once, have I ever had something I really wanted.
If you're not saying that you'll marry Se Yeon
and work hard for the company, get out!
What I want to protect is that woman!
If you want to talk about something like that,
I don't need to hear it anymore! Get out, boy!
The work that I've been in charge of till now,
I'll take care of it and leave.
Chairman!
Would you be alright to let Min Hyeok go like that?
Don't worry.
Min Hyeok will come back.
He's my child.
I know him better than anyone.
Min Hyeok, that kid. This time is different.
That woman, find out about her more thoroughly.
Yes.
SEOUL
06 TA 7183
What happened?
Like what Kang Yoo Jeong said, the fact that her car almost collided with a truck at the scene of the accident,
was true.
When he met with the police,
why did he say he pretended not to know?
What was that barrel also about?
Because the vehicle was carrying additional weight,
the driver said he didn't want to get involved
in a some problem.
The evidence?
That... The blackbox has never existed, and
because of the rain, he said he couldn't see
the driver of the other vehicle.
That truck driver,
has he ever talked to anyone about this incident?
Probably not.
He seemed to remember only after I had asked him.
Then, go see that driver again.
I said if there was no evidence, make one.
You remember that, right?
Even so...
There is one truth,
the one who drove was Ahn Do Hoon.
I don't know if I should be doing this...
Thank you.
Thank you, Unni!
Alright, take good care of your work, and
I'll be going.
On the day my dad disappeared, where did you go?
Get out.
When you were taking my dad, how was it?
"Where should I abandon him?".
Did you think something like that?
What would this be?
What are you trying to do?
What am I trying to do,
wouldn't you the Attorney know better?
Why?
When you took my dad and abandoned him,
did you not think about things like this?
You said I was grabbing your ankle?
No.
The actions you have taken
will be grabbing your ankle.
I'm just coming from meeting Chairman Jo.
It's the data about you. 2 pages in all.
They're not interested in how dramatically you have lived.
Your education, your estate, and your family relationships.
And, the record of your conviction.
With those things, their evaluation of you is complete.
Do you want to go steady with Jo Min Hyeok or something?
Don't concern yourself.
Ruining me wasn't enough,
you want to ruin Jo Min Hyeok, too?
Jo Min Hyeok who chose you
will get it all taken away with nothing left.
If you do that, I would be thankful, but.
Stop that!
Get a hold of yourself.
Do you know what your problem is?
Because of that damn love,
it's that you can't even take care of your own issues.
Current investigative data of Kang Yoo Jeong's Financials
Inmate personal data
This turned out well.
I've been wanting to see you.
The person who stands here with public recognition,
who do you think it'll be?
Rather than public recognition,
isn't the heart of the person you'll be with
more important?
I wonder what kind of confidence that is.
This marriage,
it's probably something that will make both of you unhappy.
This unhappiness,
don't you think you are the one causing it?
Stop using Min Hyeok.
You shouldn't mess with a man belonging to another,
in order to get back the man who left you.
You asked to break up with Do Hoon first, then
are you hanging around like this,
because you still have lingering feelings?
I don't regret breaking up with him.
That I didn't let him go earlier,
is all I regret.
Even while knowing that he didn't love me,
yet holding onto him stubbornly, is what I regret.
Holding onto a heart that has already left,
isn't love.
It's obsession.
Don't get cute.
Since I got hit, I'll say one more thing.
Your face with expectations of a marriage,
not even once looked happy,
never.
Did you wait for a long time?
It's what I'm good at.
Why did you wait, not knowing when I'd come?
You should have at least called.
Because I'm not following you around,
you feel a bit empty, right?
Did something happen today?
I couldn't contact you all day.
No.
Did something happen to you?
Yes.
But,
I can't think of anything now that I've seen you.
Why did you dress so light?
Because I wanted to walk a bit.
You're cold too.
I'm not cold.
I've worked at a ski resort for a long time, and
since I felt all the cold I could then,
now this much is fine.
Is there anything you haven't done?
I told you I don't drink sweet things.
If you drink it when it's cold, it's delicious.
The marriage...
I'm not going to do it.
Why no response?
This is entirely because of you, so you
can't run away.
♫ For me to have
Thank you...
And...
I'm sorry.
Why are you thankful?
It's me who should be thankful.
♫ Who is not suitable
♫ I love one person
♫ That person is you
Well...
Ah...
There's that...you know...
leaning on my shoulder...
♫ If I can, my love.
♫ Love or farewell.
♫ In the world where there is none.
♫ I want to meet once again.
♫ Hot enough to get burned.
♫ The tears in my heart.
♫ If I can pour it out to you.
♫ My love.
♫ Love or farewell.
♫ In the world where there is none.
♫ I want to meet once again.
♫ My love.
You are a lonely man who lives alone on a deserted island.
Suddenly at that moment, 3 women appear.
No. 1.
Her face is pretty but she narrates directly.
No. 2.
Her heart is like tofu but she uses informal speech.
It was right then!
Oops!
What is that bright smile?
It is extremely sexy.
The third woman.
Look at me!
1! 2! 3! Alright!
You who are wise.
Who will you choose between the 3 women?
Unni!
I am done listening!
Where are the 3 women?
I am the only woman here.
You are both old.
Hey! At every chance you bring up age!
If you are old, you are not a woman?
Till when do you think you will be young?
There is always a drinking party here.
What are you doing here?
What time is it that you are scolding the guy?
Make him work after you feed him and let him sleep.
Oh! President!
You have become deeper.
But can I ask how, how much, where and what you did with Yoo Jeong at this late hour?
Are you investigating?
What is it to you what the two of them do?
Why?
Why don't you go play with him some more?
Is this the only snack there is?
I will make something.
Why do you have to go?
Sit down.
Ahjumma!
Ahjumma, you go get the snacks.
Look here, Ahjussi.
It is because my hair is permed.
If I straighten it...
I'm like her.
Gwang Soo!
What did that ahjumma say?
I think she will be prettier with her hair straightened out.
Sit down.
Oh, seriously!
Oh, Jesus! Your taste is really vintage!
- Aigo!
- Yes, yes! Don't say anything.
Stay still. Here.
Please check the debt ratio.
I will call you back.
Se Yeon!
The Chairman's illness seemed more severe
than the rumors.
The surgery was successful.
We are watching the results.
I told you that there isn't anyone
who knows Min Hyeok as much as me, didn't I?
No matter how crazy he is over a woman, Min Hyeok...
can't abandon his family.
Shake up the K-Group.
If the Chairman collapses,
he will return.
More than anticipated,
it may take longer?
I am not that foolish, Chairman.
I have already arranged the means to escape.
I will meet with Min Hyeok.
I heard about you.
What did Father say?
The Chairman's progress isn't good.
He needs to get medical treatment briefly.
We are going to make it seem like he went down because of the foreign resort business.
When I'm not there, if even you aren't there...
the company will be in difficulty.
It was bound to happen.
It is just a little confusing because the preparations are not completed.
You have to be a support.
Hyung...
I definitely told you.
It is not a determination that will change so easily...
This is the key to the company safe-deposit box.
While I am absent, you take care of it.
Hyung!
Whether you want it or not,
you're K Group's successor.
Attorney Ahn's file that you wanted.
It is in this safe-deposit.
Attorney Ahn is of help to the K-Group now.
But he knows too many of our cards.
We don't know when Ahn Do Hoon will return.
When Attorney Ahn becomes a threat to the K-Group.
This file will be of help.
President.
You thought I didn't see you, right?
Smile.
Please smile.
I want to see you smile.
I'm going.
Documents concerning Ahn Do Hoon.
File Source: Shin Ah Foundation.
The President Dismissal Agenda for the Board.
Drafter:Ahn Do Hoon.
Shin Se Yeon.
Shin Se Yeon!
Indeed,
you only come when you need me.
Really, why are you like this?
What about this kind of stuff?
The K-Group will not collapse because of this matter.
But will Se Gwang and Shinha just let this good opportunity pass?
What are you plotting again?
What I am up to.
You know it too.
I am not one to let go of something in my hands.
If you want to protect your company,
grab onto my hand.
What's that supposed to mean?
If the image of the company becomes bad,
more than anyone else,
your father will oppose this marriage.
Isn't that what you wanted?
What I want...
is you.
You. You!
Don't say that you didn't now.
When you were having a hard time because of your mom,
when the Chairman kicked you out,
and even when that Seo Ji Hee died...
It was me who was by your side.
Se Yeon.
I love you.
I love you. I love you! I said I love you!
I'm sorry.
That woman and you, do you think it'll work out?
What happens to love that started because of revenge,
you asked me, didn't you?
That ending... I will make it for you.
Here's some more chilli.
Thank you.
Yes.
Welcome.
Please give me a bowl of Haejangguk (hangover soup).
We're closing now. Please leave.
There are still people eating.
Please give me it.
When a customer's asking for it, what are you doing?
Hurry and bring it.
Where do you think this is?
You came quickly.
You eat some too. Eat some and we'll talk.
You...you called Do Hoon here too?
You really, why -
Whose store are you trying to ruin that you are doing this?
Mom, don't worry about it.
Come out. Come out and let's talk.
Why? We can't talk here?
Sure, let's talk a bit here.
Now that Do Hoon's found a woman, let him breathe!
Why are you looking for us again and being like this?
A girl?
That's right.
She's a woman who paints.
In comparison to you-
Stop.
Shin Se Yeon..do you think she suits Oppa?
Do you think her family thinks the same?
You, come out. I said come out!
Do Hoon!
Stop it!
What? She did it first saying that she suits Do Hoon!
So imprudent!
Leave those two to talk. Is that too hard?
Affection? What affection?
Don't you go do that again needlessly!
She had his child! Do you think it's over when you say it?
Don't provide her with a reason to stick by him using the child as an excuse.
Seoul Central District Prosecutor's Office.
Contents: arraignment.
There is no use even if you sue.
You don't have any evidence! I warned you!
Is that so?
Then...
You like coming out on TV, right?
There is no use how much you squirm.
What will make you stop?
How do I make you stop? Shall I completely ruin Jo Min Hyeok?
He isn't such a terrible person to be broken by you.
Still that person... at least has sincerity.
Sincerity?
You still haven't gained hold of your senses.
You still believe that?
I believe him. You, who can't believe,
are pitiful.
It doesn't end here.
I will put you in court somehow.
In the place you looked up to,
I will make you admit it of your own accord.
Did you hear?
The corporate lawyer got imprisoned.
Will it really go bankrupt?
I saw the article.
It's no joke these days.
I saw the article. It's no joke.
What happens to us?
What do we do if it goes bankrupt?
Unni! Our restaurant being taken over, is it true?
Kang Yoo Jeong, you seem to have a good relationship with the President,
did you hear anything?
We also got an investment and...
the menu-pan was also good.
No way!
You know the least of all of us.
There is no problem with the restaurant.
The main office will face problems.
Then they will fold this kind of business first.
Then will just the name change?
Will we all get fired?
Ah! My card debt!
If I don't pay this month's rent, she will grab my hair again!
- I bough a bag last month.
- What to do?
I had expected that you sent the document to the Board of Directors.
It was no fun because it was too obvious.
I just informed the truth.
There is nothing I did well either,
so I didn't come to quibble about it.
Bring Attorney Choi Gwang Min out somehow.
I will do that.
You will definitely have to do it.
There is a file of Hyung's investigation on you.
You never know.
If you continue to be of help to the K-Group,
even if you go into jail for the hit-and-run,
Hyung will bring you out somehow.
And..this.
Listen to it when you're bored.
It is the recording of the truck driver.
It was interesting.
If you hear it, the things you did in the past
You will
I think the proceedings will become difficult.
The painting that you sent to the Director of the National Tax Service.
It was bought from Shin Ah Foundation.
If the
So?
This is your chance. I will let you go.
For the Chairman and Jo Min Hyeok, are you going to give up on your life like this?
You don't have a reason to worry about my life so much.
What is it that you want?
I heard that there was information concerning me.
When I was young..
I was a fan of chivalry books.
But the pattern is always the same.
Always the nearest person betrays.
Hand over... the material.
Attorney Ahn, you and I, our origin is similar.
We were born with nothing but thankfully we were smart so we came all the way here.
You know what makes us different?
This is your last chance.
That you won't strike me in the back because you can't have it.
Isn't betrayal too obvious?
Didn't you see it till you are fed up of it in reality and in books?
Sunbaenim!
I really wanted to do this once.
Instead of looking for the way I can live,
the person I have to protect...
I wanted to protect them.
Not in a chivalry book...
But in reality.
Jae Ha!
The 3rd generation of Se Gwang, how clumsy of you?
How can you be photographed in a picture like this?
It was your hyung who was photographed.
What?
It's information that your older brother has been buying Se Gwang Heavy Industries stocks since last year.
While you were desiring K-Group, your older brother is making your shares useless.
Why are you telling me that?
You and I...
it is true we aren't compatible.
Whenever I see you, I want to act perverse.
You and I are scum,
but let's stop the crap now.
The rumor about my father, was it you?
What is it that you want to say?
I stopped the photo with my hands.
It seems like your older brother is plotting with Shinha Hotel and trying to create bad rumors.
I like you more than your older brother.
What is it that you want?
When you feel like a drink,
call me.
Just because you do that,
you think I won't acquire the restaurant?
That's why you have no friends, you idiot!
Sit down.
I called you because I have something to say.
You and I, there is no need to inquire about each other.
Because of you, Min Hyeok says that he won't go along with the marriage that is all prepared for.
Did you hear of the company's situation?
Attorney Choi is like a real brother to Min Hyeok.
When a person like that sacrifices himself in the place of Min Hyeok for the company,
how do you think Min Hyeok would feel?
I am sorry.
If you are sorry, you should leave on your own.
Are you going to make him watch the business his father built collapse because of him?
A promise...
I made one.
Till the President tells me to go,
I promised I wouldn't go.
You don't understand what I am saying.
I am sorry.
If you can't understand, I must make you understand.
See you again.
Do it tomorrow. Why do it now?
They say if you leave dishes unwashed, you get worries.
I am done.
Aren't you tired?
No.
Will the two of you really be alright?
Unni.
If I am this happy, I will be punished, right?
I thought it would be alright for one day.
But why do I want more?
You had a hard time and you hurt till now.
It's alright for you to smile now.
Even if it is hard, it's alright.
If it wasn't for that time, I couldn't have met you unnis.
And also the President.
That's right.
If you are happy now, that will do.
Let's sleep.
It is material that will affect Shin Ah Foundation, too.
Are you handing it over being aware of it?
I know.
This will put, not only put K-Group but also you, in danger.
I can't do that.
Do as you are told.
What is the reason you are going this far?
I want to see Min Hyeok kneel in front of me and beg me desperately to save him.
Before that, you will get hurt.
Then do what I want.
I can't! I won't!
Jo Min Hyeok...
I will make him kneel in front of you.
I like that you are unchanging.
Then...
When I am really left alone,
will you hug me?
I will do that.
You are pretty.
You are prettier when you smile.
In case I fell asleep before you came,
I don't know how many cups I drank of this coffee that is only sweet.
Now I think I will live.
Yoo Jeong.
Yes.
Before me, you
shouldn't die first.
I will do that.
Father.
What brings you at this hour?
What is this, Do Hoon?
Tell me that it isn't.
Tell me that it isn't you.
Father.
Don't bother about things like this.
How can I not be bothered?
The things written here...
What is all this?
That you... abandoned Yoo Jeong's father...
what is the meaning of all this?
Yoo Jeong...
is purposely doing this because she can't accept the fact that we have broken up.
It is nothing serious.
How can this be nothing serious?
You saw how she came to the store last time, didn't you?
Yoo Jeong has changed.
She isn't in her right mind!
Do Hoon! You...
Are you really my son?
I have a meeting.
Go ahead home.
I...
I must meet Yoo Jeong.
I will meet her and hear the whole story.
If she is angry, I will apologize.
I must ask for forgiveness.
For what?
It suffices that you have lived your whole life being sorry like you sinned. What more?
You want me to live like that, too?
Don't go see Yoo Jeong.
I will take care of it.
Please go home, first.
Arraignment
It wasn't enough to get Jo Min Hyeok involved,
did you even go to my father?
What would make you stop this?
I have no intention of stopping it.
You're still in that place, just the same.
Regarding your father,
it was an accident.
Speak what is right.
It was not an accident, but murder.
That can't become an evidence.
It doesn't matter.
If not at court, media, if not at media, wherever,
as long as I follow you and reveal it wherever you are.
I'm sorry.
How convenient.
I'm sorry, Yoo Jeong.
I'll see you at the Prosecutions Office tomorrow.
Because it's a familiar place,
you shouldn't have any problem finding it.
I told you
it was an accident
beyond my ability to interfere!
It's always beyond your ability to interfere.
Because of your parents, because of me,
because of the elites!
What made your life like this
is no one else.
Don't blame the others so easily like that.
What nasty is this thing trying to pull here?
Where is this rotten smell coming from?
Are you leaving?
Why don't you stay a bit? Someone you know will be here.
Hae Jin.
Lee Hae Jin.
You've even written a recommendation for her,
weren't you two close?
Se Yeon?
Do Hoon?
Like this...
It cannot end like this!
Did you come to see father?
He is busy with the resort business.
Not that he has gotten sicker?
Why did you come?
I'm hoping he gets better by the time we have our wedding.
Just why are you like this?
Are you asking because you don't know?
I'm trying to improve the value of your company
that I heard is in trouble.
I don't need your help.
I'll talk to your father.
I don't like that.
Alright,
everything you say is right.
Thank you for being by my side, but
the marriage is not right.
To you, neither to Yoo Jeong,
I won't live my whole life feeling sorry.
What can I do?
Because I want to have you by my side.
Being unhappy by my side for your whole life,
I have to see that.
Se Yeon?
Don't call me in a friendly tone.
It's not like you.
Does that woman always call you in a friendly tone like this?
Why?
Are you too scared to come?
Attorney Ahn, why would he be here?
Shin Ah Foundation's artwork lobby
that Attorney Choi was involved in,
if the people involved are exposed,
the damage will be detrimental.
But, don't worry.
I can stop it.
What are you doing now?
This company the Chairman built
will become harder in the future.
Choi Gwang Min, your loyal dog,
for something that can be resolved in a few months,
I imagine he would have to rot for at least 10 years.
Of course, you would also be vulnerable.
While you were investing in the artworks,
the loss you incurred to K Capital is at least $27.5 mil.
The Prosecutions will see this as an embezzlement,
intended to secure illicit funds.
Get me the boss right now.
Listen carefully.
The person who can best defend you,
is none other than myself.
The person who can protect you,
none other than myself in K-Group's legal team,
is Ahn Do Hoon.
What are you going to do?
Connection has ended
Kang Yoo Jeong
What is all this bull?
He is saying you and I, we both are going to be in trouble.
Make your decision. Live together, or
crumble together.
Shin Se Yeon!
♫ I believe that I love you
♫ It's shaking me like crazy
♫ If this limping love of mine
♫ If it moves near, because