Subtitles brought to you by the Shh! Team @Viki.
Enjoy:)
SECRET
Episode 10
I'm saying I'll pay you back.
Even if I work like this, I'm saying I'll pay that debt.
But why did you even follow me here and do this?
Tell people I'm a woman who killed a person, a convict,
and make a scene to get me kicked out again?
Why do you do this, really!
Do I just look like a jerk like that to you?
Alright... alright, you have a point.
In any event... in any event, let's go up.
Let go! Let go!
Let go!
- I'm saying let's go up.
Why are you doing this?
Are you crazy?
Yes! I feel like I'm going crazy!
Worrying about you is driving me crazy!
So stay glued to my side!
If you don't come with me now,
I can start an even worse rumor.
Wherever you go,
I'll do that following you around.
If that's what it takes to have you in front of me,
I can definitely do that!
Why?
You said you hate the thought of seeing me,
just why?
That day, you were with Ahn Do Hoon.
Because I'm about to go crazy from curiosity,
just what you two have cooked up.
So, don't disappear from my eyes.
Do you now feel like going back?
He is a person who doesn't matter to me, I told you.
Then, whatever I do to Ahn Do Hoon,
you're saying it doesn't matter to you?
It's me.
Right now, immediately,
Ahn Do Hoon in the Legal Team, fire him.
There is no reason, do as you're told!
President?
Call the other law firms, too,
tell them not to accept Ahn Do Hoon.
You're pushing it!
What are you?
Just what is Ahn Do Hoon to you?!
What is he?!
Get off.
Is this where you said you were going to?
Go to work tomorrow.
Pardon?
The restaurant, as usual... I'm saying go to work.
Get off.
We're going to donate our congratulatory money
to Shin Ah Foundation.
I think it would be good for the K-Group to also donate,
if you consider the image.
Since we're the ones preparing for the wedding,
giving the congragulatory money to Shin Ah Foundation on top of that seems somewhat...
The thank-you gifts for the guests
have been determined to be the german porcelain, but
what are your thoughts on quantity?
We settled on 1000 people on our side, so
you can adjust appropriately, Madam,
keeping high standards.
You have a flair for things a bit glamorous, right?
People in that line of work,
I would rather not have them at the wedding.
For my son's wedding,
are you asking me to discriminate the guests?
I wouldn't have said anything separate like this,
to Min Hyeok's real mother.
Since this is a discussion for the two of you, and it will go on even without me,
I'll leave first.
Min Hyeok.
Isn't attending the wedding all you wanted?
Mother?
What is this? How did she get back in?
They said it was the President's order.
No wonder. Ever since this morning, the manager's condition was...
What relationship does she have with the President?
Welcome! It's nice to meet you, customer!
Hey, Substitute!
Get in.
I said get in.
Yeah, Unni let's take the ride, what else..
Why should we refuse?
Let's go! Let's go, let's go.
Thank you.
Wow... this car is really nice!
Isn't it, Unni?
Your driving is very smooth,
you're a good driver.
What aren't you good at?
But President, how did you meet Unni?
Hye Ri...
let's just go quietly.
But Unni, did you thank him?
For what?
The president went all crazy on the manager,
for firing you and telling him to bring you back.
"If the manager doesn't trust the employees
and lets them go, what is he trying to do?".
Like this. It was really cool.
Have dinner before you leave!
Hey, you dropped us all the way here, at least eat before you go.
Hye Ri, they don't want to eat here.
Leave, please.
Boss, our Unni's cooking skills are no joke.
You're really going to regret if you don't eat it. Yes?
Forget the food, I have something to say.
Let's go.
Hey! Hey!
You said you have something to say.
Do you have nothing to say?
I don't know what you want to hear from me, but
I have nothing to say.
Don't then.
Because I can find out.
There's nothing like that.
Sure, keep insisting like that.
Boss.
-That bakery...
Because it's in a bad neighborhood,
the price won't go up, and it doesn't sell,
Keeping it incurs loss.
Why don't you pay off your debt quickly,
and take it back.
Gwang Soo!
Yes.
Let's go.
Look, just look at that. They say you don't even bother
dogs when they're eating.
Crass ass, for real.
Min Hyeok!
What are you doing?
Uh...
Your tuxedo is finished. Try it on.
I told you not to touch it, didn't I?
When Chairman threw all your mom's things out,
the one who saved at least this was me.
So?
So, do you want me to be thankful?
No.
I just wanted to hear it once more.
Is this the right place he asked us to meet him?
That's what I'm saying.
It was a call from a secretary to come have dinner here.
From a secretary!
Why don't you straighten up your back?
Our son works here,
so what is there to be intimidated about?
Omo, look who's here.
Hello.
Were you going to meet us with Do Hoon, together?
No. I was the one who asked to meet you here.
Se Yeon.
I'm sorry I didn't consult you.
Because you treated me to such a wonderful dinner,
I wanted to repay you for sure.
Ah, you... didn't have to do that.
It was so delicious.
I should join you, but my work just won't end.
Mother, Father. Enjoy your dinner, okay?
Eh-alright.
O-o-kay.
Treat them well.
When you see her in this setting, she seems pretty affluent too.
Just what does her family do?
She seems to have been raised well.
She's pleasant to elders and all.
SInce it was deleted, it'll be difficult from the get-go
to check the black box video.
I can venture a guess as to who's responsible,
but I don't have the proof.
You too are curious as to what was in that video, right?
Yes.
Then restore it.
Ah, Attorney Ahn.
Did you touch other material in the Security Office?
What do you mean?
I got a call that there's damaged data.
It seems Min Hyeok ordered it to be restored.
What's the material that both of you are looking for?
I'm not sure with what motive you're asking that sort of question,
but I only checked the data related to
Pyeongchang Construction.
Is that so?
Yes.
Ah, you don't have to come too.
I will escort you to the airport.
- Never mind.
- Chairman.
Don't worry.
Be sure to help Min Hyeok while I'm gone.
Yes, sir.
Ah, and
about Director Ahn Do Hoon. There's a limit to how much
encouragement one can bestow.
Gwang Min, you make preparation well
to break him when it's necessary.
Okay, let's go.
What kind of request was this long?
He is the head of K-Group.
Even his momentary absence causes rumors to fly here.
Today's Tasting Event, is the preparation going alright?
- Yep.
Here are the plates.
Hey, Ms. Yoo Jeong. Please bring me the meat and onions.
Yes, I got it.
This is the list of people who'll be attending today's event.
Ahn Do Hoon.
Kang Yoo Jeong went to work today, right?
Yes.
Let's go to Hap Jeong Dong.
It has arrived.
There are more.
Quickly bring more of this.
- Ms. Kang Yoo Jeong.
-Yes?
President would like to see you.
What for?
I said I'll pay you for the day. Go.
President.
I said stop working for the day. How many times do I have to tell you?
As is, there's a lot of talk about how I came in with your influence.
I'd rather not make a tough situation since I've decided to work here.
Substitute. Just do as I say.
Don't work but be paid.
Why do I have to do that?
Guests have arrived.
Then I'll be going back to work.
Substitute! Hey, Substitute!
Aigoo, President Jo Min Hyeok.
Ah...
Welcome.
It's been a while.
Yes, it has.
- Got it?
- I got it.
Tell Kang Yoo Jeong to avoid coming out to the floor.
That's a little...
Why?
- I believe he picked a wrong place to belong.
- Right.
Here you are.
Do you work here?
Yes.
I will slice up the steak for you.
What's the standard for employee selection here?
That is not my role so...
I'm sorry.
It's more accurate to say that you're brazen rather than senseless.
Let's just discuss about the taste of the food.
Today is a tasting event, not an employee review day.
If you're finished, get back inside.
Do Hoon, that was Do Hoon Oppa, right?
What the heck? What the heck? Driving me crazy, seriously! Wow!!!
How can you run into him like this?
Unni, don't go out there. I'll do it.
Hye Ri, will you get some water for me?
Okay.
Weren't you supposed to have quit working?
I had some things happen.
It's difficult to find job elsewhere as well.
If it's difficult,
are you saying that you'd just grab onto whomever would help?
Don't you know who Jo Min Hyeok is?
Don't you know why he's holding on to you?
Oppa. I also don't like him. Hate him.
I heard about the parole, too.
I also know it all.
But if I'm still like this,
couldn't you first consider
that there would be a reason?
The parole?
What are you talking about?
Never mind.
It has nothing to do with you.
I have to go to work.
What are you talking about?
Move away.
I'll make sure you don't get hurt.
You,
you being here,
don't you know that's strangling my neck?
Is there even any reason I shouldn't be here?
President Jo knowing about
the relationship between you and me?
What about that? What about our relationship?
We have no relationship now.
You!
I'm saying seeing you is hard.
Seeing you in front of me,
evertime I feel my ankle is being shackled,
it's so horrifying!
The facilities are good,
and the employees are efficient.
Don't play with Yoo Jeong.
You said with your own mouth that she has nothing to do with you.
What about you Min Hyeok,
what is the reason that you keep Yoo Jeon?
I told you before.
I have an attraction for her.
As I keep seeing Yoo Jeong, it keeps getting more fun.
I'm curious.
You're curious.
Your curiosity is the problem.
She's my employee so I'll take care of it.
She has nothing to do with you.
Are you done talking?
See me.
You choose the wedding cards.
You can do at least that much.
I'm not doing this marriage by myself.
That woman,
what is she to you?
There is no reason for you to know.
This isn't a marriage, it's business.
Substitute driver.
You disappeared as soon as it ended. But why are you coming home now?
I didn't make you guys meet on purpose.
You're going to think that I did it.
Last time,
I did it.
But this time, it wasn't me.
Don't get mad at me.
I told you.
You should have gone when I told you to.
Thank you for paying attention to me.
Good Bye.
You met me then but
you abandoned me!
you abandoned me
its a lie
It's a lie It's a lie It's a-
It's a liee!!
Oh my
Yoo Jeong. Our pretty Yoo Jeong is here.
Sit here.
Unni brought an expensive brand name bag from China
Here.
All you brought back is one bottle and your making such a big deal.
Drink. Drink.
Lets celebrate our bag business being ruined.
Ayo so sad
Noo, it's so very sad
What will we eat to live now?
Live by eating our feelings
Hey! hey hey hey hey hey
You eat, eat eat eat
first eat, and then drink after
Ahhw
This..
If you place one dot on the word for sir, it becomes stranger.
Men are the ones that turn into strangers after you break up with them.
But it's strange, when he's not next to me I'm sad.
When he's next to me, it's very good.
Ohh men are the problem. Right Ja young?
Of course. You have to eat to live,
you don't need a man.
It doesn't matter.
How does love change?
You!
Love doesn't change, people change.
So, you have to pick a smart person.
A smart person.
Grocery receipt for bread
2013.10.01
(Our Supermarket)
Yoo Jeong.
Hello.
We didn't see you at all for a while. What are you
doing here at this time?
This...
This. It's this places' receipt right?
Yes. It's ours.
This is my dad's jacket.
You dad came here frequently and bought cream bread.
He couldn't get away from where he lived his whole life.
But, every time he came, there was a woman with him.
But that day, he came alone.
Ah! Your father looked really well!
That day, he even recognized me.
That day, is this the day?
I don't know whether it was that night or not.
You know, that day it poured rain.
A man came and took him.
Wasn't he the man who was supposed to be your husband?
(Wuthering Heights)
You must have a lot of free time.
You even have time to read a book.
It's all because of you.
Just because you moved the board,
don't think that you can treat me like a puppet.
I told you it's not like that.
The board already...
I don't care.
It wouldn't have even mattered if they fired me unanimously.
The important thing is you.
You couldn't have done that.
Min Hyeok.
I told you.
Don't pull Do Hoon close to you.
Us,
we are not even friends anymore.
Get out of my room.
Get in.
What is this?
Today, the President wants you to work at his house.
We already told the restaurant.
I can't skip on my own will.
Tell him that I'll go to the restaurant.
I brought her.
Okay.
Why did you call me?
You're my employee. Work here today.
What?
Since I sent the employee that works here
on a vacation, the house is a mess.
You do it instead.
Clean this up too.
Who are you?
Where is Myung Ae Ahjumma?
She went on a vacation so it...
Why a vacation so suddenly?
I want something spicy.
This is really tasty.
Unni, eat with me. It's really good.
Quickly, sit.
Hey.
Have you eaten?
Taste it.
Eat it. Quickly!
You only listen to Min Hyeok oppa. Quickly!
Isn't it good?
Yes.
What's up with your reaction? You're really boring just like my brother even though you guys aren't siblings.
Oppa,
what does Ahjussi like to eat?
Lawyer Chae. Does he have anything he likes?
Cup Ramen.
He likes it.
What? What is that?
When he was young,
he said he ate it really well.
Oppa, try this.
The new unni, she's a really good cook.
Get me some coffee.
Eat it all. I ate some while making it.
The coffee is in the kitchen?
This, where should I put it?
I cleaned everything. There is nothing to do.
If you don't have anything for me to do, I'll leave.
Why do you have nothing to do? No.
Bring that.
And, you have something to do.
Read this book.
Take it!
I'm curious about the story but i'm too bothered to read it.
Read it and write a summary.
Now.
Wait.
Don't be in front of me.
Go over there and read quietly.
You really do come when I call for you.
Did you call me to see you like this?
You're the only person I show myself to like this.
Why are you so sad?
Is it because you met with Min Hyeok?
I thought the wedding preparations were going well.
It does look like that.
But, I think were getting farther.
I thought that's how you were going to get him.
You being sad because of Min Hyeok,
I don't want to see it.
Stop drinking.
You should have been born into a better family.
Had your family been close to my family,
I might have liked you first instead of Min Hyeok.
No one is born picking their parents.
When a family is made,
there is no picking.
Except your spouse.
But you know something?
Se Yeon,
the only choice that you had,
you gave it up yourself
You want to drink, right?
Then drink.
Hey, Ahn Do Hoon!
Come here.
Have a glass.
You brought a car?
I'll call a substitute driver.
Boss. Boss.
Yeah.
I'll leave.
Come to work here again.
Boss.
Yeah, I'm the boss. So come here.
Yes.
Heathcliff and Catherine were fated to love...but Catherine ends up in a contract marriage to a nobleman...
Catherine didn't get to hear the confession of his love and Heathcliff seeks revenge on the already married Catherine
Read this.
A revenge that started because of love,
how it ends.
...Heathcliff who loses his real love Catherine, dies
a lonely death.
That person. Just because he lent you some money,
isn't he taking advantage of you?
Our boss isn't doing this because of money.
It didn't seem that he called me to take advantage of me.
Hey! Hey, hey, hey. Wake up.
There's no answer if you fall for those rich guys who are having a passing curiosity.
But unni, how long do you have to go?
The manager was so mad that today's shift was
all messed up.
He was so annoyed saying that he might have to find another part-timer...
I'll tell him tomorrow. This doesn't seem right.
Boss.
(Min Hyeok's signature)
Some man signed it.
What are you. What are you doing right now?
This.
This. I need to wash it.
Please move away.
What is this?
Why is a girl so strong?
Thank you.
That day,
you took me to the hospital.
For saving me,
thank you.
Yeah,
who told you to faint in someone else's building?
Go away.
♫ For me to have
♫ Too precious that person
♫ I dare love that person
♫ To a bad person like me
♫ Not a good match
♫ I love the one person
♫ That person is you
♫ Even though I cannot say
♫ Hot enough to get burned
The tears in my heart
♫ If I can pour it out to you,
my love
♫ Love or farewell
In the world where there is none
♫ I want to meet you once again
♫ My love
♫ For me to call
♫ Too precious that name
♫ I want to shout but
♫ I swallow it again today
♫ It's the cold lies again
♫ Love brings tears
♫ Tears then bring love
♫ I say please embrace but
♫ My love
♫ When my tears dry out
Wouldn't it be great if dad came by San?
Maybe our San might be able to eat jjajangmyeon.
♫ My love
If you don't have anything for me to do, I'll leave.
Starting tomorrow, I'll go to the restaurant.
I heard the other employees are having a hard time because of me.
I have no honor.
Un-
Unni.
You!
Ahh!
What?
I won't be satisfied even if I hit her more. Why did you stop me?
Didn't you say what you wanted you say that time?
Why did you come here?
What is this? You guys met?
But you just left her?
Unni,
I'm sorry.
I didn't know.
I can't sleep well.
Because I think of San.
I'm really sorry.
If I didn't say this, I would regret it forever.
You! If your sorry,
then why did you do that to a child?
San's name can come out of your mouth?
I really didn't know!
Why are you yelling?
The child's body was all blue. Are you a human?
No, it's alright. I didn't know.
Stop. Please.
Saying that you didn't know
is not a reason to be forgiven.
Unni.
(message from Do Hoon)
I'm in front of your house. I'll wait for you.
You said that seeing me pained you.
What is it?
I think Jo Min Hyeok is restarting the investigation
of the hit-and-run case.
Is it you?
Oppa.
Did you feel you were treated unfairly?
Then how should I interpret you sticking close to Min Hyeok.
It's not what your thinking of.
I'm not worrying.
You were the one driving.
You,
decided that yourself.
That,
did you come to confirm that?
I have something to confirm too.
Yesterday,
that supermarket in front of the railroad,
the woman said that she saw you
the day that Dad disappeared.
She said that you took Dad.
Is it true?
No.
She probably saw wrong.
Is it true?
Yeah.
Lies.
Oppa, you don't know how to lie.
Unni.
What? Did that person say something again?
What do you mean by again?
The person that wanted to stop your parole.
What do you mean?
He told me to stop your parole...
Tell me more clearly. Did you see correctly?
Is it that person!
That's right.
That guy that came for community service.
Why is that hard?
Just argue that you need the CCTV because some person scratched your car and you need to find that person.
Just as much as there are people wanting to be trusted there are no guilty people.
There is nothing wrong with not trusting black haired animals.
You stay here.
It was last January right?
She didn't come?
It seems she filed a sick day at the restaurant.
Where is she sick?
That...
Go find out.
Why?
Nothing.
I also have something to confirm.
Yesterday, that supermarket next to the railroad,
The woman said she saw you.
The day that dad disappeared.
She said you took him.
It that true?
Lies.
Oppa, you don't know how to lie.
Dad, how did this happen?
Dad!
In case. If Dad goes out alone, it's dangerous.
I filed his information already.
This was made so that he cannot take it off himself.
Where is the house for you to not come?
Let's go to Yoo Jeong.
Yes, Yoo Jeong is waiting for you. Let's get in.
Do you remember this?
Why would I not remember?
You were the one driving but let Yoo Jeong take the blame. Do you think I would not know that?
♫ Would it be alright if I move closer
♫ I was scared so I stood still
♫ Did we really have to meet
♫ I can't give an answer
♫ Because unerasable scar hurts
♫ Would I be able to tell you again that
I love you
♫ No matter how many times I let you go,
you're still the one