Secret
Attorney Ahn! Attorney Ahn!
About that news on the media...
About that great Attorney Ahn Do Hoon,
I have something to say!
Attorney Ahn, have you got something to say?
Stop it! I said stop!
Just stop it, really!
Why?
San...
Aren't you going to see him?
San... Your son.
Don't you want to see him?
How dare you...
How dare you mention my San with your mouth?
My San is alive, and...
there is no way I wouldn't have known...
How could you use San as an excuse...
You...
It was for you and Do Hoon.
The child is growing fine. Trust my words.
You two should live first.
Yoo Jeong, with that red line on your record,
unmarried woman with a child on top of that,
how are you going to live?
Do Hoon also with you,
would you guys even make sense?
How can you take responsibility for a child born in prison?
For a person to whom your own child is so precious,
how could you...
How could you do that?
So what if he was born in prison?
Can the mother have a record?
Is it not okay to raise him alone?
So what if his dad's a murderer!
Bring him out! Bring him out!
Bring him out! Where's my San?!
How can you?! Where is my San?
HOW CAN YOU?!!!
Why? Why? WHY??? Why?
Why? Why?
Why?!
Hello!
- You know that time...
Oh, of course!
Yea, that's right.
Mom!
Why that woman...
No! What are you doing to my son?
Jeong Hwan, are you okay?
That's San.
His name is San, you know.
Jeong Hwan, let's go.
He's my San!
Why?! Really!
Let go! LET GO!!!
Yoo Jeong!
Take a good look!
Look what you have taken away from me!
Didn't know...
I, really didn't know.
Don't you dare tell me you didn't know!
You could have found out.
When they said San was dead,
you just didn't see?
YOU DIDN'T WANT TO SEE IT!!!
While your mom was working on this,
did you just pretend not to know?
Saying you didn't know?!
How could you?!
Unni...
San didn't recognize me.
How could he not recognize his mom?
How could he do that?
I have to find San.
I have to bring him back.
Of course, you do.
You stomach was hurt, you breast fed him,
of course you have to take him!
These bad people, I'll just...!
Hey, Ja Yeong! Where are you going now?
You're going to go and do what?
You want to crash everything?
That's just you taking out your own feelings.
It won't be helping Yoo Jeong at all!
Hye Ri, what are you doing just standing there?
Go get a bowl of cold water.
Hey, Ja Yeong,
when we were in the can,
do you remember that darky granny in the cell next door?
That granny,
she is a documentation forgery expert.
There is no technician in the country that she doesn't know.
Let's first contact her. Contact her and
the bastard who made a fake death certificate,
and a fake adoption paper,
let's go find that bastard.
Are you still a human being doing things like that?
How could one human do that to another?
No, this was all for Do Hoon-
- STOP!!
It's always just "Do Hoon, Do Hoon."
That's what ruined Do Hoon, woman!
Aigoo~ What am I to do?
I'm so sorry towards Yoo Jeong. What to do?
How did you do this?
Document wise, he was clearly a dead child!
Mom, do you know what wrong you have done?
Ah, well, you see...
Jung who comes to the sauna...
because her niece didn't have a child...
Mother!!
I did it for you.
Would I have done it for myself?
Would you think even for me
that it was easy to cut my bloodline?
How would you have raise him?
Being loved in a good family, and might as well
Excuse us!
Yes, we'll excuse ourselves.
We came from a police office.
What is it?
Ah...yes...Mrs. Park Gye Ok?
Mrs. Park Gye Ok, you know Mr. Lee Sang Cheol, right?
From you Park Gye Ok, Lee Sang Cheol
received $3,000, and
forged a death certificate, he said.
Is that correct?
Ah, the victim filed a complaint.
Anyway,
on charges of document forgery and
for the crime of utilizing a forged document,
we're going to take you in for questioning, yes?
Wait a moment.
Even if that was true, it's a first offence.
i know the rule, you needs to proceed without detention.
I am the grandmother.
I did it to benefit everyone involved,
do you think I've done it without any reason?
Well, of course. Everyone has their reasons, I'm sure.
Whatever. I'll be escorting you now.
Now.
Wait... Look here.
- Do Hoon!
- Wait, Detective!
Honey. Honey!
Detective!
Do Hoon! Do Hoon!
Are you going to let your mom get taken like that?
Don't you think you should do something!
What exactly?
What more can I do?
Honey! Honey!
Why? Do you have something to say?
What is it?
You have something to say, don't you?
Hurry up and say it.
Kang Yoo Jeong,
they say her child is alive.
What?
Park Gye Ok?
Someone came for you.
If you make San appear to be dead,
it will get me to leave Do Hoon, and
if you bring San back alive from death,
I would be so thankful,
I will forgive Do Hoon,
did you expect it like that?
Back then, that was the best choice.
You also had a whole life ahead of you...
Just like my father,
try having a hard time.
Do Hoon rotting in prison,
please watch him.
Yoo Jeong!
Do Hoon did no wrong. Do Hoon didn't know.
It was all my doing!
For a person to whom your child is so precious to you,
you shouldn't have done that to me.
That family loves San so much.
I go and see him every month.
They always make me eat dinner with him,
because I'm his grandma.
They're such good people.
What about me?
Were you afraid I wouldn't be able to raise him like that?
Face of the son who is alive,
the pain of not being able to see him when you want to,
please experience it.
Yoo Jeong!
I'm asking you.
Please don't take...
Jeong Hwan from me.
I...
have never abandoned San.
If I had known...
If I had known that his birth mother was alive,
I would have come to find you.
When Jeong Hwan grows bigger,
when he reaches an age at which he can understand,
that I gave birth to you with my heart,
I was going to tell him.
I wasn't trying to deceive him.
Since he's still...
at an age when he can't understand,
it's still not too late.
No...
How I raised him...
My Jeong Hwan...no, no.
It can't let you have your way, either.
My San,
I also cannot give up on him.
No...
Please stop drinking.
Please stop.
Are you going to say you want to die
after drinking like before?
Yes.
If I had rather died back then,
my son breaking down like this,
I probably didn't see it.
Mom will be coming out soon.
Since it was her first offense, it will be over with a fine.
Like venom.
You or your mother,
how can humans be so venomous?
It's because you're so weak!
Alright.
It's all no-good,
my fault.
Yeah.
Ahjusshi!
This girl, really.
The Chairman is waiting!
No, he needs to see me first.
Min Joo!
- We couldn't even give him a nice birthday since ahjussi was in jail.
Come here. I bought you some gifts.
Ta da!
These are the gifts?
I heard you liked this, Ahjussi.
Wasn't that so?
I like it.
That's a relief.
In the winter,
I took my younger brother and went to find my father.
Father didn't come out and I was hungry.
I the fully grown kid was crying, when
the Chairman came to us, and
this is what he bought for us.
It was really delicious.
What's all this food that are less than good?
Please wait. I'll have a meal prepared soon.
Ahjusshi said he wanted to eat this.
You should just take care of your daughter like that.
You're not even letting me eat because I might gain weight.
You can't. You have to lose 2kg more.
Do you want to look plump on your graduation album?
Min Joo, don't eat ramyun!
Ahjusshi, my mom seems totally like a stepmother, right?
Why is the reaction so serious like this?
Just go along with it. I have known everything.
I've known since middle school.
Even as you know, you do it on purpose?
Yes.
When I call her stepmother,
My mom looks like a female main character of a tragedy,
a tiny bit.
At that time, she is very pretty.
After that, she always treats me nice.
I got mad at first for no reason, but
still, she is my mother. Right, Ahjussi?
There was a blanket
with stars and a moon.
One moment please.
Here.
When I first bought him home,
he couldn't sleep without this. Because it's a little old...
I can take it, right?
I'm home.
Oh, Jeong Hwan.
Jeong Hwan, why did you come home so early?
Why, does your tummy hurt again?
If your tummy keeps hurting, then mommy...
Mommy also hurts.
Mommy also hurts?
But who is that ahjumma?
Mommy,
why are you crying?
Are you hurt?
Why are you hurt?
Is it because of that Ahjumma?
No! It's because of me.
That person hasn't done anything wrong.
That doesn't seem right.
Should I straighten out that Ahjumma?
Next week,
there is a trial.
I'll see you there.
It's what I made for San, but
she said he can sleep without this now.
He has an allergic reaction when he eats blue crabs.
When he is upset,
she said he has a habit of tearing up the paper.
During the weekend,
she said he goes bicycle riding with dad.
Have you known?
Yoo Jeong.
I'm totally confused.
It's my child, but
it's clearly my San, but
what he likes, or
how he grew up,
I have no clue.
What would you want me to do?
Do you still not know?
Are you not coming home again today?
I have to work on the paintings
that will be going to Hannam-dong.
She is quite a capricious person,
as you would also know.
The gallery business,
you should stop doing that.
Buying and selling the paintings does not suit you.
That is my work. What would I do, if it doesn't suit me?
You...
look the most comfortable when you're painting.
I'm busy.
Would you go?
Se Yeon,
when I was having a hard time,
did you feel like this then, too?
I want to do something somehow, but
because it's hard to figure out what I should do.
I would like to see you stop having a hard time
because of me.
Still...
you and I...
we had fun.
Without even knowing that we were the outcasts
to the other kids,
we were hanging out together, and
we had great time by ourselves.
- Stop!
In order not to like you,
because I'm trying, so I said stop it.
I'm sorry.
Try this.
Your mom's seaweed roll, it's good?
This? This? Ah.
Mom makes great Seaweed roll, right?
- It tasted good.
It's the best, right?
Jeong Hwan?
Jeong Hwan.
Ahjumma, you came again?
I'm not Ahjumma.
I'm aunt.
Aunt who is good friends with mom.
Go and play.
See you again?
Jeong Hwan.
Go.
Dad, I want to ride the bicycle!
Yeah, let's ride the bicycle.
Going~
Woo hoo hoo~
Thank you, Ahjussi.
Oh, ah. Are you alright?
Thank you. Let's go.
Oppa,
what you took away from me, look.
In your life,
what you have missed, look at him.
Woo Whoa...
Abandoning that precious thing...
what has happened to us,
just look.
I'm sorry, Yoo Jeong.
I did wrong.
Yoo Jeo...
..am sorry.
Yoo Jeong...
I said I did wrong...
Fool, fool, fool!
How are you going to live with your child away from you?
Unni, I'm not making him be apart from me.
Just because of being a mom,
doesn't mean you must live holding the child in your arms.
My San being happy
is enough for me.
You don't know how happy my San smiles.
Ou, ou I'm so frustrated.
Ou, I don't know.
If my child was taken away like that,
I would go to the end of the earth to find him.
I also
thought I would be like that.
I couldn't do it.
Because when I had San taken away from me,
I was so hurt, and
had experienced feeling like dying,
I couldn't take him back.
When that family
first took my San,
they said he cried so hard.
Looking for mom,
for a whole week, without even eating anything,
they said he cried like that.
And so how can I take San back?
Missing that mom,
San who will cry all day...
How can I take him?
Premarital Agreement
You seemed to have overvalued me.
Even if you didn't see me, I thought I could hold out, but
I can't.
Let's call it quits now.
Se Yeon.
Jo Min Hyeok.
Don't worry.
I'm Shin Se Yeon.
You're handing over your shares to Se Yeon?
To the girl who could turn around anytime,
you hand over your shares?
It's not Se Yeon, but
the Shin Ah Foundation that I'm handing them over to.
Well,
Se Yeon will make good use of them.
Is your head...
I'll give up the management rights.
Min Hyeok!
That's not a decision you can make carelessly.
I didn't decide carelessly, but
I decided rationally.
You're better than me, Hyung.
I'm saying this for the K-Group, not as your son.
So,
against all odds, are you saying you want to
go to that woman that doesn't make sense?
No.
I'm dying to go to her, but
I can't, because I feel embarrassed.
Embarrassed?
There is no one in the world who lives without sin.
It's important how you repay it.
That woman told me that.
I...
will pay for my sins.
What?
The roughest place,
where no employees want to go,
please send me there.
I'll work hard most seriously.
Transfer Contract
No.
I still haven't paid for all of the debt yet.
Please take it, otherwise I'll be in trouble.
You can pay the debt slowly.
A little at a time, slowly.
He has to hear from you even like that,
so the Boss can withstand.
The boss...
is leaving for Armenia today.
Leaving?
He won't be back for a while.
♫ One day that one day
♫ Each of us, we saw for the first time today
♫ Suddenly I felt suffocated and
My painful memories
♫ Have all disappeared
♫ I believe that I love you
♫ It's shaking me like crazy
♫ If this limping love of mine
♫ If it moves near, because you might hide from fear
♫ Even though I say I'm hurt as if I could die
♫ I only watch
♫ Even though now is not the time
♫ I can feel you as you tremble
♫ Because my heart knows you
♫ Because you are the love
♫ I believe that I love you
♫ It's shaking me like crazy
♫ If this limping love of mine
♫ If it moves near, because you might hide from fear
♫ Even though I say I'm hurt as if I could die
♫ I only watch
You came?
What is it?
I'm going to close up the gallery and leave.
Before I go,
I wanted to see you, Do Hoon.
You must have heard the news about me.
Did you still want to see me?
I'll be indicted next week.
The person who killed Seo Ji Hee
is not Yoo Jeong, but
me.
That's why I wanted to see you more.
Because I thought I should tell you before I go.
The person who killed Seo Ji Hee
is not you, Do Hoon, but
is me.
I told the Chairman that I'll marry Min Hyeok.
With Min Hyeok, this is as far as I would allow.
I'm pregnant.
We'll keep the baby.
Look here...
That baby,
do you think the Chairman will accept it?
No,
do you think he will let you give birth to it?
Please take it.
The Chairman doesn't know you're pregnant, yet.
Should I go and tell him right now?
Disappear. From Min Hyeok's eyes. Forever. Until you die.
This is my last warning.
Next time, there won't be this kind of a thing.
I didn't know she would really turn up dead.
"I wish she would die."
At that time, I really thought like that.
I thought I would be happy,
even if I have Min Hyeok like that, but
ultimately it seems Min Hyeok and I
were not meant to be.
I am sorry.
Do Hoon, you got caught in the wind of what I started,
you were at the wrong place at the wrong time, that's all.
"Why did it end up like this?",
I thought about it over and over.
If that day I wasn't there,
if it didn't rain, if only the truck didn't pass by,
it was unfair.
Because I felt unfair about this misfortune
that only comes to me, I grit my teeth.
I was afraid that everything I have built
might crumble in one moment.
Then also Yoo Jeong,
also my child,
I have also lost my family and became like this.
Do Hoon.
The one who killed Seo Ji Hee is me.
It was my fault.
Thanks for all this time.
Please have a good travel.
I've heard,
the Shin Ah Foundation file,
that you never released it.
Thank you.
Your paintings,
I think I'll miss them.
Regarding the kidnapping of Kang Woo Cheol last month,
are you acknowledging it?
Yes.
The hit-and-run incident at Route #6 4 years ago,
instead of Kang Yoo Jeong who served out the term
due to the judgment at that time,
the fact that it was you the defendant who drove,
do you acknowledge it?
The fact that you the defendant drove the victim,
Seo Ji Hee, at that time to her death,
I asked you if you acknowledge it?
Father, let me borrow your car today.
Where are you going that you are taking the car?
Do you need to go somewhere far?
I have things to do.
Yeah, you need a car to make sure you get there on time.
You have to do better this time. If you do like the last time...
Mom, I'm late. I'll be back.
Do Hoon, Do Hoon, this, this, just eat this.
I'll be back.
Prosecutor, take care.
Oh, right. But did you get your wiper blade fixed?
I heard on TV that it won't rain today for sure, so don't worry.
Aigoo... it must be nice living without worry all the time.
Aigoo, I'm going to eat my son's leftover.
Why isn't this working?
It's not working?
No... that's strange.
Wait here for just a moment.
- Okay.
Yes, Director.
Yes, I am almost there. Yes.
I think Min Hyeok has gone to see that woman.
No matter what, bring me that child.
I love you.
Oppa!
Oh, Oppa!
I told you not to come out.
What was it?
Oh, I'm so relieved. What a relief!
Let's go quickly!
- Wait a minute. Let me clear it off the road.Other cars may have accidents, too.
Defendant, do you acknowledge it?
Yes.
RET
SECRET
Wow, there is a look of president about you.
When did you come?
- Early morning.
Did the preparations go well?
Are you really not going to regret it?
I have done enough regretting till now.
Ahjussi!
Min Joo.
Ah, you arrived?
We're going to be late, let's go quickly.
Okay.
Those two... what are they?
While you were away, those two have been dating.
My Hye Ri
Oppa, are you busy?
You too, what?
Oppa will be there soon.
Then.
Hey, Gwang Soo!
Gwang Soo!
I saw Assemblyman Shin's wife yesterday at the shop,
and her spirit was down.
Assemblyman Shin probably couldn't be
on this presidential election, right?
I don't know.
Because they are the types who will crawl out somehow,
once the dust settles.
Are you really not going?
Still, it's the presidential inauguration.
Why? Gwang Min will do well by himself.
You said he seemed like a son, but it was a lie.
Do you still want to give it to Min Hyeok?
Min Hyeok did as much as he could.
Now, let him live doing what he wants.
Attorney Choi...
President Choi should do alright.
Well...
As the only son I have...
Aside from that, what do we do about Min Joo?
The age difference with President Choi is a bit too much.
She keeps insisting to get married.
She must be taking after you.
What?
You also have lived well for about 20 years,
after being with me.
2008. [Ahn Do Hoon's prisoner number]
Letter.
Ah, what's the occasion? A letter arrived for you.
Wow, it's the pizza bread!
Are you saying it's coffee franchise business?
Because they haven't completed the enrollment yet,
it seems it won't be ready until next month.
I'll be the one selling that coffee.
I'm so diligently going to that Barista Hagwon, because of that.
This thing's not even paying the rent,
with that as an excuse!
How about Ae Sook Unni?
Congratulations!
Where's Alex?
Are you calling a neighborhood dog?
What do you mean "Alex", to your brother-in-law?
My Alex... says he is inviting all of you!
He said he will make a lot of Nigerian food.
You look too pretty with your hair straightened out like that.
You should've been making yourself pretty like that already.
What good does that do?
The potatohead who said I would look pretty if my hair was straightened out, is dating some chick right here.
Omo, how are you?
- Sure can't be the nobleman.
What would our Alexandra like to eat?
Streusel bread.
Give me one of these too.
Yummy, yummy.
Forget it... ummm.
She-she's coming out, she's coming out!
- Hey, Unni, Unni!
- Hospital, hospital, hospital, go to the hospital!
Get in first, get in. Okay, okay, it's okay.
Unni, I'll wrap things up here and go.
So, go there first, ok?
It's sweet. I don't like sweet things.
I didn't come to see you,
I came because I'm curious about something.
You made a wish that time at the Buddhist tower.
What was that you said then?
I said that it was a secret.
Where is the secret, secret? When it's the end.
Once I let you know about everything, it won't be fun.
President,
you don't like things that are not fun.
It's not fun, so tell me what I'm curious about.
I don't want to.
Why?
Because it has to be a secret,
so President can keep looking for me.
I am not a President anymore.
Is that right?
So, don't call me by "President" but by my name.
You still have a lot more debt left.
Do as I tell you. Say it.
Min Hyeok.
Again.
Say it again.
Subtitles brought to you by the Shh! Team @ Viki
Thank you to our manager bkiss
Thank you to our English moderators: Lazarini, SignsofSerendipity, shms
Thank you to segmenters: mihaelagh, Hnatiuc_Beniamin, narin78, steffioana26, shms, Va12ni, AmyPun,
SignsofSerendipity, Dudie, loolboi, salz, trucalling, luminosity, surrealspace
Thank you to Kor - Eng subbers: surrealspace,leenlee91,ZtarBrite,babyinspiritestar1,bmw277,
juicyfruit,Zizzy18,
Apollonion,geneva68,ginakim2469,EnaShin,
brownmebee,asiankoalaluv,J_Y_B,riceNramen,KLoveSubs,Sidra,jennayunnn,
pandaberries,Autumngirl09,tkadi,leadahsmile,ElfSonya,gmtn96
Thank you to the English editors: kakashiandme, Arishia, Beccah, surrealspace
Thank you to our channel page designer: nugu
Thank you to the other languages moderators and subbers!
Thank you for watching this drama with us!