Secret
As related to the suspicion of K-Group's tax evasion,
Breaking News "K-Group Chairman Jo in critical condition,  Secretly leaving for Germany"
starting this week, the Group's management team
has been being called in for questioning, while
activities regarding illicit funds, and other suspicions
such as offshore tax evasion,
it was confirmed that they have begun
magnifying the investigation.
Are you saying you want to hand this place
over to Segwang?
Attorney Ahn's file that you wanted
is in this safe-deposit box.
When Attorney Ahn becomes a threat to K-Group,
this file will become helpful.
This will put not only K-Group,
but also you in danger, Se Yeon.
Listen to it when you're bored.
It's the truck driver's voice recording, and
it was very interesting.
When you were taking my father and abandon him,
did you not think of things like this?
Suing won't be of any use.
What would make you stop this?
Jo Min Hyeok,
should I decisively ruin him?
It won't end here.
Whatever it takes, I'll make you stand for trial.
In the place that you so looked up to,
I'll make you admit it on your own accord.
Like this...
It cannot end like this.
Why?
Are you too scared to come?
Attorney Ahn, why would you come here?
Shin Ah Foundation's artwork lobby
that Attorny Choi was involved in,
if the people involved are exposed,
the damage will be detrimental.
But, please don't worry.
I can stop it.
What are you doing right now?
This company that the chairman built,
will become harder in the future.
Listen carefully.
The person who can best defend you,
is none other than me.
The person who can protect you, Jo Min Hyeok,
is none other than myself in the K-Group legal team,
Ahn Do Hoon.
What are you going to do?
Kang Yoo Jeong
What is all this bull?!
He is saying you and I, we both are going to be in trouble.
Make your decision.
Live together, or crumble together.
Shin Se Yeon!
Not only you and the K-Group, but also Ms. Shin Se Yeon,
and Shin Ah Foundation's Assemblyman Shin as well.
And Yoo Jeong.
I know very well about her.
She'll admonish herself, taking the blame
for this situation,
and suffer because of it.
I told you to no longer bother Kang Yoo Jeong!
You also... between that great love and your position,
you'll have to choose one of the two.
Of course, you'll choose K-Group.
You and I,
can you say we're different?
I had something I wanted to ask, so.
What are you doing now?
Don't you know that better?
Now,
what are you going to do?
Boss
Yoo Jeong, listen to me.
Are you okay?
Regardless of whatever Attorney Ahn said,
do what you have to.
Boss...
You trust me, right?
Yes.
I wouldn't crumble that easily.
Trust me and go.
RET
SECRET
I told you before, right?
That you and I are different.
Today I'm going to meet with your father.
The news about the marriage break up
will come out tomorrow.
Are you really going to the end?
Is that woman so great?
This marriage was broken because of me.
I'll take all responsibilities.
I'll do my best not to let you get hurt.
I'm sorry to have dragged it out so long.
Jo Min Hyeok!
Go back to the Shin Se Yeon that I know.
Taking these types of unmeasured steps doesn't suit you.
Using Kang Yoo Jeong wasn't enough, now you're using Se Yeon?
Shin Ah Foundation,
don't touch it.
You're the one who made the choice.
If something goes wrong with Se Yeon,
it's because of you right away.
And of course, the K-Group,
you'll regret it.
Regret? I won't.
In order for me to survive, stopping Yoo Jeong from
doing something she should...
That's what should be more regrettable.
Before being Kang Yoo Jeong's man,
you're the K-Group's heir.
That the K-Group is vulnerable,
please don't forget.
I will not be going alone.
If I go,
I will be going together with you.
You're okay, right?
Yes.
How about you, Boss?
If you're okay, then it's all good.
Tomorrow,
the news about the marriage break up will come out.
It's my choice.
You have nothing to worry about.
You just be by my side, that's all.
Okay?
Internal reference re unfair supplier acquisition of K Group.
K Hotel Convention Center expansion, remodeling construction
unfair internal transactions Survey
K Cultural Foundation director transactions specific format
account withdrawals i&gt;
If this is all true, they're all breaking news material.
You sure it's okay?
I wouldn't have done this if I worried about being "okay".
I'm not trying to criticize the K Group where
several thousands work.
Rather, Chairman Jo Han Il and President
Jo Min Hyeok that tried to gain illegal succession control...
re previous President's slush fund,
"K Group Legal Team Attoney Ahn Do Hoon,exposes K Group's corruption."
and the lobbying effort with a government official
to public and official.
During his tenure as a Prosecutor, Attorney Ahn Do Hoon
who was investigating the K Group's corruption,
immediately upon his resignation entered K Group,
Yes. Of course our Chairman has no idea.
That story isn't going to fly.
Our side blocked the news of our disengagement.
Father!
Don't bring out the talk of that trivial girl any more!
To me she isn't "that trivial girl".
I-
Are you trying to bring in a woman like that who was connected
to a jerk like that into our home, punk?
Oh! He's here! He's here!
The Director didn't come to work today.
What were you guys doing all this time?!
I'm sorry.
Schedule a press conference for today and make ready the materials to reply with.
Yes, I understand.
Gwang Soo.
Let's go to meet Hyung.
We can't leave it like this.
What are you doing?
As for you...
I told you definitely.
I'm not going in alone.
(making reference to the fact that he won't go to jail alone)
I'm thinking of going together with that man you want to protect so much, Jo Min Hyeok.
Stop it.
Stop it immediately.
Make me stop it, why don't you?
It should be difficult.
What I said is all the truth.
The truth...
Then I guess I can just tell the truth too.
What kind of human being you are.
Get out.
Tomorrow.
Don't forget and take part in the cross examination.
Get out!
Wow, Kang Yoo Jeong.
There's a reward for all the time I spent chasing you around and training you.
Look at this,
I knew that you were going to worry this much
which is why I came.
But still, because of me...
I told you not to say things like that.
Just,
just try saying..."It will all turn out all right."
"It will all turn out all right," say it.
It will turn out all right.
That's right.
Since you said, "it will turn out all right," it will all turn
out fine.
What's happened?
My father came and went.
My father,
his reputation to others is important,
so don't start rumors about this.
Shin Hwa Foundation's materials haven't been turned over yet.
Only the ones that they were already investigating.
It doesn't matter.
Look at the state you're in. It does matter!
We can stop even now.
If we stop...
Along with me...
Can you leave with me?
You said that you wanted to leave?
Let's go.
While you do the things that you want to do.
Without any thought.
Thank you.
Because of you, Do Hoon,
I really am going to marry Min Hyeok.
The Chairman who wanted to be released, I only barely was able to convince him otherwise.
Tomorrow go back to find the Chairman and tell him that you'll continue with the wedding.
Please leave.
Turning your back to your father, how much harder to you want to make things?
I told you to get out!
After you sent your mother (after she died), the you that was suffering and in pain,
I held and raised you.
Are you going to also send your father and live your whole life regretting? Over that kind of a woman?
Over a woman like you, even Father...
He threw away my mother.
You.
Are you acting like this because you really don't know,
or are you pretending not to know?
My coming into this house was by your mom's request.
The me who was only a native singer on the stage, it's true that the Chairman saw me nicely,
but it was only to there.
Even you know,
that Madam (Min Hyeok's mom) was having a hard time psychologically.
"Living as K Group's Madam, I can't do it anymore,"
the person that requesting you and the Chairman,
was your mother.
What? That doesn't even make any sense!
- Fine.
Don't believe it.
That there is even love like that that doesn't make sense,
tell the Chairman with your own mouth.
He doesn't listen to my words anymore.
The President asked for me to escort you.
Thank you.
The President has a lot of work to do today.
Yes.
Let's go.
That day, it's true that I gave Kang Woo Cheol a ride.
While I had momentarily parked my car in front of a
store he disappeared.
His Medic Alert bracelet disappeared.
What that bracelet means, there aren't a lot of people
who know.
The person who put that bracelet on
will have had some reason to take it off.
Leaving a father that had no directional sense
due to dementia,
Kang Yoo Jeong was drinking alcohol at a club.
That she had lost her father, I was only notified later. I only received her request, and
I only went to find him.
That night the store owner who saw my father said this.
As for that day, he was fine.
That he even recognized people.
What did my father say, who had regained his senses,
that it was worth putting him out onto the street?
Where you that afraid of him?
It's the start now.
That day, what had happened to my father,
you're going to have to tell me everything.
No matter how hard you try to kick your feet, there's nothing that you can prove.
It's a waste of time.
Even if it takes my whole life I'm going to make it happen.
You're wrongs with your own mouth.
Do you know how people who have nothing delude themselves?
You believe that there are things like truth and pity.
Don't be deluded. There aren't any such things.
Do you still not know?
Love or righteousness, strong people are the ones
who can protect those things.
That's why it turned out like this for us.
How did you turn out like this?
Hey, I'm not the only one who likes the shows.
I couldn't beat you.
Have you decided to be the defender of righteousness?
Or, have you become an informant
who betrayed the organization?
What are you talking about?
People were talking. It's also all over the news.
I told you, right? Min Hyeok is not such as easy person.
Whose side are you on, Sunbaenim?
It's Jo Min Hyeok who did wrong, not me.
If Min Hyeok did wrong, he should be punished.
But, it's not in my jurisdiction yet.
That woman just now,
she is that hit-and-run perpetrator, right?
Once my special prosecutions duties are over,
I'm going to ask the chief, and
I'll have to take your case.
Attorney Ahn Do Hoon who exposed K-Group's
wrongdoings, from the paper company that K-Group established in Hong Kong,
there is a suspicion that he embezzled $6.5 mil.
President Jo Min Hyeok who has become known
as K-Group's heir, at the interviews with the reporters today...
Have you been here?
It's high, eh?
It's perfect height for falling, too.
$6.5mil,
instead of my pocket,
it's money that went into your building.
Right.
But, there is no evidence.
Hyung is quite meticulous. He doesn't leave evidence.
And that two, it resembles you, Ahn Do Hoon.
Congratulations on your marriage.
Assemblyman Shin has even hit Se Yeon.
The person who made Se Yeon hurt like that
is none other than you.
I have nothing more to lose anyway.
Yoo Jeong told me
that the person who has more is supposed to worry more.
Jo Min Hyeok, don't you have more than me?
I wanted to take it away from you, but it's beyond me.
So, I want to lose together.
I have no intention of going with you, Attorney Ahn Do Hoon.
I'll admit to the $6.5 mil embezzlement, but for that
K-Group and Shin Ah Foundation, let's go down together.
Let the Chairman see the penitentiary,
then you, Se Yeon and even Assemblyman Shin,
would be busy going in and out of the Prosecutions Office.
To crumble because of you alone, Attorney Ahn,
our company is not that mediocre.
It's not just me.
People who got fed up with the actions
the Chaebols have been taking, I'll be with them.
So, what would you expect will change?
I thought you were smart, but
you're quite an idealist.
On the day of Seo Ji Hee's accident,
it wasn't Yoo Jeong, but
it was me who drove.
Would you like to record or something?
Or,
should I say it again?
It wasn't Yoo Jeong,
but it was me who killed her.
Yoo Jeong told me she would go to jail in my place.
I tried to discourage her, but it didn't work.
Ahn Do Hoon...
She's that kind of girl.
For such worthless love,
the person who would even give up her own life.
The file,
recording.
Do as you wish.
But I'm curious.
Your woman whom I could not protect,
if you can protect her with those things.
Don't touch Yoo Jeong.
I won't touch her.
As low as you fall,
because she'll be ruining herself.
Pitiful bastard.
What it is that you've lost, do you still not know?
Even though for once, you whom Kang Yoo Jeong loved,
I hoped, were not this kind of worthless human being.
Father.
Father!
It's dangerous for you to go, why are you being like this?
Then, lying down like this,
are you saying I should just keep watching you
take the company to the ground, boy?
Huh?
Father..
Father.
Alright.
since I abused it for over 60 years,
my body breaking down is rather normal.
I...
made as much money as I wanted, but
always,
I bowed to the power.
There is only one thing I want from you.
The power,
that you stand above it.
That's why
we need Assemblyman Shin, boy.
I'm not that great a punk, you know that well.
What I want to protect is
that woman.
Love?
It's good.
But,
as you go on living, it changes.
After time passes, all gets forgotten.
Your mom...
With a father who was addicted to gambling,
she was a daughter of an inn.
I brought her in for the debt, kept her by my side, and
built a small hotel for her.
That was the beginning of K-Hotel.
We were having an opening ceremony, and
she smiled brightly.
For me,
seeing her smile,
that was the last time.
Father!
Because of you, one person,
K-Hotel shaking,
I cannot allow that.
Not a desire as your father,
but as a person responsible for the company,
I'm asking you.
K-Hotel,
in place of me,
you protect it.
So that the cross that Gwang Min beared
was not done in vain.
I'm asking you.
I told you I would see you again.
Can you see?
The house is empty.
My daughter,
I sent her abroad, so that she doesn't freak out.
You saw the news, right?
If the marriage with Se Yeon breaks,
the company will become harder.
then, Min Hyeok won't be safe, either.
Investigations, trials, penitentiary!
Are you going to turn a person you love into a criminal,
like you?
Is that the way you love Min Hyeok?
Madam!
The Chairman
is in bad health.
If Min Hyeok also leaves, abandoning the company,
I guess it would become harder.
Min Hyeok, he is not someone who can abandon his father,
and continue to be happy with you.
You know that, right?
Do I need to speak more?
The boss...
He expresses more frustration when he is happy, and
when he is thankful, he expresses anger for no reason.
But...
When he is hurt, he doesn't show it.
He seems to be having a hard time because of his deceased mother.
Now...
You're his mother, right?
The boss,
I ask you to take care of him.
It's me.
Do you have time tomorrow?
Was the place you wanted to go with me,
here?
My dad...
I couldn't be by his side when he passed away.
How lonely he must have been,
when I think about it,
it hurts me a lot.
Because of the person I loved,
because of my desire,
I know because I have abandoned him.
How thoroughly regretful that is,
I know.
- Yoo Jeong?
So, how can I
tell you to abandon your father?
- Don't say.
Don't say anything.
Look at you even now.
You can't even say anything,
although it's hard for you.
It's not something you should worry about.
I've been to the restaurant.
Everyone is worried because
something might happen to the company.
Letting go of the company because of me,
to all those working employees believing in you,
it's a thing that you're sinning.
I can't tell you to do that.
I don't... want to live feeling sorry to people anymore.
What do they have to do with me?
I'm not that great of an ass!
It's hard enough just trying to protect my woman.
I don't like it. I said I don't like it!
I told you all I need is you by my side!
You... Don't say useless things.
Aish! I'm so annoyed!
I'm behind on interviews.
I'll make it short.
Gwang Soo.
The file and the recording,
destroy them.
Yoo Jeong?
Let's have fun with me.
Are you telling me to skip work?
Just today.
Then...
Let's have fun just for today.
♫ For me to have
♫ The person too precious
♫ I dare love that person
♫ To a bad guy like me
♫ Who is not suitable
♫ I love one person
♫ That person is you
♫ Even though I cannot say
♫ Hot enough to get burned
♫ The tears in my heart
♫ If I can pour it out to you
What did you scatter like that?
It's a secret.
♫ In the world where there is none
♫ I want to meet once again
♫ Hot enough to get burned
♫ The tears in my heart
♫ If I can pour it out to you
♫ My love
♫ Love or farewell
♫ In the world where there is none
♫ I want to meet once again
♫ My love
Dduckboki again? You know I can't eat spicy food.
Please try it.
Ah!
Oh, it's not spicy!
It tastes good.
I did a good job picking a right employee.
Forget about all worrisome things, and
should we live together at a place like this?
Should we?
Don't make a face like that.
Please smile!
Please leave it as a good memory today.
Boss...
Aren't we going back?
Yes, we should go back.
We
must have come too far.
It would be hard to go back.
But, I...
wish my whole life
was today.
Then, it wouldn't be fun.
Then...
Just until tomorrow, let's call it today.
Just until tomorrow.
♫ Like a fool, I
♫ Like a fool like this
♫ Laugh laugh then cry again
♫ How could our love hurt so much like this
♫ If the wind blew and swallowed my body
♫ Even if there were nothing,
I cannot live without you
♫ That I love you crazily
♫ That I miss you crazily
♫ As if my heart would explode
♫ That it's a love like a storm
♫ Only as far as I would let
♫ That it can be away
♫ Unstoppable by anyone
♫ My love which is like the fool is saying
♫ From your behind
♫ Holding you in my arms
♫ Cry cry again I cry
♫ If the wind blew
♫ And swallowed my body
♫ Even if there were nothing,
I cannot live without you
Can a person
live without love,
is it possible?
♫ As if my heart would explode
♫ That it's a love like the storm
♫ Only as far as I would let
♫ That it can be away
♫ Unstoppable by anyone
♫ My love which is like the fool
♫ Is calling you
Instead of answering, the grandfather
kept on drinking the peppermint tea,
which was supposed to be good for your health.
More.
It's up to here.
What did the old man say?
Is that all?
If you're curious,
after I leave,
please read it then.
I don't want to.
Read more before you go.
Because I have to look at the book,
I can't see your face.
For now, like this...
please let's stay like this just a little more.
What the grandfather said before he went senile
seems to be right.
A human being,
without a person to love,
cannot live.
♫ A person came into my life
♫ The person I should not love
♫ No I should not, no I should not
♫ I tried to turn away many times
I should love?
How?
Yoo Jeong,
this kind of thing is love?
When it hurts this much...
It hurts so much that I feel like I would go crazy.
This kind of thing is love?
It's love, is right.
When you think about that someone,
that it hurts, that it distresses you, is also love.
♫ Even though I say I'm hurt as if I could die
♫ I only watch
For me,
boss, you...
Min Hyeok, you...
so much,
hurt me.
♫ I believe that I love you
♫ If this limping love of mine
♫ If it moves near, because you might hide from fear
♫ Even though I say I'm hurt as if I could die
♫ I only watch
RET
SECRET
You haven't eaten yet, right?
Unni,
now, I
did the right thing, right?
Right?
Liking that person
doesn't make sense, right?
It's what should not be,
right?
That's why
for me, now
letting him go
is right,
huh?
Right.
What you're doing is all right.
Is it really right?
But, why do the tears keep coming out?
Not shedding any tears when you let a person go,
that would be more strange.
This dress...
Just shred it.
Have you any knowledge re $65M embezzlement?
We don't know anything about that.
All we know is that our son is doing a good deed.
Mother, where is Attorney Ahn Do Hoon?
Please. Just leave. Please!
- Just say something...
- No, we don't know anything.
Excuse me!
Ah, man. Seriously...
What is this all about?
I guess you really made Min Hyeok and that woman to split up.
Thank you.
Will you be...
satisfied with this?
I told you.
I must possess him, at least once.
Ms. Kang Yoo Jeong.
The business is booming thanks to you, Ms. Yoo Jeong.
It's regretful.
I'm thankful to you for the time I've spent here.
Still unwavering royal family.
Expected guests alone will surpass several thousands.
Yoo Jeong. Let's talk outside.
Why do I have to go outside?
Do Hoon Oppa will be here soon.
Get out. I'm saying to get out since there are customers.
Why? Are you worried that something will go wrong
with your attorney son?!
Listen to her. Seriously.
Then what about my dad?
What about my dad whose legs were both blistered from
wandering around the streets,
thanks to your amazing attorney son abandoning him?
Where do you get off talking about stuff that didn't even
happe...
You take her out of here. Our business is going to fail!
How can a thing that happened become non-existent?
Then make my dad come back to life!
Yoo Jeong, let's go outside and talk, please?
You can't believe it, can you?
That's right. I couldn't believe it either at first.
But, Mother, no
you used to extremely hate me calling you Mother, didn't you?
Ajummoni.
That's why I came to hear directly from Oppa's mouth.
Come. Come this way.
I heard you went to a tour office? Cancel the honeymoon
as I have no intention of going.
Se Yeon.
Is this fun for you?
I don't find this fun.
We didn't wed to have fun.
I have to change my clothes. Can you step outside, please?
Okay. Rest.
Even the married couple finishes when they divorce,
why act as if having been together for few years is a big deal?
Where do you get off trying to block the future
of someone's son?
Are you doing this as if killing someone itself was not enough?
Stop! Bringing out the past things!
How can killing someone become a "past thing"?
As you say. I'm sure killing someone doesn't become
a "past thing" because the time passes by.
The person who knows carries on like this here?
Do you still want to believe it that way?!
What? Don't say you didn't know.
That car was only titled as mine, but driving was done
by Oppa, always.
You remember the day after the accident.
I went to pick up the key [from him].
Wha-t are you saying?
You didn't understand?
Should I tell those people?
I let things slide and took into consideration thinking
what poor thing you are.
Where do you think this is to come and cause this ruckus!
You're gross. Grotesque!
I am grotesque?
Gee, I wonder how grotesque it is to kill someone in
a hit-and-run,
and make my dad pass away by abandoning?
How long do you suppose he'll be incarcerated?
I bet he'd stay in longer, won't he?
- Are you crazy?
- No.
I am more normal [clear minded] now then any other time.
What are you afraid of?
If this isn't true, then tell those people [journalists].
Won't you stop!
Why do I have to stop?
Everyone, I have something to say about
that amazing Attorney Ahn Do Hoon!
- Attorney Ahn! Have you something to say to the press?
Please take it outside.
You little wench!
Stop it. Stop it, I say!
Calm down, I say!
Why?!
San...
San... Aren't you going to see him?
San... Your son... Don't you want to see him?