Secret
Alright, hurry up and hit me once!
Isn't that why you followed me?
What bad luck is this
to meet you like this?
What if I hit you?
If I hit you, will San come back to life?
Then get hit! Get hit a hundred, a thousand times!
What are you talking about?
Take this!
Why are you like this?
Why are you doing this to me?
You need to get hit. Get hit.
San? What about?
Why is San coming back to life?
Why are you like this?
San...
he died.
"Always on my side"
Parole?
A kid who came in for theft
turned me in for some other thing.
As an additional punishment,
I would have to serve another 3 years, but
I was told I just had to stop your parole.
He said if I start a small incident,
he'll forget that it ever happened.
I just did what I was told.
Unni... Have you ever done anyone wrong?
You're really nice so
I didn't know about anything else, but
I said a problem could arise because of the baby.
He said okay.
He said they would take care of the aftermath.
It's the truth!
Stay comfortable when you're inside,
because when you come out,
it will become very uncomfortable
Try feeling the pain as much as me.
Try losing the most precious people,
without a chance to do anything.
How pathetically painful it is,
shouldn't you also feel it?
Hey, substitute driver!
Where are you going at this time of night?
Who did you meet with?
Do I have to answer even that?
What?
It's true that I have a debt, but
that doesn't mean I have an obligation
to report every single thing of my life.
Aigoo...
Are you running away?
Were you originally weak on alcohol?
Still, you shouldn't run away. As a man.
Unlike someone, I don't turn my back on a human life.
Kang Yoo Jeong, isn't she really thick-skinned?
The prosecutor who convicted her is right next to her, but
she didn't even flinch.
At that time, by chance... Was there another eyewitness?
Well, all investigative reports at that time,
we turned them over to the prosecution.
But, anyway,
the hit-and-run incident from 4 years ago, why...
Possibly... That lady you guaranteed identity for,
did she say something?
Right? Did she go to you and
say it was unfair to her?
If you remember anything, please give me a call.
Yes.
Wow, K-Group Legal Team Director...
Hold on,
I'm suddenly remembering something after seeing this, but
at that time someone who was either
a witness or a reference person came,
and showed his K-Group business card like you did, and
asked me to call if I found out anything.
Who is that?
Hold on. There's going to be something here.
Oh, yes. This one.
Let's see.
I'm sorry.
Jo Min Hyeok
RET
SECRET
It's troublesome, Proscut...no Attorney Ahn.
You have to apply through the courts first in order to review the record!
Lawyer Ahn!
Section Leader Kim.
You said your son just got into K-Construction, right?
I understood that his original wish was to get a post
at K-Hotel...
Then, please leave after you have looked.
The CCTV here is such an old model that
the quality of images aren't good.
Identifying the driver is beyond its limitation,
I barely obtained the numbers (license plate).
If I just find this car's black box, then
it seems that we may be able to find the barrel
the suspect is insisting about.
Prosecutor. If the driver of the oncoming vehicle
were to have been photographed on the blackbox,
the suspect won't be able to insist any more...
But this car is a rental.
It'll be hard to find right?
Ah Sunbaenim, you're here late.
Oh? What is someone who quit doing in someone else's office?
I came to see you, Sunbaenim.
The K-Group investigation case...
When are you going to detonate it?
Even if the world is running at LTE level speed,
can you switch sides this fast?
Since when did you become the K-Group spokesperson?
I have corrupt accounting information on Chae Gyeong Group.
- If you stop the K Group investigation then...
- Now you're even making deals, eh?
Your legal gown (Prosecutor's) suited you so well...
You must really like the money.
Be careful. There's price to be paid for exceptional treatment.
Although Min Hyeok appears to be a rich kid
born with silver spoon in his mouth,
taking after his dad, he has a scary side to him.
Yes, I will do my best.
You couldn't even sleep last night, why are you already here?
What could make you work so hard like this...
Drink it. You didn't even eat dinner yesterday.
Unni...our San...
If he had been born to a different mother,
who knows, he might still have been alive right now,
living happily.
You're saying things that don't make sense!
He's San because he came out of your stomach.
If he had been born to someone else he'd be a stranger.
What is wrong with you?
I miss our San!
Unni..unni!
Sunbae-nim!
Yes.
I'm wondering if you know about this...
Are you keeping Im Won Jin's vehicle's black box file separately?
Why are you asking about that all of a sudden?
I think I can use it as the evidential proof
for Assemblyman Shin and Chairman Jo's case.
The security team is safekeeping it, per Chairman's order.
Contact me if you need anything more.
Yes.
This is really nice.
What is it, so early in the morning?
Why are you acting like this?
This early in the morning, what could it be?
I do not have time to talk.
My gift,
did you like it?
You said before that since we are different since birth
that we could not become friends, right?
I think you're right, come to think of it.
Just because you can visit my house sporadically, don't be confused.
K-Group
is mine in the end.
Don't be looking for Se Yeon either.
Guys who can't take care of their own women
always covet other guys' women.
Do a good job today.
At least for my company.
Good morning!
I'm sorry.
Because of some business with the art center I am a bit late.
Let's get going.
Yes.
You left like that before. How could you not contact me after that?
You,
why didn't you do it?
Please give this to the President.
Please take good care of it.
Excuse me, President! Some woman left this for you.
This is combined earnings from prison labor income,
and condolence money from my father's funeral.
I will work harder and save more,
I'll repay you as quickly as possible.
Where did she go?
She went that way.
Substitute driver!
Yes?
Substitute, you're pretty ballsy.
You're in debt to me and yet you avoid my calls?
I picked up, didn't I?
Well that's that.
But this,
what are you going to do by sending this piddly pin money?
Then I'll give it to you monthly.
Never mind that.
I will decide again what the contract content should be.
I never said I'll accept what you've decided.
Come to the hotel tomorrow.
Why don't you answer?
Tomorrow is an important day. I won't have time to come.
You dare to disobey my order?
I am sorry.
I can't cancel tomorrow's schedule no matter what.
I will hang up now.
Tomorrow's schedule...
Aye she hung up the phone.
Gwang Soo.
Gwang Soo!
Yes?
What's Kang Yoo Jeong's schedule for tomorrow?
Did she get a new part time job?
100% domestic, uh,
fresh,
fish just came in.
President! (calling man of certain age in a flattering way) Unni!
Come in and see.
Gunner, Mackerel and Gar, we have it all.
It's fresh right now.
You should take it when it's good.
What is she doing?
Since when has she been doing this?
I believe she's come to visit several times after she got out of the prison.
It's not really good.
No it's not. It's pretty fat.
So why am I only finding out about this now??
You told me to stop watching Kang Yoo Jeong.
Since when did you start listening to me?
Aunty!
These are nice and fat and delicious!
They're 100% fresh from the sea!
Unni, pretty Unni! These-these..
No?
Please come next time.
Goodbye.
Sir, would you like to buy some fish?
I'm busy.
Uhh... I'm okay.
I said I don't want to see your face. Why do find your way here and hurt me?
Let me take care of it.
Ahh, just get lost will you!
I will do it.
Take it and eat it.
Omo-nii, I will eat well!
Thank you. I will come back later!
Why are you here?
You wench. You don't even go home and hang around
here every chance you get.
What good is it to work bone-crushingly?
A huge chunk is going towards paying for monthly rent.
How can I save any money?
Is it worth living here?
This- who are you speaking informally to?!
Give you a little latitude and you start to talking informally?!
It's the president, Unni. Our President.
Ayy, get off. He's president to you, but hat doesn't make him president to me.
What are you looking at?
Ommo, why are you doing?
Oh, excuse us. She's actually a quite nice and pure girl
at heart, like soft tofu.
I am glad to meet you.
I am Sandara Park.
Oh my. Your eyes are so clear. Are you married?
Hey! Hey! Hey!
You're going to get hurt again.
Someone you know?
Oh, yes. Here,
let's have dinner together! Let's eat together.
Unni, I told you he's THE President.
Our President doesn't eat things like that.
How great of a trap is that, that it can't taste delicious food like this?
How could you, Grace Lee?
Oh, I am sorry.
Um, don't decline and come and share the meal with us.
Please have a seat.
This child's heart is like soft tofu soup but
she's practicing informal speech.
Please start.
Oh my, where is this fish from? It looks delicious!
And put it in the soup like this, and
I will apologise for that. Please accept this.
Please open your mouth.
Yes, yes.
Have a seat.
Let's eat. We have to eat to live anyway.
I guess you didn't know Yoo Jeong Unni can't stomach
going near fishy smell.
She only likes sweets and is a subtly picky eater.
Would you like to have a cup?
Me, too!
Right, here.
Let's have a toast-
Cheers!
Come in if you have something to say.
What is it this time?
How could you sell the fishes if you hate the smell so much?
You are quite shameless.
How could you think to go there?
The fact that I had a child,
you know that, right?
When I was in jail I had my child taken from me.
My child, while he was dying, I couldn't even see him.
They said he was in a lot of pain. I couldn't even hug him.
Losing my child after a only few years with him hurt this much,
how hard it must have been for So Ji Hee's mother.
I am forever indebted to her.
The fact that time cannot turn back what I did wrong, I know.
But still-
still as much as I want to avoid it,
I can't run away.
President!
This is too much to accomplish with my meager earnings.
Then you shouldn't have owed any money in the first place.
You said you aren't going to run away.
So why act nice?
Are you going to cry again?
Don't cry.
I don't want to see your thankful tears.
Hey, man.
Gwang Soo.
Seeing substitute driver hurting, why do I hurt more?!
I am Lawyer Ahn.
Yes.
Why isn't this working?
No?
Yes, it's strange.
Wait here for a bit.
Yes.
Sir.
Would you like some coffee?
Yes, thank you.
What are you doing
this late at night?
I don't have any reason to report my off-duty
activities to you, President.
I know that expression.
"I will not work at the company."
and "I've been caught." It's that kind of expression, right?
Is it because it's already been over 4 years?
I shouldn't know, but I think I know too much.
You'll be quite surprised to know how much I know.
Then what should we do?
I don't know anything about you, President.
Ah, not including one thing-
That without your father, you are nothing.
I know that one thing.
I crossed a patch of thin ice.
What would happen if the ice cracked?
What would happen to my parents who are watching me fall through the ice?
I shake uncontrollably and wonder if I could ever go back.
I came this far after crawling here one step at a time.
But how did the President,
no, Jo Min Hyeok come this far?
Marriage?
Is that why you're using Se Yeon like that?
You said Se Yeon was your friend?
Then please don't do that...to a friend.
Yes, I'll check it for you right away.
Your phone continues to be busy, so...
I will call you again. Yes.
What brings you here?
I need confirmation regarding art item dealings between
Shin La Gallery and K Group.
Ah, yes.
Is this painting worth that?
Worth isn't absolute.
The moment Chairman decides to purchase,
the painting becomes worthy.
I guess people are like that too.
Depending on the perspective of the observer,
one can be an amazing
or a useless person.
I know that you're not doing this because you want to.
These are all detailed statements of superiors' dealings.
Those dealings are what I've accomplished in the end.
It doesn't matter.
Even if a problem arises, I won't let it hurt you.
Read this.
A revenge that began because of a person,
how does it end?
Kwang Soo.
Do you still believe that there is love?
Yes.
Why?
Rather than there being none,
isn't it better if there is?
I saw the file nicely.
Tomorrow morning I have to see the police, so
I'll leave first.
I don't know anything about the President.
Except one thing.
That you're nothing without your father.
So that's why you're using Se Yeon like that.
I heard you're Se Yeon's friend.
Ahh. I'm annoyed.
The hotel (share quality) rating starts from today on.
Before the panel of assessors arrive this afternoon...
Why are you looking at me like that?
Our marriage, you said it was a business marriage.
Do you really think like that?
Yes, it's a business.
We even wrote a contract.
It looks good.
Even in the morning, you working for my company. It looks very good.
But, where are you going so hurriedly?
You should report to me since this is during the hours of "duty".
In order for the Chairman to not be in a wheelchair,
I am working. Very busily.
From when did you take care of my father's health?
The Chairman has to be healthy
so that the President will have a light heart.
Stop it.
Min Hyeok. Why are you being like this?
In front of me,
don't take someone else's side, Se Yeon.
Then.
That bastard,
you said is your friend?
He's also my friend.
You're going to find out soon.
Lawyer Ahn,
whether he's a good friend or
a bad friend.
Se Yeon, look at this.
There wasn't one before, but
it bloomed. I wondered where the scent came from.
Isn't it very pretty?
They call this a gisaeng (courtesan) orchid.
I thought it was called a giseng flower because it was pretty.
Look, it has no leaves.
Only a flower hanging.
They called it a gisaeng (also can be parasite)
because it can only survive by sticking to something.
It's just like me isn't it?
Se Yeon,
show Min Hyeok your soft side too.
You're too pretty and smart.
Guys, when a woman is better than men,
don't like it.
I don't care.
Whether he likes me or not,
he's still going to marry me.
Oh, it's coming.
Please eat well.
Yes.
Oh!
Honey! Look!
It's Do Hoon! Oh my!
Oh, he looks so handsome.
Omo omo omo...
look how handsome he looks.
Hello! Please come in.
Have you ever seen any rich asses getting arrested for anything?
So called intellectual and wealthy are all the same punks.
I guess he uses the good brain for lying.
What does it matter that they studied a lot?
Just drink.
Owner! One more ramyeon noodles over here, please.
Okay.
There's a rumor that K Group has made political contributions
through Shin La Gallery, is that true?
That's a rumor without facts.
Shin Hwa Gallery is a nonprofit organization
that works towards raising tomorrow's new artistic talent
of the nation of Korea,
and has no involvement with political funding.
In order to shed this kind of doubt, we in K Group,
will provide full cooperation to the Prosecution's investigation.
If there were to be any suspicion,
I will come here accompanying the Chairman myself.
Thank you.
Hello?
What is this that Hye Ri invited us here.
I might have to live in your house so
I have to buy food at least once.
I'll eat well, Hye Ri.
This is too stiff, I want something soft.
Please eat this.
I'll get you some more, customer.
Okay. I need some soup! Bring the soup!
You know to bring our hae jang? (hangover cure soup)
Hye Ri.
I saw that there was a sign up front looking for workers.
Oh yes, there is a vacant spot.
That's great, Wait. No, come with me.
Boss,
have you recruited someone yet?
Why?
This unni is a god at part-time jobs.
She has done every service job.
She's the multitasking queen!
Really, your name is...
Kang Yoo Jeong.
Do you have experience?
Yes. From when I was in high school, I worked at fast-food restaurants,
hotel buffet, korean restaurants, coffee shops, restaurants.
Okay.
Then, I'll trust Hye Ri and hire you for a week first.
Yes. Thank you. I'll work hard.
Deposit made by Substitute: $160, $144.70, $184.30.
Unnie, your mother would be happy if you bought these for her.
These are really fresh.
Come again next time!
Mother, these mackerels! These mackerels are fresh, fat and delicious!
You thought you would be forgiven if you do that?
What about that?
Are you sure that the assailant
simply turned back and left despite having seen
Ji0 Hee collapsed?
That's what the evidence showed.
You can see that there were footprints of someone around
(the accident site) who came and then went away.
Are you sure that it's her footsteps?
Though we can't confirm the size and shape for sure,
the fact that (assailant) recognized the victim's situation
gives proof and lays guilt to the assailant.
So, it is possible that it's not this girl's footsteps.
Hey, why do you keep bringing up the already concluded case?
Even Attorney Ahn came to check that file not too long ago.
Who?
Prosecutor Ahn.
Ahn Do Hoon?
Why? Is there something?
Even though they'll continue with the investigation,
even the Prosecution won't be able to attack openly.
However, it'll behoove us to be more careful of incidents
that may cause rumors to fly.
Rumors?
The thing that represents the most danger to K Group
isn't the Prosecution, but President Jo Min Hyeok.
Attorney Ahn Do Hoon!
Speak on.
The opinions of board of directors about President
Jo Min Hyeok is less than friendly.
The deteriorating hotel operation has already surfaced,
and there is a limit to what Shin Se Yeon can block.
They (directors) know best about your deteriorating health, Chairman.
Attorney Ahn! What is this nonsense?
You know better than anyone as to how many times
the Chairman traveled to Germany, Sunbae.
At first, I investigated it thinking that (the trips) were
related to investments overseas.
But they weren't.
Chairman. What is your ailment and how serious is it?
President Jo Min Hyeok has a long way to go before
he can solidify his position as K Group successor.
Min Hyeok is in his room, correct?
I believe his schedule today starts in the afternoon.
Take Attorney Ahn to him.
Why don't you talk some sense into him.
Your pride's got to be wounded to become strong.
Since he's due to come in soon, wait a bit.
Yes.
Don't spew whatever comes to your mind,
but always watch your mouth.
Maybe it's because it's already been four years.
I think there's a lot I know about you, Attorney Ahn.
If you find out, just how much I know, you're going
to be really surprised, Attorney Ahn.
I wonder what he's doing in a room without an owner?
What happened to the difference (proceeds) after
selling off the Icheon Hotel's ballooned share price?
There's information that you've suppressed the labor union in Jaeik Hotel
despite the recommendation of the Regional Labor Union Committee.
This can lead to suspension of business,
are you at least aware of it?
Isn't that why I hired you, to take care of matters like that?
This is the kind of incident that can determine several thousands' livelihood.
- You should look at it with bit more sincerity.
- Who the hell are you to lecture?
I think you're blind to this mistaken reality of yours.
The person who knows better than anyone
(about people's livelihood), is me, the President.
All you have to do is to do what you're told, Attorney Ahn.
I understand.
As for Ms. Kang Yoo Jeong,
she's someone I loved at one point.
So don't treat her cavalierly.
I'm not sure what plan you're devising with Yoo Jeong,
but there won't be a second time that I would become your fiddle.
The hit-and-run from 4 years ago,
I wonder what bothered you so much that
you'd review the investigation record again?
Please get ready, the Chairman is waiting.
I got it.
Shouldn't I be the one to pour for you?
It's thanks to you our stock rating passed without problems.
It's fine if you know.
There's going to be a party, will you come?
I will think about it.
Se Yeon.
If I were to have killed someone
and had to go to prison, what would you do?
I would select the best lawyer.
I would block (your jail sentence) by meeting up with
the prosecutor, the judge, if not them then even
the supreme court justice.
And if I still had to go to jail?
You wouldn't go to jail, I told you I wouldn't let you.
Substitute Driver deposited $164.30 (into your account).
Ah man, this little...
Recipient: K Group Board of Directors
Do Hoon.
What are you doing here?
We're friends, right?
Yes.
Is it okay to ask a favor of a friend?
Can you make time next Wednesday for me?
It's because of the party Mr. Jo Min Hyeok is hosting, right?
Yes.
Okay.
Instead, tell me the reason.
Is it to get interest from Jo Min Hyeok again,
or is it because you actually want to go with me?
- That's of course because of Min Hyeok...
- I'll go with you.
I heard your answer.
You did a good job, Prosecutor Ahn.
I didn't know you were going to handle it this well.
Set aside your personal feelings and judge
the incident based on letter of the law only.
Please believe me. There was no person.
I didn't see anyone.
That, on that rainy road,
A truck suddenly popped out and my car slipped. We,
No, I...
I only hit a barrel that was around the construction site. That's all.
There's no way that could have happened.
I didn't know. No
I didn't hit a person.
Though we can't know for sure the assailant's
size or shape,
they did discover the footprints that came and returned
near the body.
So this may not be a woman's footprints, you're saying?
No.
I don't think that I've paid my debt.
Forever...
I will never forget it forever. How could I forget it?
My embarrassment
is nothing compared to that dead woman.
Kwang Soo.
Yes.
Find out about it.
Is this how your going to pay me back this month?
I'm trying to pay you back, so I'm working.
Don't bother me if you want to be paid.
What are you doing?
On the day of the accident,
you said that you left even after seeing the body.
Did you really see the body and leave?!
Yes. I did it.
What do want?
After bothering me for so many years,
isn't it enough now?
With this kind of work, how are you going to pay me back?
Even you don't want to see me anymore.
Put this on her.
I'll take you to the other side.
Uhhh,
I...
I told you that if you do as your told today that I would cut your debt.
Driver.
I'm sorry.
It's alright.
The design is cheap.
Change her into this.
That's good.
Ahh.
I remember now. Was it four years ago?
Please tell me more precisely.
Woo!
Why are you like this, without Min Hyeok?
Introduce yourself. This is the lawyer for K-Group.
What is this?
Are you guys playing partner changing games?
Who is that girl?
She is someone you should not pay attention to.
In order to pay her debt to Min Hyeok,
she will do anything for him, I heard.
Se Yeon.
What are you doing. To what extent are you going to go?
No.
I thought you weren't coming today.
So,
did you bring her because you thought I wasn't coming?
No, it's not like that.
I never said I wasn't coming here.
When you asked me,
I said that I would think about it.
Why are you like this?
The toy that person plays with,
I said that I could do it.
I didn't know that you would be here.
If I hadn't been here...
Would you just follow along because he says? And what about your getup?
I couldn't do anything. President forced me to...
If he asked you to,
would you sell your body?
I'm sorry.
Are you alright?
Yes. Thank you.
How much?
Yes?
I heard that since your in debt with Min Hyeok,
you do anything you're asked to do.
That debt, I'll pay for it.
Then, the things that I ask for...
It's not like that.
Then,
you're alright.
You're charming.
Are your crazy?
Come here!
Stay still.
Hey!
Hey! Come here!
Hey! You!
What is this?
She's an inferior good.
Get up.
What is this, Min Hyeok?
That girl is cheap.
What is this?
I heard that if you give her money, she'll do anything.
What are you to act like you're all that?
Buy yourself some clothes.
Hey, is there a scar here?
She does do everything she is asked to do.
Me.
She can only do what I say.
What?
Hey!
What happened? Where's Kwang Soo?
I don't know.
Yes?
What? What do you mean a meeting at this time?
What? A meeting?
What? Ahh!
Min Hyeok. I can pass one time but never twice.
Watch me.
You. I won't let you go.
Wait for me.
See you again, you inferior thing.
Yes.
They came together.
He remembered clearly because they had a proposing event.
When was that?
It was that day.
Are your sure?
Yes. It was the day of Ji Hee's accident.
Poor operation.
Increased vacancy due to group reservation cancellation.
Irregularity of share sales regarding Icheon Hotel and etc.
I recommend President Jo Min Hyeok's dismissal.
With the shares that I have,
I think I have the qualifications to join this meeting.
What?
The shareholders arranged this meeting.
These people.
How many people are there to oppose it?
The people who'd veto the recommended article
are more than half based on your influence.
Get them all on the line.
The meeting about Min Hyeok,
let's start it now.
Then, we will
start to count the vote on the issue of President Jo Min Hyeok's dismissal.
Please raise your hand for "yay"s.
Let's go.
What are you?
What the hell did you do?!