Secret
I don't remember the way home.
Now take me to Yoo Jeong.
Yoo Jeong is waiting.
Did you remember that?
Why shouldn't I? You're the one who drove.
You're blaming it on Yoo Jeong. Do you think I wouldn't know that?
Substitute.
Kang Yoo Jeong.
Substitute!
♫ Would it be alright if I move closer
♫ I was scared so I stood still
Driver.
♫ I wonder if we really had to meet
What are you doing?
♫ Because an unerasable scar hurts
♫ Would I be able to tell you again that
I love you
♫ No matter how many times I let you go,
you're still the one
♫ No matter how hard I try to erase you,
like an incurable disease
♫ Spreading inside of me
♫ I just can't stop this love
Why are you here at this time?
What happened, Do Hoon?
I'll make you some tea.
Wait.
Please just stay like this for a second.
Secret Episode 11
I'm sorry.
You always...
come inside my building and cry.
I'm sorry.
What is it this time?
Towards you...
I am sorry.
To see loved ones pass...
I know it doesn't happen only to me...
Because my dad,
my San, I sent them away like that...
and I feel so shameless being alive by myself.
So how disgusting would I
be to you?
That's fine if you know.
That helped me, too.
I'm not brave enough to die along side Ji Hee
but I found you
and hated you to death
to withstand it all.
You should
withstand it while watching me.
What's making it so difficult for you, Do Hoon?
People.
I became a prosecutor through another's sacrifice.
I came up here without anything in my hand.
But...
people on top are always predetermined.
I gave up everything and came up here,
but those who sacrificed are in my way.
Those who are up here aren't any different.
You would think it's luxury,
but I give up a lot, too, trying to live up to my parents' expectations. If you know that...
I know.
We both gave up, but
we began with different things in our hands.
Since when was the world fair?
It isn't fair.
But if you end it just complaining about it, you're the one that is foolish.
Thank you
for your advice.
It's not advice.
I'm just encouraging you to not give up.
Hi.
It's time to go check restaurant #43.
I know.
Gwang Soo,
how do you think she is doing right now?
How...?
Is there something wrong?
No, it's fine.
Let's go.
You can't see me relax on my one day off...
Please, Hye Ri, just for today.
I will take your place next time whenever you want to take off.
Anyway, is there something wrong? What's wrong with your face?
You didn't even come home last night.
Forget it.
I'm going.
Thank you.
Turn the car around to Hapjoong-dong.
I'm worried about Kang Yoo Jeong
Did something happen?
She acts like nothing happened.
That's why it's weird.
I...
saw someone like that before...
Anyway, I'm worried, so turn the car around and go back.
Okay.
Manager. Yes, Boss.
Hello.
I don't see Kang Yoo Jeong.
She said she has some emergency, so she switched shifts with Hye Ri.
Where is Kang Yoo Jeong?
Ahh...that...I'm not very sure.
You don't know? Does that make sense?
I asked but she didn't reply.
She only asked me to switch shifts.
It's written here. This is our phone number.
When the patient is missing, they contact us
from where he was first missing.
My father had this bracelet, too.
But...
it was missing...
You can't take this off by yourself.
Look at this.
By any chance, can you check whether there was a call?
If there was, we would have contacted you already.
The guardian is Ahn Do Hoon, right?
You can go first.
What's up?
I don't have a reason to see you.
I have.
Let's go out.
I don't have time. I have to attend the meeting.
This is more important than the meeting.
Go out!
Director, are you ok?
I said I have something to say.
Take her out.
Oppa.
Hurry!
Oppa! Oppa!
Oppa!
I said she's not here! Why don't you believe me?!
So where is she?
I wanted to ask you the same thing.
She went to work but why hasn't been back for 2 days?
What happened to Kang Yoo Jeong?
You know where she is.
Maybe she hid somewhere because something happened.
She has so many things going on already,
can't you just leave her alone?
What do you think you're doing?
When I went to Pohang to find my dad...
his bracelet was missing.
The bracelet...
Didn't you say it's not something that can be taken off by yourself?
Why are you asking me this?
Because that day...
you saw my dad.
No?
Yes, I saw him.
He got in the car.
But he kept trying to get out.
I stopped the car on the shoulder to avoid an accident,
but he just ran out of the car.
Lies.
It was raining and there were a lot of people so I couldn't find him.
So, you want to blame me?
Lies.
So what if I'm lying?
Yes, so what if I threw out your dad? So what?!
The one who couldn't take care of your dad is you.
You're the one who didn't agree to send him to a nursing home!
It was for your greed and your satisfaction!
My dad...
He trusted you.
Yes. Yes, and I'm sick of that.
So? So what if I didn't go after him? So what?!
Stop the car.
Stop it!
I said stop the car!
Are you crazy?
What if an accident happened?!
Why did you do it?
How could you do that to me?
To my dad?!
Because you were sick of it,
is that why you took San away, too?
Is that why you took him away...
and left him to die?
What are you talking about?
You really did go crazy.
Get out.
How can I not go crazy?
How could you act so normal, Oppa?
Kneel down!
To San...
To my dad, apologize to them!
Kneel down and beg!
If I kneel down...
If I apologize...
Will you disappear?
I don't want to live looking back anymore.
You're there at the end, in the back.
You're holding on to me, it's disgusting!
Disgusting?
Me?
I was arrogant when I said
I could make you happy.
You said you don't regret it?
I regret it!!!
That day!
The day when you said you would go in place of me.
If I had left you then,
I wouldn't be regretting it now.
Regrets...
you will start from this moment.
Till you rip your heart out with regret,
and I will make it happen.
Watch it carefully!
So that you never forget me,
my San,
my father who thought of you as his own son!
I'll make it so that you can never forget!
Disappear from you?
Don't even dream about it.
Wherever you go, I will be there.
You will see me until you're sick to death!
Don't think about running away.
Why did you come?
I would like to be... by your side, Boss.
Why?
Because I have something I should do.
There is something I must do.
Without even knowing the reason,
did you think I would help you?
As you want, President...
I will not live a happy life.
The most miserable life possible,
I'll live like that for you.
I am asking you.
Why should I help you?
Is it because of Ahn Do Hoon?
What is this?
What about the time when you protected him,
as if you would die in his place,
suddenly why?
What I can do for those people I lost,
because this is the only way.
Even though I can't get back
what was taken away from me,
I have something I must receive.
Director Ahn Do Hoon
I will make it so that...
Your heart is torn with regret.
Watch carefully.
So that you can't erase me
my son San, and my dad who thought of you like a son.
I'll make it so you can never forget.
This time too
If you do that again, I won't let it slide.
Okay, Son-in law?
Wherever you go, I'll be there.
So you'll disgustingly see me!
I will not regret.
I will not
look back anymore.
Yoo Jeong.
Ahn Do Hoon crumbling
is something I've wanted as well.
Why bother choosing a difficult way?
Wouldn't kicking him out of K Group solve the problem?
Were you
satisfied
because you took it all away from me, Deputy Head?
If you take things away so easily,
you won't comprehend how precious the things
you've taken away are.
Then,
what is the reason you need me?
Because you...
you make Do Hoon Oppa more tenacious.
That way I'll not weaken.
"Give me one more chance." "Think of our past."
So that I'll not be shaken by such words.
Ahn Do Hoon,
what did he do to you?
Gwang Soo...
Use whatever method necessary
to find out what Kang Yoo Jeong did and who she met with
for the past week.
Unni.
Is there anything to eat?
You come home for the first time in 2 days, and
all you can say is "Rice"?
Whatever happened, you should say something!
I'm hungry.
I think I need to eat a bit.
I need energy to work, don't I?
I made some yellow bean stew.
Follow me...
Until the end of the second half this year,
we plan on completing the projects for
in-country and overseas hotels.
During the slow season, hotel bidding system,
the first in Korea...
I get the data, too.
Then what did you call me
all the way over here for?
It seems you're curious.
Since I'm not good at twisting the words around,
What happened between you and Kang Yoo Jeong?
What did you do and how,
for Kang Yoo Jeong to turn around like that?
If you have nothing work related to discuss, I'll be going.
Lawyer Ahn.
You too were there on the day of the accident.
For the two of you who shares a secret like the life itself,
why you both ended up being so against each other,
I'm so curious, I'm about to go crazy.
Neither of you are telling.
Gwang Soo?
Yes.
Are you checking it out?
The blackbox video will be restored soon.
Okay.
I'll see you at the Board Meeting.
Oh,
At the Board Meeting, Se Yeon is also coming, right?
Does Se Yeon know about the relationship
between you and Kang Yoo Jeong?
My warning that you shouldn't be seeing Se Yeon,
don't forget it.
At King's Restaurant, the person who is assisting me with revenue growth and for new leaps,
I would like to introduce to you my partner.
I'm Kang Yoo Jeong.
Since when, enough for you to be able to attend the meeting,
were you promoted?
The Boss isn't yet familiar with the restaurant's menu,
so I came with him.
Please don't misunderstand.
You said that last time as well.
But what to do?
He keeps misunderstanding.
What is the real reason you keep sticking to Min Hyeok?
Please excuse me.
Miss Kang Yoo Jeong, what you said to me...
This is it?
To use Jo Min Hyeok to get a promotion in your status?
Mr Attorney, didn't you get up there like that, too?
It isn't different from the reason you
have Ahn Do Hoon by your side.
I also need someone by my side.
You really are going crazy.
You even know what kind of woman she is.
And if you knew what kind of man Lawyer Ahn was,
it would be different.
Let's go, Substitute.
Come to work at my house tomorrow.
Again?
I told you not to talk back to me.
Yes.
Is this much enough?
In front of Ahn Do Hoon,
be more confident.
Yes.
Thank you.
What do those two think they are doing?
At least those two together...
succeeded in getting your attention Se Yeon.
It bothers me.
If you want, Se Yeon, I can
split those two apart.
What is this?
K Group Chairman Jo rumored in critical condition.
His secret departure to Germany revealed...
K Group, K Construction's unreasonable building
leads to negative fund turnover ratio.
How do I stop the articles?
What's this?
These people all blab that they know everything,
so how come this is the first time I'm hearing about it?!
When will Father return?
Using Director Im and my name, we've planned to get
a $20M credit loan from K Capital.
First, we must stabilize the share price...
What about Father? What does he say?
Why did he go to Germany?
Why did he go?!
We can't let the Chairman know.
We made it so no one can contact him during the surgery period.
Surgery?
What I don't even know as a son,
the rumer sites are letting me know!
While Chairman isn't here, the head of K Group is you!
The person who knows that didn't think to TELL ME ANYTHING?!
K Hotel...
Start purchasing K Hotel shares first.
It was father's first business.
How's Father's condition?
We'll get notified soon.
You must return to the Hotel immediately.
Prove that you lack nothing as the successor.
Is this why Father said
we must make the restaurant business successful?
Chairman and K Group won't collapse that easily.
Hyung.
No matter how trivial, report it all to me.
Kang Yoo Jeong is the one who...
killed the woman Min Hyeok loved.
Knowing that and staying by her side...
Despicable, those two.
I thought I knew Min Hyeok..
But these days, I don't know anymore.
The obsession over that woman...
That reminds me of dead Seo Ji Hee.
Didn't you come because you had something to say?
Yes.
I said before that...
...there was a woman I loved, right?
So the woman I wanted to be with...
was Kang Yoo Jeong.
Do Hoon...
I didn't want to hear anything from other people.
Did it not occur to you that you were pretending
not to know that girl in front of Min Hyeok and I?!
Jo Min Hyeok already knew.
The three of you have, at this very moment,
made me into a fool.
It wasn't intended, but
having lied to you as a result...
made me distressed.
I'm sorry.
You are "sorry".
You say it so easily.
I didn't know it'd turn out like this.
With Yoo Jeong, it was already over.
I also can't [stand] the wicked things Jo Min Hyeok is doing to her...
You're just the same.
All men are the same.
I was a bit strange to hope that you were different.
Se Yeon.
Isn't it enough that I've gone along with it while it lasted?
Don't give your excuses.
Since you didn't want to hear anything from anyone anyway.
Let's drink this that I made.
Oh~ It's hot.
Do you remember what you said when we didn't have
any work to do,
and we were in the room all day?
What was that?
If you bear it, 1 minute becomes 1 hour,
1 hour become a month.
Even if you don't fret, the thing that passes is time.
That's how we talked about ourselves...
Hey, when they say how they were in their olden days,
it's all lies.
Those are all stories to pass time.
Even then I
thought about how I would live in the future.
I thought recalling what happened in the past
was a foolish thing.
Thinking about my father and San...
Hey, don't think strange thoughts.
Wasting life living as you hate others,
that is the most unworthy thing.
In this world,
there are too many people who don't get punished
even though they did wrong.
It's strange, isn't it?
It's unfair.
Unni!
Come and eat Ddeok Bokki. It's all done.
(Spicy boiled rice cake - typical, cheap Korean snack).
So what is the real nature of your relationship with our President, huh?
Well, it's just that, you got dumped by Do Hoon Oppa, and...
Since it's come to this, just grab onto him.
Hey! This bitch...
You are really too much of a "direct narration".
Yoo Jeong, didn't you say that President will get married soon, no?
The woman having an affair with a married man,
is an illegitimate existence.
Illegitimate?
For someone who knows the law so well,
why did you have an affair
with the president of your business partner?
Hey! Nasty!
He could live without the stars or the moon,
but he said he couldn't live without me!
We love each other so much, we do!
Alright that's that. But it's not for you.
Getting involved with a matter that's not good can't end well, understand?
Aiyoo, why? It's not like matchmaking animals.
Would a real marriage be done like that?
And, the boss doesn't seem interested in that woman anyway.
Oh, really?
Don't worry. There's nothing like that.
Hey, you really know how to deny things!
Then what's the reason that you're with the Boss?
It's because you have feelings, too.
Hey, hey! Your mouth is the only thing alive!
Hey, why does ddeokbokki taste like this?
Is this ddeokbokki? Go make another one.
Hurry, make another one.
Just bring some sugar.
- Sugar only?
There was a woman who came to see Kang Yoo Jeong.
Lee Hye Jin, she served with Kang Yoo Jeong
at the same correctional facility.
And?
Kang Yoo Jeong's child,
the person who reported his abuse is this woman.
Three days ago, Lee Ja Young who lives together,
went and got the CCTV footage,
which was at a location nearby the bakery.
Bakery? When?
It was a CCTV for traffic control. They said they took
the footage of the day when her dad went missing.
The child and the father...
Find this woman. Find her no matter what.
Also, the CCTV, find it and bring it to me.
Yes.
I had a woman whom I loved.
That woman was Kang Yoo Jeong.
What's the real reason that you're stuck
by Min Hyeok's side?
It isn't different from the reason you
have Ahn Do Hoon by your side.
I also need someone by my side.
Thinking of you as a woman who killed someone...
As I get to know you you're more incredible.
I heard you and Do Hoon used to date.
What are you planning between the two men?
I'm sorry for worrying you.
A person who's supposed to be sorry comes into the house?
I have something I must do.
The debt that I have to pay back to the Boss,
and the debt that I have to receive from Ahn Do Hoon.
So,
you're sorry but you'll still stick by him?
Yes.
Do that then.
Because taking out a slug is not even work.
So, you want to fold this business that is making money?
Segwang is showing interest in the King's Restaurant.
Out of all K-Group's affiliates,
the one that can be liquidated for cash is
only this place.
This place... you want to hand it over to Segwang?
Who is it that you're supposed to be
working for?
With only the growth rate we have shown,
the investment amount that the Chairman wants,
it won't be approved by the Board of Directors.
Since when did I need you guys' approval?
The number of K-Hotel shares you own
does not surpass the number of shares
owned by the Board and Shin Se Yeon. All decisions
will be determined by the Board.
How is it?
I figured you wouldn't have the time
to come and see the paintings, so I came to hang them up for you.
She was audacious.
She has something to pay back to Min Hyeok, and
from you Do Hoon,
she has something to receive.
Perhaps...do you still have lingering feelings
for that woman?
No, I don't.
Are you sincere about wanting to
forget Kang Yoo Jeong?
Yes. I've forgotten.
Then that's fine.
Because the past has no strength anyway.
These two people,
you said you could split them up, right?
Please do it.
For telling me first about that woman,
for keeping your courtesy to me,
thank you.
It's suspicious...you coming in at 3 in the morning.
I had work to do.
That's why. What work did you have that
you worked so hard?
Work to help feed and shelter us.
At a restaurant.
You're going home with me tonight, right?
I can't, I have a lot to do.
It's good that you're making progress with the boss, but
a woman loses her charm if she's too easy.
You know, right?
Hye Ri?
- Yes. You know? Right?
Since when the Board of Directors
could not wait to sell a profitable subsidiary? To Segwang at that!
This meeting here,
I understand you do not have the right to attend.
What?
Since you have been dismissed,
you cannot attend internal meetings.
Close the door.
Let me go!
Please take him outside.
Let go!
Ahn Do Hoon!
I'm Jo Min Hyeok! This company's owner is me!
The result of the Board meeting,
what happened?
You always seem to look for me at times like this.
The shares you own, liquidate it and invest in me.
For what merit of yours?
You said we're not even friends now.
What is your value as a collateral?
This kind of crisis, we've had it more than once or twice,
it's going to pass anyway.
If father returns and finds you like this,
I'll have something to say at that time.
Putting aside a woman you'll be marrying, and
taking another woman around by your side in public,
that right there is enough for your disqualification.
Unlike your mom, I'm not a person
who can have an intimate relationship, don't you also know that all too well?
Shin Se Yeon!
Do not shout!
Neither you nor she are in your right minds.
I'm doing this to talk some sense into you before you
become crazy.
Be grateful.
Send off Kang Yoo Jeong to... wherever.
Then I'll consider doing your favor.
Weren't you, at this point in time, desperate?
Never again mention
my mom.
Hey, Jae Ha!
Where are you?
What do you mean why?
Because I want to give
that apology you so wanted.
Uh, you're here.
I wonder what Attorney Ahn is doing here.
Because my work ended well,
I came by to have a drink with a friend.
A friend?
Thanks to you I met a decent friend.
Thank you.
At first it was my father you tempted,
then Se Yeon and now even Jae Ha?
Amazing, Attorney Ahn.
Per your advice,
I put some effort into networking.
You weren't here to apologize?
Hey, drink up, then
give it a try.
Ah, since you're going to [apologize], why not have that
"damaged good" [KYJ] do it too?
Then you never know.
Maybe my company, Se Gang, could
help out your tiny restaurant?
Jae Ha!
That's why, you should have been nicer when I was your friend?
We are both friendless.
If you have nothing to say, then take off.
So that we can chat amongst friends.
Even if the company [restaurant] gets acquired,
I'll make certain all the employees' retention will remain in tact.
Please send a message to Yoo Jeong that she needn't
worry about her employment.
Ah, I hope that Chairman gets better.
Ah, that mug.
He comes and goes [here] as if it's his master suite.
Where is Kang Yoo Jeong?
Is Kang Yoo Jeong your dog's name?
Do you think she's the kind that will come with tail swishing when called?
Where is she, I said?
Stop working her so hard.
She works all night so often.
What's there to work all night over a crappy little restaurant.
I'm going to report you as the vicious employer.
Substitute?
Why are you still here?
President, the sauce this time,
it tastes pretty good.
It goes good with meat,
and have special tangy taste with salad, too.
I think the response will be great.
Do you think that will change anything?
If the board of directors decide to sell this restaurant,
we're both going to be fired.
We won't know until the end.
We don't know, yet.
Would you like to taste this?
It seems alright to my taste.
Don't smile.
You would smile like that,
will you, too... also leave me?
Once you get what you wanted,
you'll also... be leaving me, right?
You said you wanted me to do what you tell me.
Until you tell me to leave, Boss...
I will not go.
♫ A person came into my life
♫ The person I should not love
♫ If the tears steal the heart and disappear
♫ Because I thought she would come closer
♫ I believe that I love you
♫ It's shaking me like crazy
♫ If this limping love of mine
♫ If it moves closer, because you
You came?
Even without you coming here,
I was just going to watch something interesting...
I was with Yoo Jeong that day.
So?
Kang Yoo Jeong.
You woman...
By any chance, did Attorney Ahn do it?
Yoo Jeong, it seems like you have a date set for your death...
I can't die, even if I wanted to.
Making food in the kitchen, how can you get revenge?
Doing great!
Happy birthday to you.
Would you like to eat before you go?
There is no secret in the world, right?
Regarding Kang Yoo Jeong's father...
I'll think about that slowly.