Secret
Please believe me. There was nobody.
No one saw anything.
On that rainy road, because a truck suddenly popped out,
my car slipped, and we...
No, I... Just that,
all I did was hit the barrel at that construction site.
I even got off the car and checked it myself.
But the barrel you keep insisting about
was not at the scene!
Because it was in the middle of the road, I pushed it away
to the shoulder because it would be dangerous.
Please try finding it again.
Find what? Just what are we finding?
Gwang Soo...
Yes.
Kang Yoo Jeong said that
the accident happened, trying to avoid a truck.
That truck driver could be the only eyewitness.
Find that person,
and find out what happened that day.
Yes.
RET
SECRET
I know Min Hyeok.
The look in Min Hyeok's eyes when he looks at that woman,
it's love.
♫ A person came into my life
♫ The person I should not love
♫ No I should not
♫ I tried to turn away many times
♫ I made that person cry
This now...
It's alright.
You could have... made a mistake.
It was not a mistake.
♫ and disappear
♫ Because I thought she would come closer
♫ I believe that I love you
♫ It's shaking me like crazy
♫ If this limping love of mine
♫ If it moves near, because you might
Don't you think it'll be really dragging tonight?
Your wound is deep.
Perhaps you should go to the hospital...
♫ I only watch
Tonight, would you stay with me?
♫ I believe that I love you
♫ It's shaking me like crazy
♫ If this limping love of mine
♫ If it moves near, because you might hide from fear
♫ Even though I say I'm hurt as if I could die
♫ I only watch
♫ If the tears knew my heart
No, it can't be farther from the truth.
The case of wrongdoing on the election
was found not guilty.
All my father did was to go out
to the local district for support.
It's something that has nothing to do with our foundation.
I'm hanging up, then.
Please drink. I just turned the switch off.
Regarding the Nanu Magic Construction
that the K-Group is funding,
please make sure you get the approval as soon as possible.
This marriage…
are you really going to do it?
Do Hoon, you said
that you and I live in two different worlds.
In this world, I will end up getting married to Min Hyeok.
And that goes the same for Min Hyeok.
Things like love,
I don’t need it.
In my world,
are you in a relationship with me?
You don’t like it?
Did you get hurt a lot yesterday?
If you’re hurt more than the scar, then just say you’re hurt.
It’s hard to see you pretend you’re not.
I have a meeting at the foundation. I have to go.
Mom… mommy…
Oh no…
Hey!
Mo...mo...mommy...
Don’t cry… don’t cry.
Mommy… mom…
Oh? What is this? Look at this! What is it? It’s a car!
Oooh!
Mommy… Mommy… !
Mommy!
Where’s mommy?
You should say thank you.
Your child is so cute.
He’s only cute for a moment, I can’t take my eyes off him for a second.
Little nuisance.
Aigoo!
Again!
Aigoo...
Mommy...
Mommy
Drink.
When you're having a hard time,
you said if you drink this, you get strength.
I’m going to drop this.
It’s hot.
Thank you.
Are you going to keep avoiding me?
What happened that day…
I've already forgotten about it.
On whose account?
I told you it was not a mistake.
Boss…
I’m really busy right now.
But…
I came here… to see you.
Because even if I see you like this,
I feel like I could live.
♫ Even though I cannot say
♫ Hot enough to get burned
The tears in my heart
♫ If I can pour it out to you
My love
♫ For me to call
It’s the contract for investment approval from Hannam-dong.
You're the one who made it happen.
Take this to Ahn Do Hoon, directly yourself.
Gwang Soo will give you a ride when you get off work.
Thank you.
♫ I have a heart
I want to shout, but
♫ I swallow it again today
Since I saw you, even like this,
I'm ok.
♫ I say please embrace but
My love
♫ When my tears dry out
When my love fades away
♫ You're going to be hurt too much
♫ My love
There a guest here.
Please come in.
Please approve this contract from the legal team.
This isn’t something I can decide by myself.
Wait until the Board of Directors approve it.
It’s not because you don’t want to take it?
What are you talking about?!
It doesn’t look good...
seeing you desiring what others have.
That’s not something for you to say.
I had chances to get up here. If you’re done with your business,
go back.
Some chance...
No.
You came all the way up here by your own will.
Therefore the consequences, the responsibility,
you're the one who must take them.
Don’t act like you’re the victim.
It’s repulsive.
I will come to get the documents tomorrow.
It’s Boss’ order.
What is it that you want?
You want me to compensate?
Compensate?
How could it be compensated?
For taking my child from me,
you left my dad to die in the streets,
how much do I have to get to get enough?
I should ask around.
What will your parents say?
Kang Yoo Jeong!
Don’t call out my name!
I will take it. That compensation.
I'll get the right amount, so
make sure to prepare yourself.
I confirmed Miss Kang Yoo Jeong going inside her home.
Good job.
You can go now.
Miss Kang Yoo Jeong...
went to the bakery again after leaving Ahn Do Hoon's office.
There is something I'm curious about.
That bakery…
Why aren’t you returning it back to Miss Kang Yoo Jeong?
Because she might go away.
If I give it to her,
because she might disappear in front of my eyes.
Sook Ja Unni
Yes Unni, this is Yoo Jeong.
I have a favor to ask…
I love you, customer!
Wow~ take this as collateral.
Customer?
Yeah, customer. I'm the customer you love
A person you should love.
Yoo Jeong!
Unni, I’m sorry all of a sudden.
You know this isn’t allowed.
That’s why I am asking you like this.
Yeah…
You're not someone who would normally ask, either.
This isn’t something that will become a problem, right?
No.
The date was the 1st.
It was a car going southbound since 11PM… it has a high pass on it.
This...
It's the make and number of the car.
I need the data from when that car was coming back to Seoul.
Unnie, so…
why isn’t the boss showing up these days?
You know the boss doesn’t have time like that.
The Boss is very sick.
The fever that started from infection on his ankle is not reducing.
Then the hospital...
His physician already came and went.
Please help.
Well… what do I have to do?
I have work to do so I have to go out.
♫ When I see you smiling
♫ I don't have to open my eyes to know it's a dream
♫ Even though I reach out my hand
There is no use
♫ After the love ended
♫ Back then I did not know
♫ Where you had stayed,
there were only tears
♫ What if the memories all get wet
What if they disappear too soon
♫ Although it hurts,
I live on without crying
♫ It's me who finally says that I love you
♫ The words I didn't know back then
The words I didn't want to hear
♫ In your flowing tears
♫ The fact I have lived there
♫ If I had also known it back then
Don’t touch that.
You…
Why are you here?
Are you feeling better now?
Aren’t you hungry?
You haven't eaten anything all day.
But...
you didn’t injure your hands.
If you’re done, I will clean up and go now.
That orgel (music box)…
It’s my mother’s.
If it makes sound,
It keeps reminding me.
I wasn’t angry at you.
I was just scared.
What’s so scary?
My mother…
Passed away because of me.
If I didn’t go in that room.
No…
If I just didn’t wind it up again…
I just don’t want to think…
How much my mother would resent me.
There is no mother in the world
that would resent their child for that.
My mother was never happy in this house.
She was always standing by the window looking outside.
As if she can’t leave this house because of me.
It was like that.
Like that.
Boss, you’re mistaken.
I don’t know everything but,
A person who was going to leave,
will eventually leave.
It’s not that she couldn’t leave here because of you,
It’s probably that she could stay here
because of you.
If she knew how distressed you are now,
she would have more of a hard time.
I too…
Had a child.
So…
Believe what I say.
Just for a moment.
Stay here just for a moment before you go.
You’re pretty close with Kim Jae Ha from Se Gwang these days.
I owe Mr Jo Min Hyeok for making a friend.
I found out who spread the rumors
Of our president’s ailment.
It was Se Gwang.
Don’t forget the saying not to fix your hat under a pear tree.
(Korean proverb – if you fix your hat under a pear tree, you look like you’re reaching your hand out to steal a pear)
Please look here.
Look here too.
Don’t think of it as only my request.
In any case, our goal is to expand the restaurant.
Let’s stop playing games like this.
Games?
-Like this.
Weren’t we always playing like this?
It’s all done, please follow me out.
I have no time. I have a meeting for my father’s election.
The Wurthering Heights you gave me,
I finished it.
Revenge that started with love ends in tragedy.
Right?
I have to go.
What I want to know is,
If it’s the opposite…
Love that starts from revenge…
What happens to that?
Think about it.
The chairman approved and the legal department agreed to it.
Congratulations.
It’s not over just because you got the investment.
Se Gwang is still observing King’s Restaurant.
The Boss…
Isn’t going to let go of the restaurant that easily.
I stopped the media.
The rumors aren’t that great right now, but if things like this go out of hand
Who’s going to trust a company that’s owned by Jo Min Hyeok?
What are you trying to say?
If you look at it, it all happened just because of you!
You think it’s ok for all those employees
to be nervous because of you?
Don’t act like you care for those employees.
You only…
Want to protect your place.
Yeah, this place.
I have the responsibility to protect K-Group.
If Jo Min Hyeok falls, K-Group is in danger. I’m just saying this…
Because you are closer to Jo Min Hyeok than I am.
Tell Jo Min Hyeok to go to Kim Jae Ha
and kneel to apologize for letting this happen
because of one woman.
That...
Would be the best for K-Group and Jo Min Hyeok.
Yes Miss Se Yeon.
No, it’s okay.
I will be there now.
What are you doing here now?
I am sorry.
I would like to apologize.
Because of me you and my boss…
I don't think your apology is going to end it.
Jo Min Hyeok is some guy…
he sent you instead of coming himself?
No, it’s not that.
The Boss doesn't know.
It's a matter that has arisen because of me.
I will apologize to you.
What do you think you are doing?
You think this is an 80’s drama?
You,
Get up.
Get up!
Well, I did get some valuable information on the company,
But I still can’t get over the humiliation Min Hyeok gave me.
He has a great fiancée like Se Yeon,
And pretty girls all around him,
So what’s the reason why he keeps getting attracted to
a defected one like you?
Jo Min Hyeok’s taste I don’t get...
Here, pour a glass.
I will accept your apology depending on how you do.
Substitute.
Why are you coming only now?
I know it’s your day off but…
aren’t you bit too late?
Where were you?
How is your foot?
Can you walk?
That's a relief.
I will go in now.
Substitute...ah!
Are you ok? Yeah.
Does it hurt?
It was ok because of you
but not so much right now.
You didn’t come with Gwang Soo?
You can go around by yourself?
Gwang Soo is in the middle of work.
Don’t mind him.
Oh…
Oh yes.
Here.
You went to get this?
Nothing happened?
No.
It’s late. You should go.
What the?
He’s all better.
That’s why you shouldn’t commit a crime in the first place.
The financial supervisory service requested the investigation, I can’t get by this one.
It was for fund raising purposes.
Lawyer Choi has to come and explain that.
I am not the most righteous but I do my best in the work I’m given.
You should be careful too.
Lawyer Choi can just say you or the president told you to do so.
You know he’s not that type of person.
You know Shin Hwa and Se Gwang is on to get K-Hotel?
I heard the rumor on his illness started from Se Gwang.
That woman
is from that hit and run accident 4 years ago right?
What are you guys doing?
I told you to do only what I told you to do.
Why are you doing things that I didn’t tell you to do?!
That’s…
Why did you go see Jae Ha?
Why did you pour him a drink?
To apologise.
I heard the company is in trouble, because of that incident.
Did Ahn Do Hoon say that?!
I just…
I was wrong, so if I apologised...
Why do YOU apologize?
Why is it always YOUR fault?
That was my fault! Taking you there was my fault!
I did it because I wanted to apologise!
I wanted to...
do something in your place.
Liquor?
Why not pour it?
I can kneel down if they want me to kneel.
If I can help my boss by doing that,
what’s so hard in doing it?
Why do YOU have to kneel down to help me?
That…
doesn’t affect me at all.
I…
I can’t accept that.
From now on,
don't kneel down to anyone.
If someone has to, it'll be me.
I can’t keep my position vacant too long.
Let me ask you one thing.
Did you do it because of me?
I don’t have any other reason… I was just…
Bothered…
Because
you might get into a difficult situation because of me…
I was just
bothered…
There's no other reason.
It’s been a while…
Chairman!
I'm fine.
Dad!
Yes?
Min Joo, no!
Mum!
It's fine.
Still, Mr. President.
Mr. President is very tired.
You,
You’re not happy to see mom?
Mom…
did you get that makeup?
They only sell that in Germany. You got it right?
Yes, let’s go up.
Let’s go in.
I heard from Kwang Min.
The Investment on the restaurants.
Good job.
Investment is only the beginning.
We will raise business performance now.
Now you’re sounding like my son.
How is...
your health?
I don’t plan on passing things onto you yet.
Don’t worry.
You should go now.
And don’t look away.
We shouldn’t
let lawyer Ahn Do Hoon know yet.
Se Gwang has a big information network,
we do not know where the source leaked from.
And?
Sorry?
Kwang Min,
you have that face when you have something to say.
Just say it.
Lawyer Ahn...
started as a prosecutor in charge of Miss Seo Ji Hee’s
hit and run accident and came up here.
It seems like Min Hyeok is looking into that accident again.
Why?
It seems like a woman problem.
Oh, that jerk. Really.
Kang Yoo Jeong?
You've seen me before, right?
Sit down.
I heard that you're a restaurant employee.
Yes. I heard that she's a person that Min Hyeok chose personally.
You helped Min Hyeok and received an investment,
you've worked very hard.
The hard work, if you've done that much, it's enough.
You shouldn't have any more reasons to see Min Hyeok.
Answer him. The Chairman is asking you.
The thing is...
Min Hyeok is still less than mature so he's not discriminating when meeting people.
There has to be no more wounds to him from meeting people.
I thought that once would be sufficient.
It's enough. There's no reason to pull out something that's passed.
It seems like you understand what I am saying.
If you met unpleasantly, you should quickly separate.
Then go ahead and prepare the meal.
Yes.
What is this?
Don't talk in such a loud voice in front of the president, he is still...
Sitting a person down here, what do you all think
you're doing?!
Let's go.
Go.
Kwang Soo.
What are you doing?
Let go. Let go, Choi Gwang Soo.
Butler Im. Let that woman out.
Yes.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I told you not to be sorry.
I told you definitely that you had done nothing wrong!
I'm sorry.
Kang Yoo Jeong. Kang Yoo Jeong!
Attorney Ahn,
I heard that you knew a way to handle that woman.
I don't think that I'll be able to dine with you.
I'll request that you take care of the back end clean up.
Attorney Ahn.
Did you see?
This is the difference between you and I, and them.
I know.
Don't get involved further with Jo Min Hyeok.
Then what about you? Until where are you going to get involved with Shin Se Yeon?
What did you say?
You advising me, you don't think it's presumptuous?
Thank you.
The Medic Alert Bracelet.
I went to the institute and you were listed as my dad's guardian.
In case you had started touching it up from there,
I was worried.
It's a relief.
That woman, don't bother her.
I'll protect her. This time you really can't!
What are you saying in front of Se Yeon?!
It doesn't matter, Chairman.
The marriage is something that we have to proceed with anyway.
I'm not getting married!
Do you think you'll be able to do that?
Sitting in this spot, is something that even the dead Seo Ji Hee couldn't do.
There should be no reason for the woman who killed Seo Ji Hee to come into this house.
There will be no matter of you coming into this house either.
Gwang Soo, let go.
Let me go!
I'm not going to do this marriage! I don't need any of it!
Se Yeon and I, no longer have anything to do
with one another.
You!
Chairman!
Leave it!
Try saying that once more!
That woman, don't mess with her.
I won't forgive you, Father.
You!
That...oh.
Let go!
Move!
Let me go! I said let me go! Move!
Move! I said move!
Let go!
I'm worried.
Kang Yoo Jeong! Kang Yoo Jeong!
Yoo Jeong. Kang Yoo Jeong!
Kang Yoo Jeong!
I know that you're here.
Go back.
It's a relief.
I was afraid that you'd hide again.
Go! Please!
I won't make the same mistake twice.
I don't care, even if I get kicked out of K Group.
President...
You have to be here. I have to keep you here next to me.
Stop talking like a little child.
Aren't my feelings important?
Why do I have to get all that insult to be next to you?
Don't you feel the same?
You said also that I unsettled your nerves.
Yes, you do unsettle my nerves.
But that's all.
I'm just using you Boss.
I am just using you because I am angry that
I broke up with Ahn Do Hoon that I loved so much.
So, please go back.
Substitute!
Substitute! Open the door!
Open the door!
Substitute!
Open the door! Open the door!
Kang Yoo Jeong!
Please! Open the door!
When I look at you Boss... its difficult.
I want to forget,
Boss, you keep on bringing out the memory.
Come out.
Come out, come out!
Let's talk facing each other.
I said come out.
Please stop this now.
I...
figured it out.
When that accident happened,
it's probably not just the barrel,
I knew it.
If I had paid just a little more attention,
Seo Ji Hee...
She probably would be with you now, Boss.
Because I was too happy at that time,
I was afraid what if my happiness shatters,
it's probably nothing,
I just believed it like that.
Because I was afraid of the poison,
I avoided it.
So, Seo Ji Hee...
I killed her, is right.
Whenever I see you, that day comes to my mind.
Because I feel suffocated for the guilt feeling,
it's hard to see you, Boss.
Really anymore...
I don't want to see you anymore.
I'm going.
Because I'm going,
don't have a hard time.
♫ we have changed
♫ Memories again today more and more
♫ Engulf me
♫ They became painful scars, and
♫ Because of your changed heart
♫ Even my recollection must be trying hard to erase you
♫ Each of us, we have loved
♫ Each of us, we have shed tears
Living under the same sky
♫ It was happiness to me
♫ You were like the sky to me
In that when I only loved,
♫ That time, when I only loved,
I want to go back to that time
♫ Each of us, we have loved
♫ Each of us, we have shed tears
♫ Living under the same sky
It was happiness to me
♫ You were like the sky to me
In that when I only loved,
♫ That time, when I only loved,
I want to go back to that time
Boss!
What fault would it be of yours,
father has always been the first to you.
I found it.
At the day of the accident,
the truck that almost hit Kang Yoo Jeong's car.
I found it.
I'm sorry.
The sins I committed to you...
I know I can't be forgiven, but
I still came shamelessly like this.
I'm sorry I dared.
I know I shouldn't, but
one day,
even if it was only one day,
I wanted to accept the boss's heart.
I know it's something I should be punished for.
Even as I know that,
I wanted to hold that hand.
I'm sorry.
♫ Would it be alright if I move closer
♫ I was scared so I stood still
♫ I wonder if we really had to meet
♫ I can't give an answer
♫ Because an unerasable scar hurts
♫ Would I be able to tell you again that
I love you
♫ No matter how many times I let you go,
you're still the one
♫ No matter how hard I try to erase you,
like an incurable disease
♫ Spreading inside of me
I just can't stop this love Yeah
♫ I cannot take another step
♫ After fending off that suffocating piercing wind
♫ That final night when I held you too tight
♫ That it was love passed and gone
Can we reassure ourselves beginning tomorrow
♫ Because an unerasable scar hurts
I'll just be stubborn this once, Father.
I won't go through the marriage.
Will you guys really be okay?
Wasn't this kind of thing, what you wanted?
What I want, is you.
If the chairman collapses, he will come back.
I'll help you.
Attorney Choi will have to be appearing at the Prosecutions.
I don't know if I can do this.
Perhaps because it's more recent than the hit-and-run,
there were may clues I could find.
It doesn't end like this.