Secret
Let's go. I have something to say.
What are you?
You, just what have you done?!
You...
What have you done?
What are you doing right now?
That's something for me to say.
Go.
Don't go.
In front of me,
don't... give orders to this woman.
I have no reason
to hear something like that from you.
You don't?
You don't?!
Oppa!
Are you crazy?
Why do you keep hitting people?!
What...
Just what are you?!
I'm so annoyed.
Oppa, are you ok...
What will make you listen to me?
Jo Min Hyeok...
He knew of the relationship between you and me.
What are you saying?
He knows about us, and he's doing this kind of crap!
No way!
Are you saying he knew, but still let us meet?
That's why I told you to stay away from him.
Yes.
♫ Love
♫ Like this
♫ More and more
♫ Goes far away
♫ Seasons
♫ Like this
♫ More and more
♫ Slip away
♫ Time flew away
♫ And we have changed
Are you going to follow him wherever he wants to go?
What's with this look and all?
I had no choice, the boss forced me to...
If he asks you to,
Would you even sell your body?
♫ They became painful scars,
and engulfed me
♫ Because of your changed heart
♫ Even my recollection must be trying hard to erase you
♫ Each of us, we have loved
♫ Each of us, we have shed tears
♫ Living under the same sky
♫ It was happiness to me
♫ You were like the sky to me
♫ In that when I only loved,
that time
♫ When I only loved,
I want to go back to that time
RET
SECRET
Now then,
with 8 votes,
which is more than half of 12 directors,
President Jo Min Hyeok's
dismissal case has passed.
You!
What are you doing?
I put you next to Min Hyeok in order for you to take care of him.
Where were you and what have you been doing
to result in this kind of mishap?
I'm sorry.
If you say sorry, does that resolve everything...
Stop, Father.
It happened while he was taking care of some business I asked him to do.
The board of directors
passed a Dismissal Case against the President.
What are you talking about?
Among those who voted yes,
Shin Se Yeon was also included.
Get out.
Father.
Get out immediately.
Is it you?
It wasn't enough what you did to Jae Ha,
you also did this to Do Hoon?
You do this to a person and not a word of apology?
I told you not to take someone else's side in front of me.
The apology,
I'm the one who should get it.
What apology are you talking about?
What apology?
Jo Min Hyeok!
- What apology?
What are you doing? Jo Min Hyeok!
Do Hoon, go.
If you wanted the hotel, why didn't you just say it?
Then, I would have just given it to you
as your wedding present.
It's not that I wanted the hotel.
It's not enough you bring that woman to a place,
where everyone we know is present,
you'd even fist fight for that woman?
To what extent will you go?
Do you know how pathetic you made me look?
Se Yeon, the Chairman can hear.
Don't you dare butt in!!
Let's go.
If he had kept his president's position as is,
the situation was that it would've been difficult
to set his foot back in the hotel.
That's why
Se Yeon, you raised your hand, and
pushed out Min Hyeok first?
There were two people who were definitely on your side,
I confirmed it.
If we call back Min Hyeon again next year at the reorganization of the board of directors...
That...
It's not you, but
it's for me to decide.
Here.
It's too obvious Gwang Min is on my side, so it won't work.
This...
Where it got conceptualized,
why don't you find out?
Yes.
What's wrong with your lips?
It's nothing.
I don't think I've paid for my sins.
For my whole life...
I won't forget it for my whole life.
How could I forget?
What I'm ashamed of...
is what I had done to that person who passed away.
You saw, but you just left,
is this correct?!
Yes. I did it.
What more do you want?
Tormenting me all this time,
isn't that enough?
Crazy bastard.
Just what did she do?
Gwang Soo,
how could there be such a revolting thing?
I only confirmed they were at the cafe.
Whether they were in the car together, I'm not sure...
After the proposal...
When they came back, in that rain,
they went separately?
Does it make sense?
Jae Ha, it seems he will keep his word this time.
No matter how low down dirty his behavior is,
the name Se Gwang is not something we can disrespect.
He wants you to directly apologize to him.
Go see him right away tomorrow.
Apology?
I can do that as much as he wants. Instead...
tell that son of a bitch to apologize first,
to that woman he wronged.
Who is that woman?
Someone that worries me.
A woman who bothers you,
first, you have to be careful.
What is this?
A defective good?
I heard that you do anything you are asked to if you are given money.
Where do you come off all expensive?
Hey!
Go buy some clothes.
She does do everything she's told.
Only what I tell her to do.
Are you not going to talk about what happened yesterday?
If you bury it like that,
your insides are going to rot completely.
That, that, that.
Seeing that you're laughing, there is a problem.
Why? Just rest!
You were burning with fever yesterday.
Do you know how I got this job?
What is that clothing?
Is that really yours?
I'll be back.
Substitute driver.
Kang Yoo Jeong!
Jo Min Hyeok,
he knew about the relationship between you and me.
He knows about our relationsip, and he's doing this kind of thing!
What is it this time again?
Just what is it that you want from me?
How far would you have to go
before you'll feel relieved?
How long do you plan to keep your mouth shut?
What are you talking about?
What is it that you're trying to guard by going this far?
Tell me with your mouth.
You and Do Hoon, what are you two hiding?
Everyone!
I am a woman that has killed someone.
A hit-and-run criminal.
I deserve to be stoned to death!
Hey!
I said it.
Are you satisfied?
Isn't this what you wanted?
Substitute driver.
Is this not enough?
Do you want me to run into the road?
Get a hold of yourself!
Are you crazy?
Yes, I am crazy.
I wish I was really crazy!!
Hey!
Kang Yoo Jeong!
Are you crazy?
Aish!
♫ Would it be alright if I move closer
♫ I was scared so I stood still
♫ Did we really have to meet
♫ I can't give an answer
♫ Because an unerasable scar hurts
Gwang Soo, how could she do that?
♫ No matter how many times I let you go
Even putting her life on the line,
what would it be that she wants to keep?
I'll go get the car.
It's alright.
I have nothing to talk about with you.
Tell Min Hyeok to come and bow down.
There is no way Jo Min Hyeok will come himself.
So he'll just send an attorney and forget about it?
You can just beat it.
The media article due for tomorrow,
why don't you fold it?
Oh my... What kind of era is this,
for a mere company to control the media?
You can stop the false modesty.
If you write them,
don't they become the public opinion?
The cancelled event of the K-Hotel this time,
will go on as planned.
You, what do you see me as?
The new Chairman,
who will lead Se Gwang in the future.
Please look at what's in the envelope first, then talk.
What do you want to do with this?
Only spreading some dirty rumor about Jo Min Hyeok,
you wouldn't be satisfied with that.
Excuse me?
Yes, why?
You've never lost in an argument, right?
Not yet.
If you become a prosecutor, you will probably always win.
Probably.
Then will you help me when something
unfair happens to me at that time too?
I'll help people without money and power unconditionally.
What about the people with money and power?
Well those people find their own way.
What would I do if I go to find you
and you act like you don't know me?
In the future, come find me with this.
I will act like I know you.
Just as you shudder at the thought of seeing me,
it's hard for me, too.
I don't ever want to see you again.
It's not because of you Se Yeon.
Jo Min Hyeok turning out like this,
I'm saying it's not because of you.
Do Hoon, there are times when you're scary.
Just by looking at my face,
how do you know what I'm thinking?
You're right. That's a big problem.
Have you eaten?
Why? You should know by just looking at my face.
It's for looking after the hotel in place of me,
that I pay you a handsome salary,
I don't believe I pay you to date my fiancée.
Why does it matter who I meet?
As long as we marry according to our contract,
dating or whatever, you said I was free?
You have to at least be discreet with whom you date
to suit your class.
Don't concern yourself over him.
Because Min Hyeok probably doesn't either.
Se Yeon.
Dinner.
Where should we eat?
You'll probably get your clothes all smelly.
Because this is this first time,
Do Hoon brought a woman to our restaurant.
She is a person who works with me.
Give it to me. I'll do it.
This, all of it, I did all the work and dried it myself.
I fried it with oil so it'll taste good.
It looks good. I'll eat well.
Okay.
Oh, your fingers are quite long.
They're pretty.
What do you do?
Since you work with Do Hoon, are you a lawyer?
No, I paint.
Paint?
No wonder, I knew your ambience was different.
Where is your house?
What does your father do?
Mom!
We came here to eat comfortably.
Aigoo, aigoo, I was acting out of line...
Aigoo, this... You probably don't know how to eat,
so I'll have to assist you.
It tastes good. Thank you.
Please eat a lot.
Min Hyeok, starting tomorrow, look after the restaurants.
Doing extracurricular activities will help you.
Just take the restaurants and be gone,
isn't that what it is?
Since I at least gave you that, you should be grateful!
The person who made the situation like this now,
it's you!
Cleaning up after you,
it's Ahn Do Hoon who did it all.
You better be embarrassed, kid!
Father.
Taking care of you ends right here.
Your bread and butter,
from now on, you protect it.
Chairman.
Don't you think you need to give more shares to Min Joo?
How can they push people out like this,
as they want?
If you want to return to the hotel even tomorrow,
the regional offices you're assigned to this time,
do a good job with them!
Why don't you Ahjussi just be the President,
instead of Oppa?
He would be so much better than Oppa.
Min Joo.
What?
Isn't it more comfortable for you too, Oppa?
Because all you'll have to do is play.
Aish.
Chairman.
Do I not know my father?
There is no way my father would have brought in a person,
without any background investigation.
So?
He probably shed any dirt if he had any.
Your data on Attorney Ahn Do Hoon's investigation,
turn all of it over to me.
Hey, are you not going home?
I'm waiting for Yoo Jeong...
-yo. (making it formal)
Unni!
What happened? You didn't even come to work!
What is she talking about? You went out to work.
I told them that you were sick today, but
if you don't come without contacting...
Sorry. I'm sorry, Hye Ri.
You've been really weird since yesterday.
What's going on?
Just talk.
I'm so frustrated, frustrated. I'm so frustrated!
I'm the one who is crazy, asking that stone-buddha.
Do you still not know that if unni closes her mouth once,
it's the end?
What is this? That's Boss's secretary,
did you come with him?
Tell him to come in!
Yes, Mr. President.
Now you're even keeping a watch on me?
Getting people to do this, it's displeasing.
Do I really have to disappear from you,
before you'll end this?
Substitute, if you do what you did today again...
That's because I'm worried. . .
- I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
I told you not to do what you'll be sorry for.
That's okay. Come back.
And... tomorrow morning, call Ahn Do Hoon.
Yes.
Since you got promoted thanks to me,
shouldn't you at least say a word of thanks?
Yes.
Thanks to you I have more work,
I'll have to go to the office right away.
Is that so?
Okay.
Don't worry about Kang Yoo Jeong.
Because I confirmed she is doing well.
Yoo Jeong...
She is not a woman for you to treat carelessly like that.
Me? No.
It may not seem it, but I'm really concerned over her.
At any event,
however I treat Kang Yoo Jeong,
do I need permission from you for that, Attorney Ahn?
Isn't she not a woman detached from you now?
If not, is there a problem for me being with that woman?
They say even hateful connection is still binding,
the more I see her, I feel more closely binding.
She's an interesting woman.
If it's a story that doesn't matter to me,
I'll not listen anymore.
I took quite a bit of your time.
Alright, while I'm not here,
you'll have your hands full managing the hotel.
Keep up the good work.
Let's start visiting the branch offices in Seoul from today,
and let your face be known.
Work regarding restaurant management,
an employee from the main office will accompany you.
Attorney Ahn, I have let the security team know,
were you able to find the black-box data alright?
On the next prosecution investigation,
I think we can use them as data.
I have to go to a meeting, so. . .
President, at 2 o'clock,
Shin Se Yeon wants to see you in the work room.
Se Yeon?
Did you have good time on your date yesterday?
Yeah.
That's a relief.
The one who got Do Hoon participating in the hotel work,
it was you I heard?
He must have done a lot of work for the K-Group,
for him to be approved by the board of directors?
Was that something I could do alone?
If your purpose was to get me angry,
then you've succeeded.
Why did you want to see me?
The food we'll provide during the weekend,
for the children on the small islands,
I would like one of your restaurants to sponsor it.
Okay.
That's it?
You're saying you want to do a good thing, right?
Let's do it.
The Chinese food that will go to the correctional facilities,
it will be sponsored by K-Hotel.
Are you having fun?
What?
Providing for here and there with a shallow sympathy,
comforting yourself, saying "I'm a good person."
What are you trying to say?
You and I, we are both in this position
thanks to our parents, so
don't pretend to be high and mighty by yourself.
Using Ahn Do Hoon as if you want me to watch,
do you have enough confidence to say you're not?
Or could you really have fallen in love with him?
As you said,
it doesn't matter to me whether you love or date, but
Ahn Do Hoon that jerk can't be the one.
Jo Min Hyeok.
But then, was that even necessary?
I know you a little bit.
Shin Se Yeon, you're not someone who gives up so easily.
Get out.
If you have something to ask in the future,
you come find me yourself,
instead of telling me to come and go.
♫ Back then I did not know
♫ Where you had stayed,
there were only tears
♫ What if the memories all get wet
♫ What if they disappear too soon
♫ Although it hurts,
I live on without crying
♫ It's me who finally says that I love you
♫ The words I didn't know back then
The words I didn't want to hear
♫ In your flowing tears
♫ The fact I have lived there
♫ If I had also known it back then
The bakery building,
it's correct that it became the property of the company Jo Min Hyeok is the CEO of, but
because it's the company's estate,
he shouldn't be able to do whatever he wants.
I can stop that myself.
Take this.
Oppa.
I said take it.
Use this to pay back Jo Min Hyeok.
I will take care of that myself.
Until when are you going to act foolish?
Just what are you going to do to pay him back?
I help out here during the night and work during the day.
What kind of work?
It's at the restaurant.
If I work well, I might be promoted and work at the office too.
That restaurant. . .
Did you know that Jo Min Hyeok was the CEO of it?
What?
If you want to be the fiddle in Jo Min Hyeok's hand,
do it alone if you want.
Oppa, I didn't know about that.
Then take this money!
I'm not giving you this, so you'll like it,
I'm giving you this, so I can be comfortable!
And this is what I ask, please...
get away from Jo Min Hyeok.
Because of you, he is tightening his ropes around me, too!
You said you wanted us to be comfortable.
You said you wanted us to stop being sorry for each other.
Then why are you like this?
Why do keep making me feel sorry for you?
Until when are you going to be like this?
Seriously, until when?!
Detective Choi?
This is Ahn Do Hoon.
Did you see that yesterday?
Ahh! Daebak!
- Ugly! Really ugly...
It was everywhere on the face.
Kang Yoo Jeong.
Hello.
Long time, no see.
Someone turned you in,
for trademark violation.
Legal Team, Director Ahn Do Hoon.
Ahh. . .yes. . .
Last week he came by and copied some files.
What files?
Between April and July,
those who have worked with Pyungchang construction,
the reports of the Management-Team's vehicles.
What else?
Nothing.
Those files, send them to me too.
Okay.
From today, the Chairman ordered
that you manage the sales of the restaurants.
Okay. Let's go before more gets taken away from me.
The vehicle reports and the black-box videos,
how far do you go back in safeguarding?
For director level and above, it's 5 years.
5 years?
5 years.
Wait a moment!
Hello, Director.
By the way, why is the president
suddenly looking for the black-box backup files?
I think he said there was something to confirm.
First, lets do it after we eat dinner.
because I didn't get to eat lunch.
But, is there a need to backup the black-box videos?
Ahh, there was a time when a virus wiped out all HD.
It's not that I don't know you are a good worker.
But this is a service job and it doesn't look good having police officers look into here.
Substitute driver.
What are you doing not working?
I'm not here to see you.
Didn't you know I was the CEO here?
No.
I should have left on my own, if I knew, but
I stuck here to earn money. I'm sorry.
What are you talking about?
Take it.
It should be worth several months.
Please stop torturing me.
Where did you get this money?
Why does it matter?
Isn't getting my debt back all you needed?
No matter what I do or however I make the money,
it's not something you should be concerned about?
Substitute driver.
Just!
Please!
Leave me alone.
I'll pay you back the rest, no matter what it takes.
She quit?
That. . .actually she was fired.
Some police officer came by and the officer
looked like a robber and... talking about hit-and-run...
And, she had a bad incident previously and he scared her, so
the boss told her not to come anymore.
Unni.
What happened?
Why did you come early?
Unni!
When we were going around selling bags,
someone must have turned us in.
Aish, how can we get caught after only one time?
Such bad luck.
- Aish.
It's alright. We only had a few samples so we only have to pay a fine.
Let's just sell what we can sell.
Why try to make a few more bucks...
Hey, when the police officers were suddenly barging in here,
when I thought about going to jail again
and not being able to see my son for a few years again, my heart just dropped.
Unni.
Should I give you a sedative supplement also?
There's a new one that came in.
I'm sorry, Unni.
I'm sorry.
Why are you sorry?
I'm the one who did wrong.
It's because of me.
I'm sorry.
The detective who came to the store today,
is someone Ahn Do Hoon was close with
when he was a prosecutor,
called Detective Choi Do Hyun.
Are you not answering the phone, Lawyer Ahn?
You must have been surprised at the ringing phone sound.
What are you doing?
That's what I want to ask.
Attorney Ahn, what are you doing here right now?
You're cute when you're baffled.
Talk.
Why you came here.
Regarding the whereabouts of
Assemblyman Shin and Chairman Jo...
Stop talking nonsense and tell me why you're here.
Should I tell you then?
The secret inside there...
Because it might come out... You came here to hide that.
What would it be... That secret?
There is no such thing as secret.
I don't know what you're looking for, but
if you can find it, try finding it.
Fine, Ahn Do Hoon.
With your life on the line,
try to keep that secret.
Because I will reveal it with my own hands.
Pushing Jo Min Hyeok out,
you're not going to regret it?
If I was going to regret it,
I would not have started in the first place.
Why did you go that far?
Min Hyeok...
Because he has too much,
it seemed that he couldn't see me next to him.
If you keep Jo Min Hyeok next to you,
do you think you'll be satisfied?
Even if I go that route,
I must have him at least once.
If you want, Se Yeon,
I will help you.
What Jo Min Hyeok has,
I'll take it all away for you.
You, Do Hoon,
why are you so trying to take Min Hyeok down?
Are you two some kind of bickering enemies?
Do Hoon, you sent it to the
Board of Directors' meeting, did you not?
Earlier when you were investigating the
business transactions of our Gallery,
it was the file that was there together.
That. . .
I didn't tell Min Hyeok.
Looking from a high place,
does the world look a little different now?
I can't tell yet.
But it's true I'm curious.
How high do I have to go up,
before you'll hold my hand?
I don't know.
Try going up as high as you can.
Because if you can't have it,
it will be better to destroy it.
For the time being,
in place of President Jo Min Hyeok, who is vacant,
To help with the hotel management,
a person from the Main Office Legal Team,
I introduce Director Ahn Do Hoon to you.
I'm Ahn Do Hoon.
Yes, I found the data.
Yes, please don't worry. I took care of it.
Yes.
Where is my father?
Because of his trip to Germany next week,
he went to the Main Office for a little bit.
He's going out quite often these days.
What happened?
Oh, it's nothing much.
At the remodeled restaurant,
I would like to throw a food tasting party, and
I wanted to ask my father about it.
It looks good, you're working hard.
Once you solidify your position as his successor,
the Chairman will also feel more assured...
Successor?
Because my father has all the good stuff,
I got a long shot in taking over.
Working hard can't be bad.
That woman who caught your attention,
did it all go well?
Substitute!
Where are you going like that?
Where are you?
Why are you barging into another's home?
Kang Yoo Jeong!
Where is Yoo Jeong?
Why are you asking me that?
The person who ran away to avoid you.
Substitute!
Let's have a talk.
Why are you asking me that?
After Kang Yoo Jeong left my restaurant,
she gave me the money she didn't have, and left!
A few days ago, she contacted me.
She seemed to be scared of you, so
I helped her a little.
Well, that's all.
As you know,
because she is a woman who doesn't matter to me.
But why do you act like she is a woman who matters?
What do you mean?
What she is hiding, I'm sure you know better than me!
I'm curious
whether there is a secret in this world
that can be kept forever,
if there is.
You are the one who appears anxious, Jo Min Hyeok.
You wouldn't be looking for Kang Yoo Jeong to receive
money you have in abundance.
Is it because you're bored
to have lost the toy you've been torturing?
If you have nothing further to say, may I excuse myself?
Yes, this is Ahn Do Hoon.
Yes. Of course.
You can decide as you're accustomed.
Message: $161.00 was deposited into Joeun Bank.
Ugh, Kang Yoo Jeong. Where are you now, huh?
Gwang Soo.
Find the bank where Kang Yoo Jeong deposited
money into my account from today.
Search that area thoroughly!
Yes, sir.
Do you not paint anymore?
I don't have the desire.
What was that about with Min Hyeok earlier?
Did you call me because you were curious about that?
He was looking for Ms. Kang Yoo Jeong.
What I said about Jo Min Hyeok,
that I thought he had feelings for you, I'll correct it.
He just didn't want to have you taken away. That's all.
Would I...
not be the one?
If I move up higher,
would an opportunity also come to me?
♫ Would it be alright if I move closer
Defendant Kang Yoo Jeong's irresponsible behavior,
took a precious life of a young person, and
also took the precious life of the one
who hasn't seen the light of day.
For this, the prosecution team
sentences defendant Kang Yoo Jeong
to 5 years imprisonment.
♫ Would I be able to tell you again that
I love you
San, you should say "Thank you for the delicious food."
to Mr. Prosecutor, huh?
♫ No matter how many times I let you go,
you're still the one
♫ No matter how hard I try to erase you,
like an incurable disease
♫ Spreading inside of me, I just can't stop this love.
♫ I can't take a another step
♫ After feeling the suffocating and sharp wind
♫ It was the last night that I violently held you
♫ Can we promise that this love is all in the past?
You two...
♫ I can't hold it in anymore, my memories toward you
what are you trying to do?
♫ Because unerasable scar hurts
♫ Would I be able to tell you again that
I love you
♫ No matter how many times I let you go,
you're still the one
♫ No matter how hard I try to erase you,
like an incurable disease
♫ Spreading inside of me
♫ I just can't stop this love
♫ In the lost memories, to the door where I see you
♫ If you are standing in the lost time
♫ Please don't move, don't try to forget me
♫ The time that has been stopped
♫ Is flowing to you again
♫ Would I be able to tell you again that
I love you
♫ No matter how many times I let you go,
you're still the one
♫ No matter how hard I try to erase you,
like an incurable disease
♫ Spreading inside of me
Substitute Driver.
♫ I just can't stop this love.
What are you afraid of that you hid?
Who said I hid?
I needed a job, so I came down.
And, I didn't avoid you out of fear, but
I avoided you because I didn't want to see you.
Yoo Jeong, are you all done now?
Yes, please go home and rest.
Okay. Good job.
Yes. See you tomorrow.
Please have a safe trip home.
Don't smile.
Don't smile in front of other people.
Have a good one!
Lodging
Cafeteria
Hello!
Hello! Good morning.
I'm hungry. Give me some food.
It's not meal time yet. Please leave.
I'll just wait until it's time.
Why are you being this way?
I'm hungry, I said.
Hello.
Hello. Yes!
Please give us some food.
Okay.
Yes.
Please also get us some seaweed.
Get out.
I told you I'll pay you back.
Even if I have to work in places like this, I will pay
my debt.
So why did you follow me to here and act out?
Are you going to kick me out again by telling people
that I killed someone and that I'm a criminal?
Why are you doing this!
Is that all you take me for?
Okay. I'll give you that.
At any rate,
regardless, let's go back (to Seoul).
Let go. Let go.
Let's go back!
Let go. Let go!
Why are you like this, are you crazy?!
That's right. I feel like going crazy!
Because you worry me so much, I feel like going crazy!
That's why you stay right next to me!
~ Preview ~
Fire Ahn Do Hoon in the legal department right now.
What are you trying to pull?
So if you stay in front of me, i'll do that for you.
President asks that you start your work from his home.
Did you touch other materials while in the Security Office?
I guess Min Hyeok asked you to report back to him again.
I think Jo Min Hyeok is restarting the investigation
of the hit-and-run case. Did you know?
This is a receipt from your store, right?
Your father has become so much better!
Some guy came and picked him up.
Subtitles brought to you by The Shh! Team @ Viki