Secret
Accumulated fatigue... and
she doesn't seem to have been eating right, either.
Symptoms of exhaustion are serious.
For now, she is stable.
♫ When I see you smiling
♫ I don't have to open my eyes to know it's a dream
♫ Even though I reach out my hand
If you're like this... It's no fun.
♫ After the love ended
♫ Back then I did not know
Get up!
Come back to your senses!
Kang Yoo Jeong.
♫ And they disappear too fast
♫ Although it hurts,
I live on without crying
♫ It's me who finally says I love you
♫ The words I didn't know back then
♫ The words I didn't want to hear
♫ Inside your flowing tears
♫ The fact that I have lived there
♫ If I had also known it back then
Kang Yoo Jeong, are you awake now?
Let's go!
Okay.
I hate it, seriously!
A woman dying because of me,
I don't want to see that anymore.
Because of you...
I didn't say that to get your reply.
Yes!
Don't reply!
Just because she asked for help,
you took all this much?
For a guy not making a penny,
you're so generous to others...
This is why I'm the only one suffering, just me.
Is In Sook one of the others?
She is my younger sister,
and your in-law!
We're going to be eating those fishes anyway,
telling her to send me a few boxes because they were not selling,
Was that so wrong?
You're only oppa to her when she needs...
For the decades she's been in business,
has she ever just given us a few?
They said they're having a hard time.
They said they're having a hard time!
I'm having a hard time too!
Mom?
Our house... Can't we even afford a few fishes?
Who said that?
There are only three of us,
but your father got too much...
Being a prosecutor is nothing.
Lots of work to do, but no increase in salary.
Should I quit?
If I marry a woman who will set me up
with an attorney's office, will it be better?
Do you want to do that? Should I start looking one for you?
WHAT NOW?!
Why are you shouting like that?
You! Because you want to live a good life for yourself,
are you saying you want to do trashy work
for those who are rich?
People who are powerless and and unfairly treated,
I told you to become a prosecutor for those people, too!
That must be the limitation of my abilities.
So you give up?
If you give up because it's hard, is there anything
that can be done in the world?
Then what about you, Dad?
Why did you give up?
What?
Do Hoon.
The life you gave up... Thanks to that,
I didn't even look any other way,
I didn't even think about anyone else!
That's how I have lived.
The dream you couldn't fulfill,
I wanted to accomplish it in place of you.
That's why I...
Do you know what have I done to keep that place?
How I held out, I'm saying do you know?
But look at me.
Look at you two, fighting for a few fishes!
Me right now, I'm not the great prosecutor you think I am.
The righteous prosecutor that you want!
There is nothing I can do with my strength!
Mr. Prosecutor.
Do Hoon.
Se Yeon.
Hotel business... You shouldn't take it lightly.
If I thought it was easy,
I would not have asked you like this, Chairman.
Others might think I have it easy
just working on my paintings, but
what I have done is
smiling and smooching the others instead of my father.
I had received the most suitable education
in dealing with the customers.
Mm.
With the 14.2% shares Min Hyeok has,
It would be difficult to keep the K-Hotel.
I am a person who will soon be joining this family.
Chairman,
The hotel shares K-Construction will be selling,
please give them to me.
I heard you were supposed to get my father's hotel shares?
I have to take what I should take.
Because our marriage... It's business, right?
And what happened that day...
What happened that day... About what?
I practiced singing for days for you without sleeping, but
you just left, that?
Or bringing a cheap ring and asking me to marry,
when you were asking to please help you.
If that's not it either,
when you brought the person
who killed the woman you loved, and had her sitting next to me?
Listen to me.
I thought about it.
I tried to understand it too.
If Min Hyeok you died, would I have done the same thing like you?
I probably would've been like that for a while,
get angry and cry...
But keep acting like this after years,
it's an obsession.
Stop it!
To you and also to that dead woman...
It's a meaningless obsession that doesn't do any good.
I said stop it, Shin Se Yeon.
For all you have done, even Seo Ji Hee that woman
would understand your heart, how sorry you are.
So, stop it now... Taking out your anger on others.
I said stop it!
What you're doing to that woman Kang Yoo Jeong!
It's childish. If you make that weak woman crumble,
do you think Seo Ji Hee will be touched because
you're such a great person and she is grateful?
Hey, Shin Se Yeon!
I told you to stop it!
Right! Raise your voice to me.
Get angry or cry. Do it in front of me!
Read it.
The revenge started because of love... How it ends.
[Wuthering Heights]
RET
SECRET
Earlier, some man took care of the bill.
You came.
You came at the right time.
Let's move together tomorrow.
Hey, let's eat.
Okay.
Thank you, Unni.
What?
How difficult can adding one more setting on the table be?
My son.
He looks handsome right?
He's sick.
A lot.
What was that? Ummm...
I can't even remember the name. What kind of
disease has such long name?!
It's a kind of a hereditary disease on the mom's side.
My son whose only sin is being born from me.
I have to save him.
Whatever it takes, I have to save him.
Yes Unni, be strong.
Even though he's sick,
you being able to stay next to him.
That is a blessing.
Don't make a face like that.
I promised that I would not be sad anymore because of San.
I am thankful that he came along and made me happy.
That's how I am going to think from now on.
That way I can live.
Here.
I'm sorry.
When I saw you and San tightly holding each other,
I was belligerant because I was reminded of my son.
Because I was narrow minded.
A prosecutor under investigation isn't desirable,
first of all.
Regardless, because there is a surplus of
law school grads these days,
the attorneys are a dime a dozen in corporations.
Be that as it may,
how did you end things that
you're infamous in the field?
I think it'd be difficult for you to find a job prospect for a while.
Ah, it's just that, I really have to meet with the President.
Is there any way you can help me?
What is it, Substitute?
It's that I...
received this.
The debt I'm responsible for has been transferred to you,
President.
How did this happen?
That just means that you have a debt to pay me.
Can't you understand that?
That's what I mean. Why?
In order to get rid of the flies (bothersome people) near
your bakery,
I suffered a loss.
What are you looking at?
I will pay you back without fail.
I will pay you back for sure.
What are you doing?
We're going to be late for our 2 O'clock appointment.
I will "for sure" pay you back.
I will pay you back for sure, sir.
This is my contact information.
I won't run away.
I will pay you back, I swear it on my life.
So, as for that bakery...
Just leave that bakery as...
That's right. That bakery.
You're saying that is a precious place, right?
Yes.
That's why I bought it.
So that I can bulldoze it over.
I told you before.
That crap (bakery) is nothing compared to what you took away from me.
President. That's...
Look here.
I know what your and Min Hyeok's relationship is.
But, you come here to see him again?
It's not something you should get involved with.
I'm the person who're going to marry you.
Last time it was the surgery fee, this time it's the debt.
Are you thick-skinned or shameless?
Take this woman out of here.
Immediately!
President!
President. President!!
Presi... Listen, please!
President!
You left as if you won't ever see me again.
What brings you here?
I don't know myself as to why I came here.
It's just
that I wanted to see the other world.
Because the world I live in is too suffocating.
I heard you resigned your job as a prosecutor.
I didn't have the time to go around and see the paintings.
It was more pressing to read one more law book in that time,
and I struggled to not be surpassed by others.
Why people take their time out to see the paintings,
now...
I think I know.
So, what is your impression?
I'd like to go there.
If I can go.
I'm satisfied with it because I was able to paint it in one try.
When you paint over a mistaken brush stroke to correct it,
you end up not remembering what it was that you were
trying to paint in the first place.
In those cases, one must bravely change the canvas,
but it's difficult to do, stupidly.
It's not stupid but natural.
Because regretting over the time spent to correct your mistake
is human.
That's your story, isn't it, Do Hoon?
I don't think you can lie well, Do Hoon.
Excuse me.
Are you okay?
Aiyoo. I'm okay
But, this bunch. I was supposed to deliver
quickly across the street where a car is.
Just give them to me. I'll do it.
But, do you think you may need to go to the hospital?
Aiyoo, it's okay.
I'm sorry.
Hello. You seem hard at work.
I'm going to take a look here, okay?
Illegal Flyers (ad leaflet) Special Crackdown Period.
- Look here.
Yes?
"Cha Ma Sseo"
Cha Ma Sseo: Adult nightclub (Cham At Sseo means I stifled something and let it go)
What were they stifling?
It wasn't me.
A woman fell down so...
Everyone says it's not theirs.
Excuse me.
You know me, right?
Was it the hit-and-run?
A woman and a baby died.
I'm right.
How long has it been that you got out that now your doing this?
How could you do that, really?
Born in July 21st, right?
It was not me, really.
How can I trust you?
Is there a person who can guarantee your identification?
I enjoyed the drawings.
See you next time.
I'm on my way meeting my friend to drink.
Do you want to go together??
Last time, you just left.
Se Yeon.
Oh, you guys are here.
Have you finished?
Where shall we go?
Who is this?
Are you already cheating?
What are you going to do when Min Hyeok hears about this?
No lo somos...
You're right.
We are exactly like you think.
I like Min Hyeok because he's fun
Can you spread the rumors.
I don't think so.
You're right. We are in that kind of relationship.
If Se Yeon think like that.
What's going on here.
Oh.
Where are you going?
Let's go together with us.
Yeah. It can be boring if there are only girls.
What do you do?
What do you think he's doing?
This person, he's unemployed, he was recently a prosecutor.
How did you two meet?
Was it three years ago?
A black dress and
red high heels.
She was angry and was drunk so she yelled.
That time, she looked at me.
"Did you enjoy it?"
She said that.
That was our first meeting.
Do you remember that?
Do you remember?
Even then, we drank alcohol.
I heard that Shinha Hotel became
the World Forum this time.
Didn't know there was something
that Shin Se Yeon can't do.
This is not about Se Yeon.
What is this? You're defending your wife already?
Ay...you!
You don't have any friends, do you?
Why do I need friends?
You must be so happy. You have a lot of money but your a hobo.
But,
Should I marry Se Yeon?
Again?
Your company isn't a neighborhood store.
Try making a mistake.
"That's why an heir isn't good, we need a professional manager"
They'll all bite you right away.
If you want to secure your place, be good to Se Yeon.
I don't know.
If you're not going to do it...
Can our family take her?
What did you say?
Everyone is telling me to remarry.
For me, I would be thankful for Se Yeon.
Are you crazy?
Never.
She was meant for a better guy than me or you.
I'm warning you.
Don't touch her.
This is irritating.
Este es mi número de contacto.
I'm not going anywhere.
I will put my life on it and pay it back.
So, the bakery
Just leave the bakery.
I need to collect my debt.
[Kang Yoo Jeong]
[010-138-4736]
Kang Yoo Jeong
"Driver"
010-
Conductor.
There is a woman that I would like to help.
No,
I wanted to help her.
But, I couldn't do it.
Because I'm too late.
If I look at you,
I keep thinking about that woman.
Do I...
look like someone that needs help?
Are you not?
Even if you spread rumors,
people don't listen if they're not interested.
In that case, you have show them in their eyes.
Yoo Jeong
[Eradicate social evils]
[We'll do it first.]
Oppa.
Thank you.
And I'm sorry.
I don't have anyone else to call.
You refused all of my favors and...
You were doing these kind of things?
You even got help from Jo Min Hyeok,
and do this kind of stuff?
It's not like that.
[All Family Job Sharing Organization]
- It's an organization for ex-convicts' rehabilitation.
They'll find the job for you.
One who said to break up was you.
Let's not
see each other like this.
[President]
Yes?
- Driver
Hello?
Come and pick me up.
What?
- Hey, driver.
- Driver.
Driver, driver~
Take the wheel.
I can't drive.
My license was cancelled.
Oh, that's right.
You did a hit-and-run.
Then why did you come?
I thought you were too drunk and something might happen.
So you're worried.
What are you?
You have time to worry...
I guess you're life is fine?
I'll call another driver for you.
Give me the key.
Let go.
No. Do you want to end up like me?
Customer, where should I take you?
Uhh, wait a second.
Hey, boss?
Did you sleep well?
Why are you here?
Do you not remember?
Yesterday, you drank a lot
so even when I asked you where you lived, you couldn't reply
Yesterday, it seems you had too much to drink.
Eat this.
You want me to eat this?
Eat it before it cools.
And,
I organized how I am going to pay back the debt.
These days I am learning hard at my job.
I might be able to pay back my debt faster.
So, the bakery...
Spoon.
Water...
-Huh?
Water.
- Ah, water.
Why do you pour water like that?
It's alright. It's alright. Don't think about it.
Don't laugh.
Don't laugh in front of me.
Gosh.
Boss.
Here.
You phone, it's in the car from yesterday,
I'm not beholden to you, alright?
I'm taking this off of your debt.
Yes.
Then the bakery...
I don't want to see a person who has already refused my offer.
I didn't know that K Group had
so much interest in paintings.
K Culture Foundation, in every year of particular time,
they've been buying new artists' art work at a high price.
Shinha Gallery is the main connection and got several million dollars from Shinha Foundation as a commission.
That's what I've collected for 2 years.
I get how you're maintaining a good relationship
with Assemblyman Shin.
You came here to talk about what we all know?
There's know way that the prosecution
doesn't know what I know.
In this country where anything can be
excused with the word 'nation,'
K Group isn't a "national" company that deals with exports like Customs, is it?
To see in that way, K Group
is a good provision for government.
Since they always need some
other issues to turn nations' view.
There will be a public announcement of the sale of the Port of Incheon next week.
The public will demand the re-investigation of K Group.
And the Prosecution won't let it pass this time.
Why did you come to me, while you have all that?
Please give me that opportunity, once again.
You brought me information that the Prosecutors already have.
Why should I give you another opportunity?
You see as much as you know and you can stop if you know.
You'll never ride those wheelchair again.
What's the reason that you turned back all of sudden?
Don't worry, I'm not trying to take your spot.
I will become the best in K-Group.
I have seen, endlessly, people that had good parents and did no work but received everything.
I want to see a junior colleague like you win.
But, listen well.
A person that Chairman is trying to make the best
Is only Min Hyeok.
You cannot be Jo Min Hyeok.
No matter how hard you try,
you will only be a well trained dog.
Look after me well.
I am different from the Chairman.
Those who so thoroughly throw away their convictions
cannot be trusted even more.
I'll try to look after you. Good bye.
Oh my goodness! Yoo Jeong!
Oh my goodness!
Long time no see. It is nice to see you.
Did you know how worried I was when I learned you were living with her?
Is Ja Yoon being mean to you?
What do you mean? She's the one being mean to me for drinking a lot and sleeping in.
Then why don't you drink less and wake up early?
Did late year sergeant get a vacation or something?
Look here, Yoo Jeong.
If you're uncomfortable staying in her home or
if you ever get into a big fight or if you feel very sad, you can come to unni's house.
I'm single, so I'll let you have a room for cheap.
Yes, okay.
Oh, but Unni, where do you sell these?
Do you take these to the market?
Yoo Jeong, this is
How dare you say "this!?"
Yoo Jeong.
Don't call them "this" and "that." Call is our baby.
Aren't our babies so beautiful?
People go crazy and become regulars!
Just let us do the buying and selling.
So don't worry and just move your belongings.
Those investment to remodel the meeting room
for assorting this year's World Forum,
How are you going to collect these?
In Shinha Hotel, the CEO personally guided
the inspection team.
For ours, why did the general manager did it instead?
In order to recover the loss from the first half year,
You needed to make a right action for the forum.
Do you have a strategy for the second half year?
I heard that forum assortment
was changed in the last minute.
Did you know?
They said that in the executive commission,
it was already nominated to Shinha Hotel.
Didn't you guys already know?
The list of those who supported Shinha,
Should I reveal it?
Hello?
Boss?
Can you not hear well?
Hello?
Shin Se Yeon.
What is this? Is this what you meant by meeting a friend?
Something good happened to me
so I wanted be congratulated by Se Yeon.
Do I need your permission to meet with a friend?
A friend?
Let's go. The car's at the front.
I am also your friend.
Can't I also congratulate you?
You must really be friends.
To see that Se Yeon called you here.
I asked her to do it.
I wanted come here because there really isn't a chance to look at Se Yeon's paintings.
Attorney Ahn, you're very shameless than I expected.
Oh yeah, your not an attorney anymore.
It probably was hard getting into our company.
You have a lot of talent.
But now you need to meet some girls that fits those standards.
That's right.
Please introduce me to some good woman.
Is there anyone like Se Yeon?
Se Yeon is my fiancee.
From the time you start working at K Group, she is your superior.
Please talk with manners.
She's not someone you can meet.
If you know that well, why do you treat her like that?
Like you said, Se Yeon
is not the type of person who should be treated like that by you.
Se Yeon and I,
are not in the type of relationship where
you can talk about carelessly.
Saying it carelessly is probably you, Jo Min Hyeok.
Se Yeon,
is the type of person who I want to take away
because she does not deserve you.
Just because I am sitting here drinking wine,
doesn't mean I'm in the same class as you.
Whatever reason you came to this company,
you are always below me, and that is not going to change.
Just because you are being treated well, doesn't mean
you can act like this. Isn't it so obvious?
Isn't getting a free ride more evident?
Isn't it shameless to get treated because of your parents?
Do you think that's something you can say?
Jo Min Heok, are you here to fight?
Didn't you just hear?
It's okay.
He didn't say anything wrong either.
I'm not alright.
He's my guest. I don't want to displease him.
You cook too?
Sometimes.
You've never done it for me.
You've never told me you want to.
It's good, Se Yeon.
It doesn't look like Min Hyeok has no feelings for you.
I can tell from a man's perspective.
Do Hoon, your actually a good actor.
I thought you wouldn't be good at lying.
A girl you would want to steal?
It's not a lie.
Why those main characters from the drama
fall in love and get married in the real life,
I get it.
If you immerse in your role,
I guess those feelings actually arise.
It's hot.
What is this? You want me to drink this?
There's nothing better that this after working hard.
Why is it so sweet?
Nevermind.
Are you playing with me?
30 years?
Do I have to look at you for 30 more years just to get a little sum of money?
It's too much money for me.
I'll work harder.
Then, a few years will be taken off.
A few years?
I don't want to.
I heard you have a boyfriend.
Ask your boyfriend to help you.
why, did you get dumped?
you did get dumped!
of course, what kind of man would accept a woman who hit-and-ran as his girlfriend?
He's not that kind of person.
What do you mean he's not. I can tell just by once glance.
You met him thinking that he was a genuine man.
Yet he took after marriage was brought up.
Aren't all those men you met like that?
I said it's not like that!
I...
do have a lot of debt because of him but,
I didn't break up with him because of that.
My oppa,
He's not the worthless kind of man you think he is.
Even after he broke up with me,
Even when I did stupid things,
He's a person who dropped me off
to the hospital to save me.
He was there all night
and went away without even saying hi to me,
because I might feel sorry.
Hey, that's...
That's..
So,
Don't talk like you know everything.
Ahn Do Hoon.
You're that great?
It's what I've been saving
and advance pay all together.
Severance Pay?
I've become a part of the K Group legal team.
The benefits are good.
Do Hoon, you've decided end things with the government?
Yes.
I didn't give up my dream.
I've made a decision not to give up my dream.
A store in Shinha plaza has opened up.
Please go take a look at it yourselves.
A store?
Stop doing work where you have to listen to other's dislikes.
I'll give you the money.
I'm saying this because I knew you wouldn't take a break even if I asked you to.
The two of you have fought your whole lives over your jobs.
It's become difficult for me to sit by and watch.
Suffering because of me,
living with only watching me,
I would like to pay you back.
Mom, this looks nice.
That looks too old.
How about this one?
No, I want this one.
I want both blue and red.
Just pick one.
Why?
Your only going to carry it around a few times a year. It is a waste of money.
My friends buy a lot and pick what they want daily.
You, I'm going to tell on you that you came here instead of going to your lessons.
Mom!
Whenever you talk like this, you sound like a stepmother.
Min Joo.
Those girls get whatever they want because their parents don't care about them.
I will call someone to get Min Joo the bag you will love.
Really?
Mom, you want me to buy an imitation?
That is not just a imitation, customer.
It is a triple A brand where the maker created with all their might.
Aigo, princess.
Our princess looks so pretty. It is a right statement.
Imitation, who would know that it is an imitation?
Whether or not it's real only depends on the person's feelings.
Now, try closing your eyes princess. One, two, three!
Give me a Dolce and Gabbana bag or Chanel.
Now, empty you thoughts.
Think that you do not know anything.
Now open your eyes. One, two, three.
Look at this. This line, this
brightness. Look at this beautiful bag.
Every bug will slip off this bag.
"This is a place where I shouldn't be around!"
(Voice of a bug)
Now, look at this bag.
But still...
Min Joo.
Rather than carrying around the same one for a while,
wouldn't you feel better carrying a different one everyday?
And,
it's fun watching people get jealous over imitation bags thinking it's real.
Oh my goodness! Long time no see.
You're getting younger.
Sandara Wang, it's been a while.
Yes, I've been afar to...
New York, Seattle, Manhattan
because of business...
Please introduce yourselves. This is Madam Hong.
You know me right?
Yes.
How dare you come here?
With what in mind did you come here?
It's not like that.
You're a bold one, aren't you?
Last time you sold that ring and now you dare to set foot in the house?
You face looks naive but your actions are like a fox.
Mink Hyeok's taste is so... peculiar.
Why are you here?
What are you doing?
Min Hyeok.
Now your meeting this kind of woman?
No, the boss and I don't have that kind of relationship.
What kind of woman is this kind of woman?
Do you have to tell you with my own mouth?
You can just tell that she sticks by smelling money.
Don't meet with Min Hyeok again.
I'm not the type of person who has respect, so I don't know what I'm going to do next time.
What do you think your doing?
I can understand a man acting like this before a marriage.
But Min Hyeok.
If your going to meet a woman, pick one with more class.
That isn't something Ahjumma can say.
You looked at dad's money.
You came here in this house waiting for my mom to die. Is that something you can say?
Let's go.
Are you crazy?
Now your even following me to my house?
I didn't know this was you house.
You said you were going to pay your debt but now your doing stuff like this.
I'm seeing you frequently these days, my friend.
I can't today. We have things to discuss.
I sent a present to Ahn Do Hoon's house. Did you get it?
I hope you like it.
Do you want a glass?
I told have the time to drink at this time of the day.
You know Attorney Do Hoon right?
No,
he's not an attorney anymore since he works in my company now.
He's Lawyer Do Hoon.
Did you not know?
What's wrong with your expression?
Do you have a prior relation with Lawyer Do Hoon?
No.
He's my friend.
Now that I think about it, because of you, I gained a friend.
Why?
Is it weird that we're friends?
Lawyer Do Hoon, looked at us like that earlier.
Yes, unni.
I'm going now.
I won't ever come find you anymore.
It's important to look and seem smart and elegant even when selling one item.
Unnie, don't forget we're splitting 7:3, and I'm 7.
How about some soju and stew?
Hey.
What are you doing?
Do you know who he is?
I know.
You know?
Although you know, your still like this?
Then what about you?
You quit being an attorney.
Now your working in that company? What does that mean?
I heard you two are friends.
Friends?
Yes,
He does whatever he wants with his friends, I guess I can call him a friend.
I didn't quit being an attorney and entered the company on my own will.
I don't want to talk long.
I have a debt.
All of my debt went to him. I don't know how it happened.
Yoo Jeong. Wake up.
Joo Min Hyeok has played with you for a reason.
I can't pay back a debt.
Do you know what Jo Min Hyeok did?
Do you know how much I hate him?
DO you know who disgusted I am?
Stop saying stupid things like that!
We've already paid our debt.
We had a long and tiring four years.
Listen to me.
I'm worried.
Stay away from Min Hyeok.
I'll look into te debt and contact you.
Lee Yea Jin.
Yea Jin!
Ahh!
Ahh sshi! You're not going to go!
I'm not going to run!
I said, I'm not going to run!
Just hurry up and hit me.
Isn't that why you followed me?
What rotten luck to meet you like this...
What if I hit you?
If I hit you, will San come back alive?
Then get hit!
Get hit a hundred, a thousand times!
Ahh!
Why are you like this?
San? What about San?
He died.
The work place.
That's the last time
I hugged my San.
At first, I wondered what I would do when I met you.
Every night, I thought about how to relieve my heart.
That's how I spent my time.
Why did you do it?
I have always been curious about that.
Why did you
Why did you do that to San?
Why did you do it?
Why did you do it!
I didn't know.
I'm not like you but,
I also liked San.
I really did. I thought that San would be alright.
Unni,
Unni, they only wanted me to make you fail your test.
Test?
I only did what I was told.
Unni,
did you ever do someone wrong?
Do you know what Min Hyeok did to you?
Be carefree when your inside,
When you get out, your life will get hard.
Try hurting as much as me.
Lose the most precious person to you.
Congratulations on your entrance.
♫ Each of us, we have loved
Each of us, we have shed tears
♫ Living under the same sky
♫ It was happiness to me
What is this?
Why are you here?
You said that person looked at the dead person and walked away right?
Are you sure it's this woman's footprint?
It was taken on the day of Ji Hee's accident.
If you know
how much about Ahn Do Hoon, you would be surprised.
Is the blackbox file filed?
Can I ask of a favor as friends?
On the day of the accident,
did you really leave after looking?